<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game id="6032" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./DK - Jungle Climber (USA).zip</path>
		<name>DK - Jungle Climber</name>
		<desc>King K. Rool is up to no good again, and it-s up to Donkey Kong to swing into action. Using the same simple control scheme that made the DK: King of Swing Game Boy Advance SP game so accessible and fun to play, players of all skill levels can swing and climb to new heights made possible by the dual screens of Nintendo DS.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20070910T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>PAON Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/DK - Jungle Climber (USA).jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game id="6072" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mega Man Zero Collection (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man Zero Collection</name>
		<desc>Mega Man Zero Collection is a set of all four games in the Mega Man Zero series on a single game cart.  It includes:

Mega Man Zero
Mega Man Zero 2
Mega Man Zero 3
Mega Man Zero 4

In addition to the four games, Mega Man Zero Collection also features an art gallery with works from the games in the series.  The e-Reader cards that were exclusive to the Japanese version of Mega Man Zero 3 and provided in-game enhancements are now discoverable throughout that game as collectibles.  There is also the option to play through all four games in one continuous playthrough, rather than having to select each game individually.  Finally, an included "Easy Mode" makes the game more accessible to those not used to the game's tough difficulty level.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20100608T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Compilation-Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Mega Man Zero Collection (USA).jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game id="6230" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Metal Slug 7 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Metal Slug 7</name>
		<desc>The Peregrine Falcon Strike Force, the Ikari Warriors, and the SPARROWS are once again on a search for General Morden and his army. Their mission is to catch General Morden and prevent his attempts at another coup d'état on the government. However, as soon as Morden was defeated, a strange army from the future came to his aid. Now, they must face Morden once again and this time, put a stop to his plans once and for all.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20081121T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter-Shooter / Run and Gun-Action-Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Metal Slug 7 (USA).jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game id="5807" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Metroid Prime Hunters (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Metroid Prime - Hunters</name>
		<desc>An episode in the Metroid Prime series which started on the GameCube, this game takes place between Metroid Prime and Metroid Prime 2: Echoes. Interstellar bounty hunter Samus Aran is sent to the distant Alimbic Cluster by the Galactic Federation to investigate a message saying that the source of ultimate power lies in this desolate part of the galaxy, once home to an advanced culture. 
 
Samus is not alone, however. Other races have heard this mysterious message, too. Six other bounty hunters, each with unique characteristics, will do everything to get their hands on the Alimbic relics for their own reasons. 
 
The single-player mode is more focused on shooting than other Metroid games but also has puzzles in classic Metroid fashion. Unlike previous games, Samus has all her moves from the start, but she still has to look for weapons. The player may also run into other bounty hunters in this mode. 
 
The multiplayer mode is similar to Unreal Tournament or Quake games. Players can choose from any hunter that was defeated in single-player mode. There are seven modes in total including: Nodes, Survival, Bounty, Prime Hunter, Battle, Capture, and Defender. Each mode has its own unique rules. There are a vast number of arenas that can be played over local wireless or Nintendo Wi-Fi Connection. When using friend codes, voice chat before and after matches is enabled.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20060505T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Lightgun Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Metroid Prime Hunters (USA).jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game id="6172" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Naruto Shippuden - Ninja Council 4 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Naruto Shippuden - Ninja Council 4</name>
		<desc>Set two and a half years after the events of the classic Naruto series, Naruto fans are introduced to older characters as the storyline advances and unfolds with copious plot twists. Naruto Shippuden: Ninja Council 4 also allows gamers to follow an older Naruto and his friends on the quest to save Gaara from the sinister Akatsuki organization. Players are able to choose their allies and form a three-man squad with special jutsu techniques to ward off looming danger. Dedicated franchise fans and new Naruto fighters alike can utilize the touch screen to unleash their unique jutsu attacks and take on anyone that gets in their way. As an added bonus, unlockable jutsu allow aspiring ninja to explore previously unreachable areas.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>20090602T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tomy</developer>
		<publisher>Tomy</publisher>
		<genre>Fight-Adventure</genre>
		<image>./media/images/Naruto Shippuden - Ninja Council 4 (USA).jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game id="6523" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Need for Speed - Nitro (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Need for Speed - Nitro</name>
		<desc>Need for Speed: Nitro brings the fun and exhilaration of high-speed racing to your Nintendo DS.  It brings the Need for Speed franchise's trademark attitude and car culture with deep and thrilling gameplay.  Gamers must battle through the mayhem of relentless cops master the art of drifting to gain boost at 150 mph and prove themselves across five mega cities at a gripping 60 frames per second.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>20091105T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>EA Games</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<image>./media/images/Need for Speed - Nitro (USA).jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game id="5803" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Need for Speed - Underground 2 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Need for Speed - Underground 2</name>
		<desc>This installment in the Need for Speed series, Underground 2 is a racing game based on illicit, night time races, with the player gaining street credit, cash and access to unique tuner parts by schooling the competition.

Taking place in a massive, open city, NFS Underground 2 allows players to explore the city at will, engaging random challengers and moving into the coveted Underground Racing League. Once in the Underground Racing League, the player advances first by race wins, then with building up their tuner car and taking on tougher opponents. The objective is to win all Underground Racing League engagements and trick out your car to the max.

The PC version is the only version that allows the user to save magazine screen shots of your tricked out car to disk.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>20050510T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Need for Speed - Underground 2 (USA).jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game id="5748" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./New Super Mario Bros. (USA).zip</path>
		<name>New Super Mario Bros</name>
		<desc>In an all new 2D side-scrolling adventure, Mario and Luigi return after nearly fifteen years. The first traditional Mario Bros. game since Super Mario World. 
 
The character models are rendered in real time 3D, allowing for a far greater number of moves ever before seen in a Mario Bros. title. Also as the game is on DS, the touch screen allows players to store an additional power-up and view the distance still to go in a level.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20060515T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action-Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/New Super Mario Bros. (USA).jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game id="86747" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Pokemon Platinum Version (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Pokemon - Platinum Version</name>
		<desc>Together with Pokémon Diamond and Pokémon Pearl, this game is the 3rd games in the 4th generation of the Pokémon series. Set in a new region, Sinnoh, it includes 107 new Pokémon, bringing the total up to 493. Pokémon Platinum includes for the first time in the 4th generation, the Battle Frontier which can be played on and off-line, make Poffins on-line. Players can collect badges, challenge the Elite Four, and become the ultimate Pokémon master. 
 
The game continues the basic idea of previous Pokémon games - the player, a new trainer, sets out on a quest to catch every known Pokémon and defeat the Pokémon league. Along the way, the player will attempt to foil the plots of the evil organization, Team Galactic, who seek to use a trio of legendary Pokémon to awaken a sleeping titan with the power to control space. There are many sidequests and other activities along the way, the Battle Frontier, expanded on-line options, downloadable content via Mystery Gift, a brand new GTS with the option to receive notifications of completed traded over the Wii, record battle videos, the option to submit one's Pokémon party data for others to see and the Distortion World, which defies the laws of gravity and contains Platinum's mascot, Giratina. 
 
The core Pokémon series features an RPG turn-based battle system. Each monster can learn up to four attacks. In a single turn, the two opponents select their attacks, and the one with the higher Speed attacks first. The amount of damage is influenced by the Attack and Defense stats. In the past, attacks were automatically classified as Physical or Special based on their elemental type. In Diamond, Pearl, and Platinum each attack can be individually categorized, so attacks which use natural elements are Special, and those which use simple force are Physical. 
 
The Pokémon Contests from Ruby and Sapphire return, with many new features. In addition to the attack performance, where the player must try to impress the judge with flashy moves, players will also dress up their Pokémon and dance in time to music. Diamond and Pearl also bring back the real time system from Gold and Silver, where day and night are reflected in your game. Some Pokémon are only catchable during certain times.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20090322T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<image>./media/images/Pokemon Platinum Version (USA).jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game id="5977" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Rayman DS (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Rayman DS</name>
		<desc>The character with no arms and no legs makes his debut on the Nintendo DS. Rayman must defeat the pirates who have enslaved his world. As Rayman, you'll travel through magical worlds where you can explore waterfalls, sea caves, and pirate hideouts. Master Rayman's special moves to progress through each challenging level. The DS's bottom screen let you monitor your progress, track your lums, and keep an eye on Rayman's health.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20050324T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>DC Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Rayman DS (USA).jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game id="5754" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Resident Evil - Deadly Silence (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Resident Evil - Deadly Silence</name>
		<desc>Resident Evil: Deadly Silence brings the original PlayStation survival horror game, Resident Evil, to your Nintendo DS. You can play through the original game or in rebirth mode. Rebirth mode is essentially the same story but with new puzzles, monster placements, and touch-screen-specific minigames. You can also partake in a multiplayer match that challenges you and your opponents to complete a stretch of the game not only with the fastest time, but also with the most points, which are earned by killing enemies along the way.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20060207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Resident Evil - Deadly Silence (USA).jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game id="5993" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Sonic and Sega All Stars Racing (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Sonic &amp; Sega All-Stars Racing</name>
		<desc>In a frantic battle to the checkered flag, Sonic and friends speed around tracks set in medieval castle ramparts, lush rainforests and bustling cities, all taken from the visually rich and varied universes of Sonic and SEGA. Fan favorites such as Dr. Eggman, Tails, AiAi, Amigo and many more will join Sonic in their custom built vehicles, revving their engines and jostling to stay ahead of the pack. Each character will speed around the track in cars, planes, motorbikes, and in Aiai's case -- a banana mobile! Secret short cuts, swift handling and avoiding strategically placed obstacles are certainly the best way to get to the top of the podium.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20100226T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Sonic and Sega All Stars Racing (USA).jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game id="6089" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Sonic Classic Collection (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Sonic Classic Collection</name>
		<desc>Sonic Classic Collection is a set of four games from the Sonic series on one cart.  The games included on the cart are:

1.  Sonic the Hedgehog
2.  Sonic the Hedgehog 2
3.  Sonic the Hedgehog 3
4.  Sonic and Knuckles

The compilation also includes Knuckles in Sonic the Hedgehog 2 and Knuckles in Sonic the Hedgehog 3, which were originally accessed by connecting Sonic 2 or Sonic 3 into the Sonic and Knuckles cart.  All multiplayer modes in the games have been removed, making this a single player only game.

In addition to the main game, an art gallery can also be accessed.  This gallery features promotional art from Sonic 1, Sonic 2, Sonic 3, Sonic Spinball and Sonic Drift.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20100312T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Compilation-Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Sonic Classic Collection (USA).jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game id="5966" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Sonic Rush Adventure (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Sonic Rush Adventure</name>
		<desc>While flying in their plane across the ocean, looking for a strange energy source, Sonic and Tails' plane is struck by lightning!  They plunge into the murky depths of the ocean...and awaken on a small island.  A local, a raccoon named Marine, informs them that they are on Southern Island.  With Marine and Tails' help, Sonic sets about to explore the nearby islands.

Sonic Rush Adventure is a side-scrolling adventure game, and the sequel to Sonic Rush.  Sonic's goal through these platform levels is to zip through as quickly as possible.  By pressing the B Button while in the air, Sonic can increase his Tension Gauge by performing aerial tricks. Pressing Y uses a Super Boost, which will allow him to plow through anything in his path at amazing speed, but drains the Tension Gauge.

When Sonic reaches the treasure chest at the end of each level, he will be given a material that can be used for construction of ships and other devices.  At first, Sonic is stranded on Southern Island, but after the construction of the waterbike, he can travel to other islands and explore them.  Similar to The Legend of Zelda: Phantom Hourglass, the player must plot a path to the next island using the stylus, and then provide limited control over the ship as it travels.  However, Sonic has different ships, each of which are notably different from Link's steamboat.

Sonic Rush Adventure also features a Battle Mode, where players can either play locally with a friend, or across the world through Nintendo Wi-Fi Connection.  Players can take each other on in a one-on-one race through various levels as each player aims to get to the end first.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20070918T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Sonic Rush Adventure (USA).jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game id="6101" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Spider-Man 2 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Spider-Man 2</name>
		<desc>A pseudo 3D (game is played on a 2D plane, but the stages will rotate around Spider-Man at certain points) beat-em-up/adventure game. Vicarious Visions' first title on the Nintendo DS, the game puts the player into the role of Peter Parker (AKA Spider-Man) playing through various missions with varying objectives and pitting him against the likes of Mysterio, The Vulture, and the main villain, Doctor Octavius. The missions themselves vary from missions requiring you to find all hostages to bomb defusal missions and fast paced boss battles.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20050324T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Vicarious Vision</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Spider-Man 2 (USA).jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game id="5764" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Super Mario 64 DS (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario 64 DS</name>
		<desc>Mario, Luigi, and Wario have all gone to the Mushroom Palace for some of Princess Peach's famous home made cake. However, when they don't return its up to the heroic dino Yoshi to find out what's wrong.

In this portable remake of the original Super Mario 64 You' are able to play as different characters from the Mario franchise. Wario, Yoshi, Luigi, and of course Mario. Each character has different abilities to be made use of during the games expanded quest. 

The game now features 150 Stars to collect up from the previous 120, new stages with new bosses, changes to old stages and bosses, and a multiplayer in which player compete to get the most stars.

The game also includes over two dozen mini games that make use of both screens and the touch pad.

The DS touch screen can be used to mimic analog control.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20041120T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Platform / Run Jump-Action-Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Super Mario 64 DS (USA).jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game id="5753" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Legend of Zelda - Phantom Hourglass, The (USA).zip</path>
		<name>The Legend Of Zelda - Phantom Hourglass</name>
		<desc>Continue the Wind Waker adventure in Link's first DS game. 
 
The epic story of The Legend of Zelda: The Wind Waker continues as Link finds himself lost and alone in unknown seas in a new adventure. Featuring intuitive touch-screen controls and innovative puzzles, The Legend of Zelda: Phantom Hourglass offers new challenges for fans of the series and an easy-to-grasp introduction for gamers new to The Legend of Zelda. But time grows short, and only the Phantom Hourglass can buy Link the minutes he'll need to survive. 
 
Many months have passed since the events of The Legend of Zelda: The Wind Waker, and Link, Tetra and Tetra's band of pirates have set sail in search of new lands. They come across a patch of ocean covered in a dense fog, in which they discover an abandoned ship. Tetra falls into danger when she explores the ship alone, and Link falls into the ocean when he attempts to rescue her. When he washes up unconscious on the shores of a mysterious island, he is awakened by the sound of a fairy's voice. With the aid of this fairy, he sets off to find Tetra and his way back to the seas he once knew.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20071001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games-Adventure</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./media/images/Legend of Zelda, The - Phantom Hourglass (USA) (En,Fr,Es).jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game id="5760" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Legend of Zelda - Spirit Tracks, The (USA).zip</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda: Spirit Tracks</name>
		<desc>Ride into adventure with Link and Princess Zelda. 
 
? Wield weapons and solve puzzles, all with your stylus 
 
? Duke it out with friends in multiplayer battle mode 
 
? Link and Zelda adventure together for the first time 
 
The Legend of Zelda: Spirit Tracks sets hero Link on a daring new adventure. The game provides players with a new story, more puzzles and even a new mode of transportation. In this game, Link voyages by train, which offers up new possibilities for problem-solving. The game has the same look and feel established in the hit Nintendo DS game The Legend of Zelda: Phantom Hourglass. 
 
? Link has a valuable new companion. While navigating dungeons, he?s accompanied by a Phantom, a hulking suit of armor that responds to his commands. Players can tap the Phantom to take command of him, then draw a line on the touchscreen to direct him where to go. The stout Phantom can walk through fire or lava, be used as a platform to carry Link above dangers, or even run interference to block Link from harm. 
 
? When Link conducts the train, players enjoy a satisfying combination of action and real-time puzzle solving as they determine which track to take and how to best manipulate their speed. When on the train, Link must plot the best route to the end of the line around ever-moving obstacles. While en route, Link might need to fire an onboard cannon at enemies who attack the train or sound the whistle to scare animals off the tracks. 
 
? Link uses a variety of new items and weapons, including the Whirlwind, which players activate by blowing into the microphone of the Nintendo DS system. 
 
? As with The Legend of Zelda: Phantom Hourglass, players can draw notes on the in-game maps using the stylus on the touch screen.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20091207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Legend of Zelda - Spirit Tracks, The (USA).jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game id="5838" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Tomb Raider - Underworld (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Tomb Raider - Underworld</name>
		<desc>For generations, stories have been told of the fearsome weapon of Thor, the Norse god of thunder. Legend holds that Thor?s hammer had the power to smash mountains into valleys and to destroy even the gods. For more than a thousand years it has existed only as a myth...until now.

In an ancient ruin on the floor of the Mediterranean Sea, Lara Croft uncovers proof of the Norse underworld and the mythical hammer. As she attempts to unravel the secrets behind these myths, Lara?s perilous journey leads her toward a forgotten power that, if unleashed, could lay waste to all civilization.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20081121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crystal Dynamics</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Tomb Raider - Underworld (USA).jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game id="6825" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Transformers - Dark of the Moon - Autobots (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Transformers - Dark of the Moon - Decepticons</name>
		<desc>It has been three years since MEGATRON and the DECEPTICONS last threatened the world. Earth's leaders believe that MEGATRON has fled the planet in defeat-but OPTIMUS PRIME knows better. An alien transmission is intercepted, exposing MEGATRON'S plan to spread chaos and fear among the humans, and unleash the ultimate DECEPTICON assassin: SHOCKWAVE! The AUTOBOTS must hunt MEGATRON, neutralize SHOCKWAVE, and save their new home from total destruction at the hands of the DECEPTICONS.</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20110624T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Behaviour Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./media/images/Transformers - Dark of the Moon - Autobots (USA).jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game id="6589" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Transformers - War for Cybertron - Autobots (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Transformers - War for Cybertron - Autobots</name>
		<desc>Taking place on the Transformers home planet of Cybertron, Transformers: The War for Cybertron tells the story of the Transformers long before they came in contact with Earth, an event that had been previously explored in the games based on the 2007 and 2009 movies. In Transformers: War for Cybertron - Autobots players can play their favorite Decepticon characters and fight as the ultimate weapon, transforming at any time between vehicle and robot and hitting enemies with futuristic firepower. 
 
Like the console version there are linear campaign of missions, following basically the same story. There is an Arena mode with five "arenas", each with six missions available, four bonus levels from the opposing game, and seven multiplayer levels. 
 
There are two DS versions of the game, this and the Decepticons version. To unlock all 30 total playable Transformers, including 11 DS-exclusives, players need to defeat friends in head-to-head multi-player to win their characters.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20100622T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vicarious Vision</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<image>./media/images/Transformers - War for Cybertron - Autobots (USA).jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game id="5918" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Yoshi's Island DS (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Yoshi Island DS</name>
		<desc>After failing to kidnap the Mario Bros. in the original Yoshi's Island, Kamek the Magikoopa has decided to set his sights higher.  Instead of just kidnapping the famous brothers, he's sent an army of his toadies out to kidnap children across the world!  Luckily, Mario avoids escape, and again lands in the hands of the Yoshis.  It's up to the Yoshis to carry Mario across Yoshi's Island and rescue Luigi and the other babies.

Yoshi's Island DS is a sequel to the SNES game, Yoshi's Island.  In it, players control Yoshi as he travels to Kamek's castle to rescue Luigi.  Yoshi can carry Baby Mario, Peach, DK, Wario or Bowser on his back - depending on the baby carried, Yoshi will gain a special ability; for example, Mario lets Yoshi dash, Peach allows Yoshi to float for a longer period of time, and Wario whips out a gigantic magnet to attract coins and other metallic objects.  If Yoshi is hit by an enemy, a counter appears, and begins to slowly count down to zero.  If it reaches zero, the baby is kidnapped, and Yoshi loses a life.  Yoshi can increase his counter by collecting stars that are rewards for some puzzles and defeating certain enemies.

Another feature of Yoshi's Island DS is the ability to hurl eggs to defeat foes.  Yoshi can eat nearly every enemy - if you press down on the control pad when Yoshi is holding an enemy in his mouth, he will turn it into an egg.  Yoshi can hurl his eggs at enemies and objects such as certain walls to destroy them.  You can even pick up coins and other collectibles by throwing an egg at them.  Finally, Yoshi can ricochet eggs off walls to hit things that he would otherwise be unable to reach.

While the object of each level is to simply reach the end, avid gamers will aim to get 100% for each level.  To do this, they must reach the end of each level with thirty stars, find the twenty red coins hidden amongst the regular ones, and collect the five flowers in each level.  One special  "Character Coin" is also hidden in each level - these have a picture of a particular baby on them, and can only be collected when Yoshi has that baby on his back.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20061113T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Artoon</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Yoshi's Island DS (USA).jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game id="6187" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles 3 - Mutant Nightmare (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles 3 - Mutant Nightmare</name>
		<desc>Join the TMNT in their latest set of adventures. Whether they are battling the Foot Ninjas on the streets of NYC or infiltrating the Triceraton base they are always looking for action - or perhaps action is looking for them? Play as your favorite Turtle through the TMNT universe alone or grab some friends for some 4 player intense action! Over 50 action packed stages. Strategically use skills of all 4 Turtles to clear traps and obstacles. 4 player wireless and touch panel controls.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>20051208T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles 3 - Mutant Nightmare (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="6374" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles - Arcade Attack (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles - Arcade Attack</name>
		<desc>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Arcade Attack is a modern take on the original Turtles arcade game. Unlike Konami's Turtle beat 'em ups, Arcade Attack is in fact 3D while attempting to play as though it were 2D but with a slightly isometric camera angle. The game can be played alone with a CPU ally or with a friend wirelessly with a selection of the four turtles, each with their own varying stats. Also much like Smash Up, while the game tries to blend both the new and the old TMNT universe all into one it leans a lot more heavily toward the new with its visual style and enemy selection.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles - Arcade Attack (USA).jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20091126T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>4kids entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="5741" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Call of Duty - Modern Warfare 3 - Defiance (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Call of Duty - Modern Warfare 3 - Defiance</name>
		<desc>Call of Duty: Modern Warfare 3 is the 2011 release in the best-selling Call of Duty First-Person Shooter action series. The game is a direct sequel to the previous game in the series, Call of Duty: Modern Warfare 2, with a campaign storyline continuing the struggle of U.S. forces against an invasion by the Russian Federation following the framing of an undercover U.S. agent in a terrorist attack on Moscow. Along with classic Call of Duty multi-character control, Call of Duty: Modern Warfare 3 contains deep multiplayer support, including two-player Co-op Survival mode. The game also contains all-new Kill Streak categories and customizable strike packages that offer more options for player combat styles and strategies.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Call of Duty - Modern Warfare 3 - Defiance (USA).jpg</image>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20111108T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>n-Space</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>6</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="6395" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Bomberman Story DS (Europe).zip</path>
		<name>Bomberman Story Ds</name>
		<desc>This game plays like traditional Bomberman games except with an experience system. The player must navigate the map on each planet to locate the dungeon and then the boss. Along the way they must defeat enemies and destroy soft blocks with bombs. Every time an enemy is defeated it will display the experience that was earned by the player. After enough experience is obtained, they will level up and gain a new skill like increased number of bombs or fire power.

There are also various types of bombs that can be obtained that have different functions. They are kept in a specific quantity and more can be found from inside soft blocks or defeated monsters.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Bomberman Story DS (Europe).jpg</image>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20071123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rising Star Games</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
	<game id="6418" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Asphalt - Urban GT (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Asphalt : Urban GT</name>
		<desc>Asphalt Urban GT combines the virtues of both simulation and arcade racing for the Nintendo DS. You'll hit the streets in a variety of licensed high-performance cars on tracks all over the world. Winning races, collecting prize money, and then purchasing new cars and modifying current ones are keys to success. The game also features three different multiplayer modes that let you race against three other players.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Asphalt - Urban GT (USA).jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050311T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gameloft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="6328" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Ben 10 - Protector of Earth (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Ben 10 : Protector of Earth</name>
		<desc>Players will take on the role of Cartoon Network's popular everyday-kid-turned-alien-hero, Ben Tennyson. Using the power of the Omnitrix which has embedded itself on Ben's wrist, players will be able to battle as one of five popular alien heroes from the show. By taking on these amazing powers, players can battle to save the world through the game's diverse challenges, puzzles and skirmishes.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Ben 10 - Protector of Earth (USA).jpg</image>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20071030T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>1st Playable Productions</developer>
		<publisher>D3 Publisher</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Beat'em Up</genre>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="6334" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Captain America - Super Soldier (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Captain America - Super Soldier</name>
		<desc>Captain America: Super Soldier combines a highly athletic combat system with fluid platforming and a highly tuned suite of shield attacks, as Cap explores a massive castle turned military installation. His shield can be employed in numerous ways: taking out multiple enemies at once, deflecting incoming fire back at enemies, solving puzzles, and scaling walls. Players will be able to launch shield-first into the fray with the superior force of the world's first Super-Soldier at their fingertips and they'll need every bit of that strength to overcome a castle that's both an acrobatic playground for the Captain's physical prowess and a house of mystery with enemies and danger at every turn.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Captain America - Super Soldier (USA).jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20110719T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>Griptonite Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="5825" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Castlevania - Portrait of Ruin (EUR).zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania - Portrait Of Ruin</name>
		<desc>Take control of two heroes, Jonathan Morris, a vampire killer and his close friend Charlotte Orlean, a girl with tremendous magical ability. Amidst the chaos of World War II, two mysterious sisters emerge, working to resurrect Dracula and David and Charlotte are all that stand in their way.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Castlevania - Portrait of Ruin (EUR).jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20061205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game id="5778" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mario Kart DS (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Mario Kart Ds</name>
		<desc>Mario Kart DS is the continuation of the long running racing game series that began on the Super Nintendo. It features 16 new tracks as well as 16 tracks from the previous 4 games, with each set split up into the Nitro and Retro Grand Prix respectively. Eight racers are initially available, each with two go-karts to choose from. A number of characters and additional karts are also available to unlock. New items have been added to the arsenal, including a Blooper squid that squirts ink onto the screens of other players and a Bullet Bill power up that transforms the player into a giant, fast-travelling bullet on autopilot.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Mario Kart DS (USA).jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20051114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="5795" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Grand Theft Auto - Chinatown Wars (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Grand Theft Auto - Chinatown Wars</name>
		<desc>Grand Theft Auto: Chinatown Wars is an entirely original entry into the critically acclaimed Grand Theft Auto series, and brings a new level of interactivity to its sprawling open environments. With the use of the DS touch screen, players navigate their way through the streets as they uncover the truth behind an epic tale of crime and corruption within the Triad crime syndicate, delivering the unprecedented amount of depth that has become a true trademark of the franchise.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Grand Theft Auto - Chinatown Wars (USA).jpg</image>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20090317T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rockstar Leeds</developer>
		<publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter-Race, Driving-Fight</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="5934" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Kirby Super Stars Ultra (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Kirby - Super Star Ultra</name>
		<desc>Kirby's back with a bunch of fun adventures!  Explore Dream Land and defeat King Dedede, tame the ferocious Dynablade, explore a huge cave, take part in a gluttonous race, vandalize Meta Knight's ship, the Halberd, explore the entire galaxy, and more!
Kirby Super Star Ultra is an updated remake of Kirby Super Star, a popular SNES game which is broken up into seven main games.  In addition to those previous games, Ultra includes five new games and three new sub-games.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Kirby Super Star Ultra (USA).jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20080922T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Platform</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="86129" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Lara Croft Tomb Raider - Legend (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Lara Croft Tomb Raider - Legend</name>
		<desc>Tomb Raider: Legend revives the athletic, intelligent and entertaining adventurer who won the hearts and minds of gamers worldwide. Lara comes alive with intricately animated expressions, moves and abilities. An arsenal of modern equipment, such as a magnetic grappling device, binoculars, frag grenades, personal lighting device and communications equipment, allows gamers to experience tomb raiding as never before.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Lara Croft Tomb Raider - Legend (USA).jpg</image>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Human Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="5882" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mario Party DS (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Mario Party DS</name>
		<desc>He's captured Mario and his friends in his pursuit of a crystal that the group collected when it fell from the sky, and he doesn't hesitate to shrink them to miniature size to get rid of them and get his hands on the other four crystals. The mini-heroes have to find the crystals before he does, making their way through giant environments filled with enormous creatures. The single-player campaign takes place in five different settings, each of them ending with a boss. As usual, players have to collect coins and stars, at the same time escaping dangers such as Piranha Plants and other classic creatures from the Mario universe.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Mario Party DS (USA).jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20071119T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Board game-Strategy-Various</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="5809" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Castlevania - Dawn of Sorrow (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania: Dawn of Sorrow</name>
		<desc>The team that developed Castlevania: Aria of Sorrow returns to bring the sequel, CastleVania: Dawn of Sorrow, to the Nintendo DS. This time, you must infiltrate a castle belonging to a cult that is planning to resurrect Lord Dracula. Castlevania: Dawn of Sorrow lets you defeat evil spirits using the "Magic Seal" system which utilizes the Nintendo DS touch screen. You can trade captured souls with other players using the wireless system as well.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Castlevania - Dawn of Sorrow (USA).jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20051004T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="85411" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Crash - Mind over Mutant (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Crash: Mind Over Mutant</name>
		<desc>In Crash Bandicoot: Mind Over Mutant, a rejuvenated Neo Cortex is taking over the world one brain at a time! Cortex and N. Brio devise a new kind of evil: a text-messaging, do-anything device that controls both mutant and bandicoot minds. Armed with his quick wits and lightning agility, Crash must free his friends, the titans, and save the day!</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Crash - Mind over Mutant (USA).jpg</image>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="6607" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Crash Boom Bang! (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Crash Boom Bang !</name>
		<desc>Roll the dice and dive into one of the 40 multiplayer action-oriented mini-games, where you can communicate with other players through the revolutionary DS Touch Panel Communication.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Crash Boom Bang! (USA).jpg</image>
		<rating>0.35</rating>
		<releasedate>20061027T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dimps</developer>
		<publisher>Universal</publisher>
		<genre>Casual Game</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="6108" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Diddy Kong Racing DS (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Diddy Kong Racing Ds</name>
		<desc>When Tiger Island is taken over by the evil Wizpig, Timber sends a letter to Diddy to request his assistance.  Diddy, Dixie, Tiny Kong and the rogue Kremling Krunch turn up to help Timber and his friends, Bumper, Tiptup and Pipsy.

Diddy Kong Racing DS is remake of the Nintendo 64 game of the same name.  However, while the story and setting remains the same, this is more of an upgrade instead of a port.  Players can still race around assorted tracks around Tiger Island via kart, hovercraft or plane, winning races to earn golden balloons to progress and defeating bosses to confront Wizpig.

There have been subtle tweaks to the gameplay.  While you can still level up your balloons by collecting another of the same colored balloon in a row, collecting a different colored balloon will not change your weapon - you'll have to fire your current weapon first.  The Silver Coin Challenge from the original game has been removed from the main adventure, and is replaced with a first-person touch screen shooter where you fly around on Taj's magic carpet and aim to pop as many balloons as you can.  There's also an optional racing mode where you race by using the stylus to guide the vehicle through a top-down map.

The game now supports currency system for most unlockables - dotted along the track are coins, which can be used to buy 'wishes' from Taj the Genie.  These include anything from new characters, exclusive tracks, a custom track editor, battle modes to unlock in multiplayer and so forth.  The DS version of Diddy Kong Racing also heavily supports multiplayer.  You can play with one game card or multiple game cards (to a maximum of eight players), or online to a maximum of six players.  Similar to Mario Kart DS, you can design your own custom decal and have it as your visual representation for when you race around the world.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Diddy Kong Racing DS (USA).jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20070420T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving-Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="6201" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Bomberman Land Touch! 2 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Bomberman Land Touch ! 2</name>
		<desc>BOMBERMAN LAND Touch! 2 is the follow up sequel to IGN's Best Online Multiplayer 2006 Game of the Year on the Nintendo DS. Embark on a fun-filled, theme park adventure as you discover a huge land to explore, a gigantic multiplayer pack, and a host of addicting mini-games that can be played by yourself or with up to 4 people.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Bomberman Land Touch! 2 (USA).jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20080129T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rising Star Games</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Casual Game</genre>
		<players>8</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="5817" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Castlevania - Order of Ecclesia (EUR).zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania - Order of Ecclesia</name>
		<desc>Set in the early 19th century, this installment of the long running Castlevania series takes a slight departure from the typical series storyline. A secret monastic organization, Order of Ecclesia, is charged with finding alternative ways of combating the hordes of undead summoned by the ever-returning evil lord Dracula, as the Belmont clan has apparently gone into hiding. Shanoa, a young acolyte of the Order, is chosen for her extraordinary magical abilities to wield Dominus: the ultimate spell against evil. As she is about to complete the ritual to absorb Dominus a rogue acolyte named Albus steals the three tomes containing the spell. Shanoa is then dispatched to track down Albus and return him and the spell back to the Order.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Castlevania - Order of Ecclesia (EUR).jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20081021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
</gameList>
