<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Digimon Tamers - Battle Spirit (Japan) (En,Ja).zip</path>
		<name>Battle Spirit - Digimon Frontier</name>
		<desc>The plot of Digimon Battle Spirit 2 echoes that of its source series, Digimon Frontier; several children receive messages on their cell phones asking them if they want their lives to change. Some answer yes, some answer no, and five who answer yes are summoned to the Digital World where they receive the ability to become Digimon and fight to end Kerpymon's reign of terror.</desc>
		<image>./images/Digimon Tamers - Battle Spirit (Japan) (En,Ja)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Digimon Tamers - Battle Spirit (Japan) (En,Ja)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Digimon Tamers - Battle Spirit (Japan) (En,Ja)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Digimon Tamers - Battle Spirit (Japan) (En,Ja)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20021207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dimps</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Guilty Gear Petit (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Guilty Gear Petit</name>
		<desc>The game takes place in 22th century. Scientists developed a new technique that allowed them to merge the DNA of humans and animals, producing powerful creatures known as "gears". The characters of the game participate in a tournament, the winner of which would face a gear who went out of control and is threatening to lead a gear rebellion against the humans. The game allows you to play as familiar characters from Guilty Gear series, such as the main hero Sol Badguy, who has a certain connection to the gears, and his rival, the leader of the Holy Knights named Ky Kiske. It also introduces a new character, the nurse Fanny, who fights with a syringe and has a mysterious connection to the genius surgeon, and later serial murderer, Dr. Baldhead. 

"Guilty Gear Petit" is a 2D fighting game. The story mode lets you pick a character and take him/her through a series of fights, while in time attack mode you can choose your opponents freely. The graphics are done in "super-deformed" style. The game retains key ingredients of Guilty Gear gameplay, such as building tension in order to execute powerful attacks, combo moves, etc.</desc>
		<image>./images/Guilty Gear Petit (Japan)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Guilty Gear Petit (Japan)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Guilty Gear Petit (Japan)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Guilty Gear Petit (Japan)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20010125T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Arc System Works</developer>
		<genre>Luta</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Judgement Silversword - Rebirth Edition (Japan) (Rev 4321).zip</path>
		<name>Judgement Silversword - Rebirth Edition</name>
		<desc>In your space fighter, the S-AIXAK, you'll be going up against the minions of the Judgement Silversword. Starting from a small space station above the earth your lone fighter will travail the bullet filled cosmos, always a shot away from death, to achieve this goal.

Judgement Silversword is a vertically scrolling shooter in which wave upon wave of multifarious of opposing craft will try to take you down with bullets, bombs, lasers, or even their own fuselages. Using the Y-Buttons as a directional pad and the X-Buttons for your weaponry you'll try your hand at completing the S-AIXAKs destiny.

You'll have three weapons at your disposal, spread cannon, concentrated cannon, and your energy shield. The spread cannon will fire an arch of bullet out before you, while a concentrated will fire only directly before you. Your energy shield can be used to absorb incoming shot, however, your back and sides will remain vulnerable. The shield can also be used to damage enemies by ramming them with it. As you use it the shield will run out of energy and need to be recharged. 

The game has thirty different areas each comprised of about ten sub areas. Scores are awarded based on kill ratio and completion time. New modes and easter eggs will be unlocked as you obtain higher scores.</desc>
		<image>./images/Judgement Silversword - Rebirth Edition (Japan) (Rev 4321)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Judgement Silversword - Rebirth Edition (Japan) (Rev 4321)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Judgement Silversword - Rebirth Edition (Japan) (Rev 4321)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Judgement Silversword - Rebirth Edition (Japan) (Rev 4321)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20040205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>M-KAI</developer>
		<publisher>Qute</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Raku Jongg (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Raku Jongg</name>
		<desc>Imagine Puyo Puyo or Panic Bomber, but with Mahjong tiles instead.</desc>
		<image>./images/Raku Jongg (Japan)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Raku Jongg (Japan)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Raku Jongg (Japan)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Raku Jongg (Japan)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20010531T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Enterbrain, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<genre>Quebra-cabeças / Queda</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./XI Little (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>XI -sai- Little</name>
		<desc>"Roll the dice game will be off the edge. I know that someone you know is a famous game. Chain can not be perplexed in the beginning, when man used to enjoy! Highly addictive puzzle. I </desc>
		<image>./images/XI Little (Japan)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/XI Little (Japan)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/XI Little (Japan)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/XI Little (Japan)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20011220T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>MBI Limited</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Quebra-cabeças</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kidou Senshi Gundam Seed (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Kidou Senshi Gundam Seed</name>
		<desc>Kidou Senshi Gundam Seed is an action game with 8 stages. The player controls the Strike Gundam, while trying to destroy Gin and Shigu of Zaft's mobile suits and enemy Gundam on the stages of colonies, outer space and desert!

Strike Gundam can be modified with optional parts according to the situation, so consider the characteristics of each equipment, such as focusing on mobility with an ale striker pack, close combat with a sword striker pack or firepower with a launcher striker pack.

After clearing the game with Strike Gundam, you can play the side stories of Aegis Gundam, Duel Gundam, Blitz Gundam, Buster Gundam, and the new Freedom Gundam.</desc>
		<image>./images/Kidou Senshi Gundam Seed (Japan)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Kidou Senshi Gundam Seed (Japan)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Kidou Senshi Gundam Seed (Japan)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Kidou Senshi Gundam Seed (Japan)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20030315T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ultraman - Hikari no Kuni no Shisha (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Ultraman - Hikari no Kuni no Shisha</name>
		<desc>Sinister aliens and giant monsters are constantly threatening civilization. The only Earth organization equipped to handle these disasters is the Science Special Search Party (SSSP), a special police force with br</desc>
		<image>./images/Ultraman - Hikari no Kuni no Shisha (Japan)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Ultraman - Hikari no Kuni no Shisha (Japan)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Ultraman - Hikari no Kuni no Shisha (Japan)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Ultraman - Hikari no Kuni no Shisha (Japan)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20010621T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<genre>Luta / 2D</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kurupara! (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Kurupara!</name>
		<desc>Kurupara! is a puzzle game, in which panels arranged in a 5x5 field are rearranged and erased. To turn off the panel, you must first arrange three or more of the same pattern. Then, when three panels are arranged, the pattern drawn on the surface disappears and the panel is turned over. And if you put three or more panels that are turned over again, the pattern on the back will disappear and the panel will disappear. Repeat this and all the panels disappear to clear the stage.

</desc>
		<image>./images/Kurupara! (Japan)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Kurupara! (Japan)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Kurupara! (Japan)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Kurupara! (Japan)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20010614T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tomcreate</developer>
		<publisher>Tomcreate</publisher>
		<genre>Quebra-cabeças</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kinnikuman IIsei - Dream Tag Match (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Kinnikuman IIsei - Dream Tag Match</name>
		<desc>Kinnikuman Nisei: Dream Tag Match is a wrestling game based in the manga/anime series of the same name. It features the cast of Kinnikuman Nisei (known in the West as "Kinnikuman: Second Generations") in a battle to victory. The main story follows Kid Muscle, the prince of Muscle Planet and son of King Muscle (the early protagonist of the series), who fought for peace and justice in the Universe. Kid has now been chosen as King Muscle's predecessor in wrestling history, and must now defeat every opponent that comes his way, stopping total domination by the Demon Manufacturing Plant, an evil wrestling league which wants to take control of the universe, and the loss of his fanbase, which includes the love of his life, Roxanne.

</desc>
		<image>./images/Kinnikuman IIsei - Dream Tag Match (Japan)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Kinnikuman IIsei - Dream Tag Match (Japan)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Kinnikuman IIsei - Dream Tag Match (Japan)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Kinnikuman IIsei - Dream Tag Match (Japan)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20020302T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<genre>Esporte</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tetris (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Tetris</name>
		<desc> Geometric shapes fall from the top of a playfield to rest on the bottom; fit the pieces together, and the line they form disappears. If the pieces don't form lin</desc>
		<image>./images/Tetris (Japan)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Tetris (Japan)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Tetris (Japan)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Tetris (Japan)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20020418T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Elorg</developer>
		<publisher>Vanguard Works</publisher>
		<genre>Quebra-cabeças</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Front Mission (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Front Mission</name>
		<desc>In the future, many military forces are dependent on huge mech robots, called Wanzers (Walking Panzers) for combat. At Huffman Island, located in the the pacific ocean, wanzers are deployed by both the USN (United States of the New Continent) and the OCU (Oceana Community Union), who dispute ownership over the island.  One night, the OCU forces stage a covert recon mission on a facility located in Larcus, a USN-held territory and weapons facility. Lead by a soldier named Roid, this mission was entirely unofficial and violated the peace treaty. During the mission, USN forces lead by Commander Driscoll appeared and ambushed the OCU soldiers. During the combat, Roid's fiance, Karen is killed and the USN facility is blown up; placing the blame on the OCU. This became known as the &amp;quot;Larcus Incident&amp;quot; and the OCU denied all knowledge of it's soldiers actions. Ultimately it would be a leading cause to the second Huffman War. 

One year later, the war is underway and Huffman island is under provisional control of the OCU, but with a weakened military unable to defend against USN attacks. The soldiers involved involved in the Larcus Incident have all been discharged and disgraced. Roid spends his time fighting as a gladiator in the Wanzer fighting arena before being approached by a mysterious man. Colonel Olson has found out about Roid's history and wants him to command a mercenary unit he is assembling on behalf of the OCU, dubbed &amp;quot;Carrion Crow&amp;quot;. Convincing Roid that Driscoll is still out there on the island, Roid agrees.

Front Mission is a turn-based strategy RPG played from an isometric perspective. Players progress in the story through large strategic battles involving multiple units and cutscenes between them. At certain places, usually towns, the player can visit multiple locations including bars and shops, and talk to people. Shops are also found to purchase new weaponry, parts and make repairs. In combat, each Wanzer robot is a seperate unit and, has a large variety of weapons and attack styles depending on what's equipped. Units get experience for defeating enemies and also for using various techniques. The more an attack is used, the more powerful it becomes.</desc>
		<image>./images/Front Mission (Japan)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Front Mission (Japan)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Front Mission (Japan)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Front Mission (Japan)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20020712T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>G-Craft</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./From TV Animation One Piece - Grand Battle Swan Colosseum (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>From TV Animation One Piece - Grand Battle Swan Co</name>
		<desc> A real high point in the WonderSwan One Piece series </desc>
		<image>./images/From TV Animation One Piece - Grand Battle Swan Colosseum (Japan)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/From TV Animation One Piece - Grand Battle Swan Colosseum (Japan)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/From TV Animation One Piece - Grand Battle Swan Colosseum (Japan)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/From TV Animation One Piece - Grand Battle Swan Colosseum (Japan)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20020712T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<genre>Luta</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Flash Koibito-kun (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Flash Koibito-kun</name>
		<desc>Flash Koibito-Kun is a Puzzle game, developed by Koto and published by Koubunsha, which was released in Japan in 2000.</desc>
		<image>./images/Flash Koibito-kun (Japan)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Flash Koibito-kun (Japan)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Flash Koibito-kun (Japan)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Flash Koibito-kun (Japan)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20001228T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Koto Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Kobunsha</publisher>
		<genre>Jogos de RPG</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rhyme Rider Kerorican (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Rhyme Rider Kerorican</name>
		<desc>You play as the rhyme rider Kerorcian, a vivacious space girl with a large frog helmet, as she skips to the music through the games four stages. The games music is largely comprised of jazzy techno pieces.

Kerorcian skips down a set line while randomly placed enemies and obstacles appear before her. Various button combos will avoid certain obstacles, although a "one-button" easy mode is available. When you avoid an obstacle a note will sound, clearing long chains of obstacles will result in funky melodies popping up inside the song that is playing. This gameplay is reminiscent of the studios earlier game Vib Ribbon.  

Some of the obstacles are interactive, such as a rocket one can jump on and ride a short distance, others can merely be kicked out of the way or jumped over.

Occasionally a crown will appear over an obstacle, if you successfully clear it you will briefly soar over the stage avoiding anything that might have been in your path. This is especially common before obstacles that might require outlandish button combos.</desc>
		<image>./images/Rhyme Rider Kerorican (Japan)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Rhyme Rider Kerorican (Japan)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Rhyme Rider Kerorican (Japan)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Rhyme Rider Kerorican (Japan)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20001209T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NanaOn-Sha Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<genre>Estratégia</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./GunPey EX (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>GunPey EX</name>
		<desc>Sequela direta do Gunpey original no WonderSwan, o Gunpey EX adiciona vários novos elementos ao clássico; mais notavelmente, cor.

Além de ganhar pontos por completar uma linha em todo o campo, você ganhará pontos se essas linhas forem de uma cor correspondente. Anteriormente, apenas linhas cinzentas eram possíveis, e agora aparecem linhas vermelhas, azuis e verdes.

Gunpey EX tem os mesmos modos do jogo anterior, exceto um modo de história. Modo Time Attack, onde é preciso eliminar o maior número possível de peças em dois de cinco minutos. Modo infinito dá ao jogador tempo ilimitado para produzir qualquer pontuação que deseje. O modo de palco apresenta um número definido de peças a serem removidas em um determinado momento. O modo de quebra-cabeça coloca o jogador na situação de ter que remover um certo grupo de peças, o jogador pode mudar a cor das linhas aqui quando elas trocarem suas posições de peças.
</desc>
		<image>./images/GunPey EX (Japan)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/GunPey EX (Japan)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/GunPey EX (Japan)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/GunPey EX (Japan)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>20001209T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Koto Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<genre>Simulação</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Blue Wing Blitz (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Blue Wing Blitz</name>
		<desc>There are six nations living in the world of floating islands. The most powerful one is the Ordia Empire, possessing the best aircrafts in the world. But its leaders were hungry for even more power, and planned to invade and to occupy the other five nations. The other nations tried to maintain diplomatic relationship with the Empire as long as possible. But one of those countries, the Esk Republic, decided to send a special strike team of skillful pilots, attempting to initiate a secret rebellion against the Empire. A young pilot named Keid, guided by his senior partner, the girl Payer, is the one who was chosen for this mission.

"Blue Wing Blitz" is a turn-based strategy RPG with a twist: instead of fighters or soldier units, you command aircrafts. You navigate your planes over a battle field, which consists of airspaces, in round-based fashion. Once you land on a space occupied by an enemy plane, a battle follows. During those battles you have control over your aircraft, performing various attacks or defending. After several turns, the battle stops, but will resume if the enemy planes are still standing on the same space.</desc>
		<image>./images/Blue Wing Blitz (Japan)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Blue Wing Blitz (Japan)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Blue Wing Blitz (Japan)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Blue Wing Blitz (Japan)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20010705T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Jogos de RPG</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wonder Classic (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Namco Wonder Classic</name>
		<desc>Wonder Classic is a golfing game developed by Yoshidayama-Workshop and published by Bandai in january 2011 for the WonderSwan Color.
You will use different characters with specific abilities to your advantage. For example the character, Reiko Nagase nullifies the effects of wind, most others have certain benefits to certain types of shot. There are two starting characters and twenty-two unlockable and downloadable characters.</desc>
		<image>./images/Wonder Classic (Japan)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Wonder Classic (Japan)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Wonder Classic (Japan)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Wonder Classic (Japan)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20010118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Yoshidayama-Workshop</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<genre>Quebra-cabeças</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Makai Toushi Sa-Ga (Japan) (T).zip</path>
		<name>Makai Toushi Sa-Ga</name>
		<desc>This remake of SaGa features several changes compared to the original. The graphics have been updated to 16-bit level, with new sprites and artwork drawn by Toshiyuki Itahana. New animated sequences have been added to the game as well as an intro sequence. Other new features include the ability to see what a monster would change to if they eat a new meat ahead of time, a bestiary, and the ability to re-target enemies when a previous target is slain by another character. There's even an option to play a straight port of the original Game Boy version as well.</desc>
		<image>./images/Makai Toushi Sa-Ga (Japan) (T)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Makai Toushi Sa-Ga (Japan) (T)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Makai Toushi Sa-Ga (Japan) (T)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Makai Toushi Sa-Ga (Japan) (T)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20020320T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Jogos de RPG</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Lap Special - GT &amp; Formula Machine (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Final Lap Special - GT &amp; Formula Machine</name>
		<desc> For each mode, GT and Formula, you can only race as those cars in its respective tournaments whi</desc>
		<image>./images/Final Lap Special - GT &amp; Formula Machine (Japan)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Final Lap Special - GT &amp; Formula Machine (Japan)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Final Lap Special - GT &amp; Formula Machine (Japan)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Final Lap Special - GT &amp; Formula Machine (Japan)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20011115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<genre>Corrida, Pilotagem</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sorobang (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Soroban Gu</name>
		<desc>This is an action puzzle game, in which blocks appearing one after another are aligned and erased. However, the top, bottom, left, and right of the screen loop in this game. As a result, the blocks will be connected unexpectedly.nnnnThe battle mode, which is a classic action puzzle, is also supported. In this mode there are three levels of difficulty, so you can play with friends of different skill levels.</desc>
		<image>./images/Sorobang (Japan)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Sorobang (Japan)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Sorobang (Japan)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Sorobang (Japan)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20000912T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mechanic Arms</developer>
		<publisher>Naxat Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Quebra-cabeças</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rockman EXE WS (Japan) (T).zip</path>
		<name>Rockman EXE WS</name>
		<desc>Rockman EXE WS is a spin-off loosely based on Mega Man Battle Network's anime adaption. The game attempts to blend traditional platforming with Battle Network's chip collection.</desc>
		<image>./images/Rockman EXE WS (Japan) (T)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Rockman EXE WS (Japan) (T)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Rockman EXE WS (Japan) (T)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Rockman EXE WS (Japan) (T)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20030208T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Plataforma</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Guilty Gear Petit 2 (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Guilty Gear Petit 2</name>
		<desc>In 22th century, scientists found a way to create artificial beings whom they called "gears". These gears were very powerful, but did not have wills of their own, and were completely obedient to the humans. However, a gear named Justice was able to free himself from the control and led a rebellion against the humans. Since then, the humanity lived in fear that the gears will one day gain the power on the Earth. For that purpose, the Sacred Order of the Holy Knights organized fighting tournaments to find out who is strong enough to face the renegade gears.

"Guilty Gear Petit 2" is very similar to its  predecessor, having the same "super-deformed" graphical style, battle moves (including the tension system to accumulate power and combo attacks), as well as backgrounds for battles. Several new characters appear in "Guilty Gear Petit 2", such as Zato-1, the former head of the assassin guild, the pirate captain Johnny, the time traveler Axl Lou from the 20th century, the mysterious Faust, and others.</desc>
		<image>./images/Guilty Gear Petit 2 (Japan)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Guilty Gear Petit 2 (Japan)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Guilty Gear Petit 2 (Japan)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Guilty Gear Petit 2 (Japan)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20010927T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Arc System Works</developer>
		<genre>Luta</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Digimon - Anode Tamer &amp; Cathode Tamer (Asia).zip</path>
		<name>Digimon Anode &amp; Cathode Tamer</name>
		<desc>This release contains the first  Digimon Adventure, both  Anode Tamer and  Cathode Tamer versions. The game is based on the manga and animé series Digimon. You play as an ordinary Japanese boy named Ryou who gets sucked into the mysterious digital world and has to help the digital monster Agumon and his friends to recruit digital monsters and send them into battles against evil ones.
</desc>
		<image>./images/Digimon - Anode Tamer &amp; Cathode Tamer (Asia)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Digimon - Anode Tamer &amp; Cathode Tamer (Asia)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Digimon - Anode Tamer &amp; Cathode Tamer (Asia)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Digimon - Anode Tamer &amp; Cathode Tamer (Asia)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<developer>Bandai</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<genre>Jogos de RPG</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mr. Driller (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Mr. Driller</name>
		<desc>Mr Driller's world has been covered with mysterious blocks. Armed with only a mighty drill, you'll have to dig your way down to safety before his air supply runs out!

Mr Driller is a real-time puzzle game that relies solely on quick-thinking and a bit of planning.  Gameplay is a combination of Tetris and Boulder Dash: You have to drill down through multi-colored blocks to reach the bottom while avoiding the consequences of reckless drilling (blocks may fall on you and crush you).</desc>
		<image>./images/Mr. Driller (Japan)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Mr. Driller (Japan)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Mr. Driller (Japan)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Mr. Driller (Japan)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20010405T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Quebra-cabeças</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SD Gundam - Operation U.C. (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>SD Gundam - Operation U.C.</name>
		<desc>Quando você começar a jogar o jogo e chegar ao menu principal, você terá algumas coisas que você pode escolher.</desc>
		<image>./images/SD Gundam - Operation U.C. (Japan)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/SD Gundam - Operation U.C. (Japan)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/SD Gundam - Operation U.C. (Japan)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/SD Gundam - Operation U.C. (Japan)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20020216T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<genre>Tiro / Vertical</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kinnikuman IIsei - Choujin Seisenshi (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Kinnikuman IIsei - Choujin Seisenshi</name>
		<desc>Kinnikuman Nisei: Ch?jin Seisenshi is an RPG game based in the Kinnikuman/Ultimate Muscle series, although the plot of the game bears no relation to any of the original series' sagas. Here you will take the role of an anonymous guy -created specially for this game- named "The Mask" (although you can change his name for one of your choice) and will have to defeat all the characters of the Kinnikuman universe that appear in your way.

</desc>
		<image>./images/Kinnikuman IIsei - Choujin Seisenshi (Japan)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Kinnikuman IIsei - Choujin Seisenshi (Japan)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Kinnikuman IIsei - Choujin Seisenshi (Japan)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Kinnikuman IIsei - Choujin Seisenshi (Japan)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20030130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<genre>Jogos de RPG</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dicing Knight (Japan) (T).zip</path>
		<name>Dicing Knight.</name>
		<desc>Dicing Knight. follows the journey of a nameless knight fighting through a series of randomly generated dungeons.  The game will start on the floor of a dungeon, your goal being to find the floors key to progress to the next floor. Eventually you will reach a dungeon boss, after you beat it you’ll be allowed access to a new more difficult dungeon. Dungeons are timed by a “Food Gauge” which when depleted will force you to exit the dungeon.

The dungeons are named:

1. Lindwurm - German term for dragon, meant to establish the mythic setting. This dungeon has a heavenly aura.
2. Shootingstar - A fiery land that will start to test your knowledge of the controls from Lindwurm.
3. Jabberwock - A whimsical land that is bathed in night. When the night shall end is unknown.
4. Quetzalcoatl - The area named for the Aztec sky god and creator. The entire map can no longer be seen.
5. Jörmungandr - The serpent that shall kill Thor. This stage is a mythic earthy setting.

The A button swings your sword and the B rings up your shield, the key items of any knight. Slashing your foes with your sword and devouring projectiles with your shield will increase your special meter, which when filled will allow you to perform a deadly special attack “Shining Sword” or "Blazing Sword".

One interesting features of Dicing Knight is the “dicing” every time you attack an enemy dice will pop out of it and roll, you’ll deal damage to the foe based on the rolls you get. Likewise when you are hit dice also roll to determine you’re damaged. 

The Y buttons will be mapped to four different items, which can be found inside your foes. A variety of items are included in the game such as an item that will predict or alter dice rolls, a variety of stat altering potions, invincibility items,  and a drill that will let you progress through dungeon wall to avoid monster filled rooms. Various orbs are also obtainable, via a lottery system, which will improve your abilities. 

After you beat the game on “Knight Mode” you’ll obtain a, “Fortuner Mode”, which will alter the game play, keeping the dungeon crawling style but giving you the ability to shoot to you and more of the monsters. The A button will be transformed into a double pistol, and the B will lob grenades. As well as two new specials that allow you to absorb enemy bullets or do a powerful shock attack. A new stage with a fitting title will also appear:

1. Ouroboros - The snake eating its own tail, an alchemical symbol of immortality, this dungeon rests betwixt time, eternal, and waiting.</desc>
		<image>./images/Dicing Knight (Japan) (T)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Dicing Knight (Japan) (T)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Dicing Knight (Japan) (T)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Dicing Knight (Japan) (T)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20040531T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Platine Dispositif</developer>
		<publisher>Qute</publisher>
		<genre>Jogos de RPG</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./RUN=DIM - Return to Earth (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>RUN=DIM - Return to Earth</name>
		<desc>In the early 21st century, due to the global warming that has accelerated since the end of the previous century, several tens of percent of the earth's land was submerged. Many big cities were submerged in the sea, and the global economy was devastated.

The year is 2052. The world has established a new order centered on the two major camps, the Space Development Organization ?Jesus? and the International Civil Organization ?Green Frontier?. The two major organizations that were born as a result of repeated mergers by large corporations around the world will eventually become more tense over space development initiatives. And, with the surprise attack on the side of Jesus, the two camps finally enter the battle!

The player chooses and plays either pilot Kazuhito Moriguchi (boarding machine RUN = DIM) or Kanna Aso (boarding machine I = RA) belonging to the Green Frontier camp. The game consists of 6 stages.</desc>
		<image>./images/RUN=DIM - Return to Earth (Japan)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/RUN=DIM - Return to Earth (Japan)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/RUN=DIM - Return to Earth (Japan)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/RUN=DIM - Return to Earth (Japan)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<releasedate>20020207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Dream Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Digital Dream Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up / Vertical</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Battle Spirit - Digimon Frontier (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Battle Spirit - Digimon Frontier</name>
		<desc>The plot of Digimon Battle Spirit 2 echoes that of its source series, Digimon Frontier; several children receive messages on their cell phones asking them if they want their lives to change. Some answer yes, some answer no, and five who answer yes are summoned to the Digital World where they receive the ability to become Digimon and fight to end Kerpymon's reign of terror.</desc>
		<image>./images/Battle Spirit - Digimon Frontier (Japan)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Battle Spirit - Digimon Frontier (Japan)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Battle Spirit - Digimon Frontier (Japan)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Battle Spirit - Digimon Frontier (Japan)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20021207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dimps</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<genre>Ação</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Golden Axe (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Golden Axe</name>
		<desc>Sega's classic arcade beat-'em-up game, Golden Axe puts in the shoes of one of three heroes, each with his own reason for trying to overthrow the evil rule of Death-Adder, who - along with his forces of darkness - kidnapped and imprisoned the King and his daughter and stole the legendary Golden Axe.

This is a horizontal fighting game, where you basically take one of the three characters (a warrior, a dwarf or an amazon) and bash everything which stands between you and Death Adder himself.</desc>
		<image>./images/Golden Axe (Japan)-image.png</image>
		<video>./videos/Golden Axe (Japan)-video.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./images/Golden Axe (Japan)-marquee.png</marquee>
		<thumbnail>./images/Golden Axe (Japan)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20020228T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<genre>Jogos de RPG</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
</gameList>
