<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game id="12734" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Captain Tsubasa (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Captain Tsubasa</name>
		<desc>Captain Tsubasa for the SEGA CD is a football game that follows the style of Tecmo Cup. Just like the Japanese version of Tecmo Cup, it is based on the anime series that narrate the adventures of the young Tsubasa, from his beginnings in the Nankatsu team, till the end of the National Championship, where he will compete against his biggest rival in the series, Kojro Hyuga, star striker of the Meiwa.

During matches, you will see an animation of the player you control, and below him a map that indicates the locations of all players competing, your position being highlighted. If no rival appears in your way, you will have total freedom to advance to the rival goal, and when you find it appropriate, stop the game in order to make an action, and then it will appear a menu asking you if you want to pass, shoot or make a special move (depending on how high your guts counter is).</desc>
		<releasedate>19940930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/Captain Tsubasa (Japan).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="12783" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Cobra Command (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Cobra Command</name>
		<desc>Cobra Command is an arcade conversion of a helicopter shooting game from Data East.  It is an "on rails" style shooter with the player controlling only the aiming of the shooting but not the direction of the helicopter.  

Your job is to shoot down the enemies as you are flown through footage of New York streets, the Statue of Liberty, the Atlantic Ocean, Italy, the Grand Canyon and finally, the treacherous corners and return fire of the enemy's stronghold on Easter Island.

There is no background music to go along with the sound effects.  The levels are fairly short with a total game run through possible in about 20 minutes.</desc>
		<rating>0.15</rating>
		<releasedate>19921101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation-Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Cobra Command (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="12806" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Death Bringer (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Death Bringer</name>
		<desc>Death Bringer on Mega CD is a FPS RPG (first person roleplaying game) in the world of Mezron. The story begins with the resurrection of the evil Azazael, looking for five precious stones giving great powers. The player plays an adventurer who tries to stop Azazael in his quest.</desc>
		<rating>0.25</rating>
		<releasedate>19920417T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Telenet</developer>
		<publisher>Telenet</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Death Bringer (Japan).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="12719" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dragon's Lair (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Dragon's Lair</name>
		<desc>A conversion of the 1983 Don Bluth coin op cartoon game.  Players control Dirk the Daring as he struggles his way through a dungeon to fight Singe, the Dragon, and rescue the beautiful Princess Daphne.  With limited movement allowed, the game's main emphasis is on its heart-stopping graphics.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ReadySoft</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure-Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Dragon's Lair (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="97352" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Egawa Suguru no Super League CD (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Egawa Suguru No Super League CD</name>
		<desc>Egawa Suguru no Super League CD is the fourth and final entry in Sega's 16-bit Super League baseball franchise, featuring the endorsement of baseball commentator Suguru Egawa, star pitcher for the Yomiuri Giants from 1979 until 1987. As usual, the game features an NPB license and includes all 12 Pacific and Central League teams with full 1993 rosters, along with All-Star teams for each league. 
 
Gameplay is largely unchanged from previous installments, utilizing the standard catcher's view for both batting and pitching. The game includes the usual Pennant Race and Exhibition match modes. New in this version are the additions of a Home Run Contest mode and a team database. 
 
Alongside Konami's Hyper Dunk, Super League CD is one of the few commercialized games that supports up to eight players with the use of two SegaTap adapters. 
 
</desc>
		<releasedate>19930806T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./media/images/Egawa Suguru no Super League CD (Japan).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="12702" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Sonic CD (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Sonic the Hedgehog CD</name>
		<desc>This is a standard Sonic the Hedgehog side-scrolling action game. Dr. Robotnik has taken over the Little Planet, captured Amy, and created Metal Sonic with the goal of collecting all the Time Stones to be able to manipulate time and conquer the world.  It is up to Sonic to stop him, by rushing through levels set in different time periods, collecting Time Stones.

Sonic CD has features that take advantage of the CD format such as CD audio, video clips, and more levels (over 50 in total).</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19931119T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Sonic CD (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="12703" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Theme Park (Europe).chd</path>
		<name>Theme Park</name>
		<desc>Dominating the exciting world of Theme Park ownership is your goal in this strategy game from Bullfrog. The first task is to set up your rides within the available land, structuring convenient paths and queues and ideally leaving some space for bigger rides once they become available, and include some lakes and trees to increase the park's allure. Rides range from Teacups and Haunted Houses to the biggest most elaborate roller-coaster you can design, and water rides that loop around other rides.

Shops must also be included, so that the visitors can buy food, drinks and souvenirs - the cunning player will combine salt, sugar and caffeine settings to maximize consumer interest. Staff must be hired to keep everything running smoothly, and they will only work for what they consider a fair rate of pay.

You are competing against other Theme Parks, so don't let them get an advantage over you - monitor your success in attracting customers and financial viability closely using the supplied statistics pages. More important, ensure that research is adequately funded to produce new rides.

It can be played in three modes - Sandbox level lets you concentrate on the park design elements, while Sim and Full add more strategic features.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Domark</developer>
		<publisher>Bullfrog</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Theme Park (Europe).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="12783" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Thunder Storm FX (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Thunder Storm</name>
		<desc>Cobra Command is an arcade conversion of a helicopter shooting game from Data East.  It is an "on rails" style shooter with the player controlling only the aiming of the shooting but not the direction of the helicopter.  

Your job is to shoot down the enemies as you are flown through footage of New York streets, the Statue of Liberty, the Atlantic Ocean, Italy, the Grand Canyon and finally, the treacherous corners and return fire of the enemy's stronghold on Easter Island.

There is no background music to go along with the sound effects.  The levels are fairly short with a total game run through possible in about 20 minutes.</desc>
		<rating>0.15</rating>
		<releasedate>19920828T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation-Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Cobra Command (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="12708" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Final Fight CD (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Final Fight CD</name>
		<desc>The game is set in the metropolis of Metro City, a town constantly plagued by crime and violence. When the mayor, Mike Haggar, promises to clean up the city, the Mad Gear gang kidnaps his daughter Jessica and warns him not to interfere. Haggar responds going on a battle across the city to free her, bringing along her boyfriend Cody, and the ninjitsu master Guy to assist him.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Final Fight CD (USA).png</image>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
</gameList>
