<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game id="43837" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./unsquad.7z</path>
		<name>U.N. Squadron (US) (aka Area 88)</name>
		<desc>U.N. Squadron / Area 88 is a horizontally-scrolling shoot-em-up and is based on the Manga series of the same name. The game features characters from the original Manga and their mission is to battle their way through enemy-packed levels to stop a terrorist group known as 'Project 4'.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Shoot'em up / Horizontal</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/unsquad.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37363" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./forgottn.7z</path>
		<name>Forgotten Worlds (World, newer)</name>
		<desc>The planet used to be beautiful, with gorgeous cities and gleaming countrysides. Until the Aliens attacked! With fire, bombs, and napalm they devastated the world! They made the planet so abominable that it became an outcast in the universe - the Forgotten World. Until you, the Nameless One, appear. You're a Super Warrior of incredible power and energy. You make it your business to reclaim the panet for its rightful owners - the Human Beings!</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Horizontal-Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/forgottn.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="149437" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./gng.7z</path>
		<name>Ghosts'n Goblins (World? set 1)</name>
		<desc>Ghosts 'n Goblins is a platform game where the player controls a knight, named Sir Arthur, who must defeat zombies, ogres, demons, cyclops, dragons and other monsters in order to rescue Princess Prin Prin, who has been kidnapped by Satan, king of Demon World. Along the way the player can pick up new weapons, bonuses and extra suits of armor that can help in this task. 
 
The player can only be hit twice before losing a life. If the player loses a life, they are returned to the start of the level, or the halfway point if they have managed to get that far. Furthermore, each life can only last a certain length of time. After defeating the final boss, the player must then replay the entire game on a higher difficulty level to reach the genuine final battle.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/gng.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="42200" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./lwings.7z</path>
		<name>Legendary Wings (US set 1)</name>
		<desc>The human race was about to achieve the evolution from an ancient civilization to a state of millennium with the help of DARK, a super powerful computer left by spacemen long ago. DARK suddenly began to malfunction. 
 
The world was in a panic. The human race was on the brink of extinction. 
 
ARES, god of war, gave two young men Wings of Love and Courage and entrusted them with the survival and future of the human race. Time is of the essence. Destroy DARK Take wings, legendary soldiers.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Shoot'em up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/lwings.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="57920" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./msword.7z</path>
		<name>Magic Sword: Heroic Fantasy (World 900725)</name>
		<desc>Magic Sword: Heroic Fantasy is a side-scrolling fantasy arcade game released by Capcom in 1990. The player can use a sword, an axe, or magic, and can also rescue and recruit potential allies from different character classes, each with their own special abilities. Three years earlier, Capcom had released the similar Black Tiger in 1987. 
 
Magic Sword is set in a nameless world threatened by the dark lord Drokmar, who is in control of an evil crystal known as the "Black Orb" that would allow him to rule the world. To prevent this from happening, the Brave Hero must climb to the top of the 50-story tower that Drokmar resides in, known as the Dragon Keep. After Drokmar is defeated, the player has the option of two endings: destroy the Black Orb, or take control of it and become the new Dark Lord.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform / Fighter Scrolling-Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/msword.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37399" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./mmatrix.7z</path>
		<name>Mars Matrix: Hyper Solid Shooting (USA 000412)</name>
		<desc>A prediction is that before human civilization, there was once an advanced civilization on Mars. A sorceress destroyed the civilization and everything that was remembered of it, except a chip called "INFINITY". In 2100, millions of people were starving due to massive food shortages and has caused civil wars around the world. Centuries later, however, the world government had sent colonists to Mars which began to solve these problems. At a nearby farm, the Infinity chip was discovered and it revealed all the technology of the advanced civilization. In 2309, a Declaration of Independence has been sent to Earth. Large armies have been amassed on Mars, and a gigantic armada was waiting for any attack from Earth. The Earth government sends out a fleet of battleships followed by a special air raid unit called ACID; ACID is equipped with a new fighter ship known as the Mosquito. Their mission is to enter Mars, stop the rebel violence, locate and destroy the rebel leader, whoever... or whatever it may be...</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Takumi</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Shoot'em up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/mmatrix.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37401" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./msh.7z</path>
		<name>Marvel Super Heroes (Euro 951024)</name>
		<desc>Play as your favorite Marvel character: Wolverine, Spider-Man, The Incredible Hulk, Captain America, Iron Man, Psylocke, Shuma-Gorath, Blackheart, Juggernaut or Magneto. Power up with an Infinity Gem - Grant your super hero healing power, super attacks and increased strength.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight-Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/msh.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37402" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./mshvsf.7z</path>
		<name>Marvel Super Heroes vs. Street Fighter (Euro 970625)</name>
		<desc>Marvel Super Heroes vs. Street Fighter is the fourth Marvel Comics-licensed fighting game produced by Capcom and the second installment in the Marvel vs. Capcom series. It is a sequel to X-Men vs. Street Fighter which replaces most of the X-Men characters with characters from Marvel Super Heroes. In an attempt to balance the previous game's problems, the game engine was altered, although it remained aesthetically the same which is what the game was criticized for. The game was released for the arcade in 1997 
 
Marvel Super Heroes vs. Street Fighter features a roster of 17 playable fighters, with nine characters from the Street Fighter universe and eight heroes from the Marvel Universe, It utilizes the same one-on-one tag team format previously employed in X-Men vs. Street Fighter.  
The player chooses a team of two fighters, each sporting their own life gauge; at the start of the match, the first selected character is controlled by the player, while the second character remains off-screen and acts as support. 
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight-Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/mshvsf.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37402" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./mshvsfj1.7z</path>
		<name>Marvel Super Heroes vs. Street Fighter (Japan 970702)</name>
		<desc>####### Norimaro unlock ########
Marvel Super Heroes vs. Street Fighter is the fourth Marvel Comics-licensed fighting game produced by Capcom and the second installment in the Marvel vs. Capcom series. It is a sequel to X-Men vs. Street Fighter which replaces most of the X-Men characters with characters from Marvel Super Heroes. In an attempt to balance the previous game's problems, the game engine was altered, although it remained aesthetically the same which is what the game was criticized for. The game was released for the arcade in 1997 

Marvel Super Heroes vs. Street Fighter features a roster of 17 playable fighters, with nine characters from the Street Fighter universe and eight heroes from the Marvel Universe, It utilizes the same one-on-one tag team format previously employed in X-Men vs. Street Fighter.  
The player chooses a team of two fighters, each sporting their own life gauge; at the start of the match, the first selected character is controlled by the player, while the second character remains off-screen and acts as support. 
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight-Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/mshvsfj.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37402" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./mshvsfj.7z</path>
		<name>Marvel Super Heroes vs. Street Fighter (Japan 970702)</name>
		<desc>####### Norimaro unlock ########
Marvel Super Heroes vs. Street Fighter is the fourth Marvel Comics-licensed fighting game produced by Capcom and the second installment in the Marvel vs. Capcom series. It is a sequel to X-Men vs. Street Fighter which replaces most of the X-Men characters with characters from Marvel Super Heroes. In an attempt to balance the previous game's problems, the game engine was altered, although it remained aesthetically the same which is what the game was criticized for. The game was released for the arcade in 1997 

Marvel Super Heroes vs. Street Fighter features a roster of 17 playable fighters, with nine characters from the Street Fighter universe and eight heroes from the Marvel Universe, It utilizes the same one-on-one tag team format previously employed in X-Men vs. Street Fighter.  
The player chooses a team of two fighters, each sporting their own life gauge; at the start of the match, the first selected character is controlled by the player, while the second character remains off-screen and acts as support. 
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight-Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/mshvsfj.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37403" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./mvsc.7z</path>
		<name>Marvel vs. Capcom : Clash of Super Heroes (Euro 980123)</name>
		<desc>Marvel vs. Capcom: Clash of Super Heroes is the fifth Marvel Comics-licensed fighting game by Capcom and the third game in the Marvel vs. Capcom series. In contrast to X-Men vs. Street Fighter and Marvel Super Heroes vs. Street Fighter, the game features characters from numerous Capcom franchises such as Mega Man and Strider, rather than just Street Fighter characters. The game takes place within the Marvel comic continuity, as Professor Charles Xavier calls out for heroes to stop him before he merges with the consciousness of Magneto and becomes the being known as Onslaught, the final boss. The game was developed in late 1997 and first released in January 1998.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19980123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight-Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/mvsc.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37371" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./mtwins.7z</path>
		<name>Mega Twins (World 900619)</name>
		<desc>The game features two twins who are attempting to re-take control of their land, Alurea, after a monster unexpectedly attacks, destroying everything in its path. The people of Alurea have lived in peace for a thousand years and have forgotten how to fight, yet the land's only survivors, the twin sons of the king, must take up the challenge and return their kingdom to its former glory. The two twins, aged around 15 at the time the game takes place, venture forth in search of a legendary stone known as "Dragon Blue Eyes", which is rumored to be able to put everything back to rights.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Platform / Fighter Scrolling</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/mtwins.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="78903" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./mercs.7z</path>
		<name>Mercs (World 900302)</name>
		<desc>The US faces a grave crisis! The former president has been kidnapped by a group of revolutionaries while on a trip on Central Africa meant to promote world peace. Take control of three highly skilled anti-terrorist soldiers and venture through enemy lines to save the former president &amp; annihilate the rebel army in the process. Features solid graphics &amp; sound, plenty of weapons &amp; vehicles to use and hulking bosses to defeat.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter-Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-3</players>
		<image>./media/images/mercs.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37400" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./mpang.7z</path>
		<name>Mighty! Pang (Euro 001010)</name>
		<desc>Mighty! Pang is the fourth game in the superb Pang series. While the artistic design has been drastically changed, Mighty! Pang retains the same gameplay of its predecessors. The game features three modes of play: panic, tour and expert modes.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mitchell</developer>
		<publisher>Mitchell</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/mpang.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37367" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./mbombrd.7z</path>
		<name>Muscle Bomber Duo : Ultimate Team Battle (World 931206)</name>
		<desc>Professional wrestling experienced a sudden increase in popularity during the early 1980s, where many professional wrestling organizations were started all over the world. A severe rivalry existed among the organizations. 
 
In order to resolve this conflict, 8 organizations combined to form the Capcom Professional Wrestling Association (CPWA), led by Victor Ortega, the CPWA?s first champion. 
 
One day, Ortega suddenly vanished. He was considered to be the axis of the sport and his unexpected disappearance caused the CPWA to enter an age of confusion and disorder. The BPWA, a dark underground wrestling organization, chose to take advantage of this opportunity and began moving. With "Fighters of Muscle Bomber = Destiny" as the theme, the CPWA chief executives decided to hold a world tour called the ?Crash Carnival,? to decide the new king of the CPWA. 
 
The gong that determines the new ?Master of Muscle Bomber? is sounded?</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Sports-Sports / Wrestling</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/mbombrd.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37372" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./nemo.7z</path>
		<name>Nemo (World 901130)</name>
		<desc>One night, as Nemo sleeps, he is visited in a dream by the King of Slumberland, who invites Nemo to come and play with the King's daughter, the Princess. Nemo finds himself unable to find the Princess however, so he and 'Flip', a strange companion who also turns up in the dream, decide to explore Slumberland and find the king.

Nemo is a colourful and abstract platform shoot-em-up set in the dream world of Slumberland, a surreal world in which childrens' toys are running amok and must be destroyed. Nemo is armed with a magical staff that emits a burst of magic to destroy the many enemies, some of which require multiple hits. A number of power-ups also appear at regular intervals to aid Nemo in his quest through seven tough stages.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform / Fighter Scrolling-Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/nemo.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37373" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./pang3.7z</path>
		<name>Pang! 3 (Euro 950601)</name>
		<desc>Pang! 3 is the second sequel to the superb 1989 original, Pang! 3 retains the same gameplay of its predecessors but adds vastly improved graphics and a choice of three difficulty levels; Beginner, Normal and Panic. On both the 'Normal' and 'Panic' skill levels, players can choose from 4 different playable characters; each possessing different strengths and weaknesses, such as a double harpoon or quick shots. On the beginner level, players can only use the Mexican character. 
 
Another notable difference is in the game's use of backdrops: instead of the world landmarks of the first two games, Pang! 3 features classical works of art in the form of paintings and sculptures.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mitchell</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/pang3.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="41675" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./higemaru.7z</path>
		<name>Pirate Ship Higemaru</name>
		<desc>Take on the role of Momotaro who must launch barrels at enemies to stop the evil Higemaru pirates.</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Action / Labyrinth</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/higemaru.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37374" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./pnickj.7z</path>
		<name>Pnickies (Japan 940608)</name>
		<desc>A falling blocks game released only to arcades. Like-colored blocks merge together and more points are awarded for larger masses.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game / Fall-Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/pnickj.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37410" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./sgemf.7z</path>
		<name>Super Gem Fighter Mini Mix (USA 970904)</name>
		<desc>Super Gem Fighter: Mini Mix / Pocket Fighter is a superb, abstract and humorous fighting game featuring miniaturized renditions from several Capcom fighting games; including the legendary "Street Fighter" series, as well as "Darkstalkers" and the little-known "Red Earth". 
 
During a bout, players will be able to release coloured gems from successful attacks against their opponent, as well as from wooden chests that regularly appear. Collecting these gems will 'power-up' the player's character, giving them more powerful attacks. There are two bars and three sub-bars in the interface. The two main bars are the life bar and the super bar; the first indicates the player's health and the second their ability to throw super combos. The Super Bar itself can be filled up to nine levels, allowing players to execute more super combos. Each super combo has a level assigned to it, and it uses Super Bars depending on it.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus-Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/sgemf.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37404" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./progear.7z</path>
		<name>Progear (USA 010117)</name>
		<desc>In a time when the industrialization of the world had just begun, various inventions appeared and changed the life of the peaceful kingdom. One of them was a propeller that evolved from pure wind generation by using the created electricity to re-rotate it. It was called 'The Professional Gear', or just 'Progear'. This invention was the key to conquer the great wide open sky. Another discovery made the ancient dream of the immortal body come true. But it was affordable only by some wealthy elderly. They formed a new council called 'the Motorouin' and declared the current government as a corruptive and greedy establishment and that they want to correct it by a new educational system, in order to create a new race of man. So they built a military force to realize the first step of their plan, which was the takeover of the kingdom. The government decided to stop the aggression by putting it's own army in motion. It was a dreadful battle with many victims. But it was won by the Motorouin. This battle is mentioned in the books of history as 'The Punishment of the Sages'. 
 
A group of young pilots, actually children whose families were killed in that war, finally decided to fight back. They secretly developed a new powerful weapon which adults were not able to use. They called it 'Gun Flyer' and installed it in all of their planes. The Storm of Progear was about to begin!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20010101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cave</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Shoot'em up / Horizontal</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/progear.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37405" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./pzloop2.7z</path>
		<name>Puzz Loop 2 (Euro 010302)</name>
		<desc>Gameplay is exactly the same as its predecessor, Puzz Loop , with the player needing to deplete all the colored balls before they hit the center of the screen.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20010101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mitchell</developer>
		<publisher>Mitchell</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game / Throw-Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/pzloop2.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="42597" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./qndream.7z</path>
		<name>Quiz Nanairo Dreams: Nijiirochou no Kiseki (Japan 960826)</name>
		<desc>Quiz Nanairo Dreams - Nijiirochou no Kiseki is a quiz game where your goal is to befriend a number of female and obtain the crystals which are used to defeat the Devil King.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Quiz / Japanese-Quiz</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/qndream.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="78893" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./megaman2.7z</path>
		<name>Rockman 2: The Power Fighters (USA 960708)</name>
		<desc>Building upon the previous game, you must battle Dr. Wily's evil robot criminals with the help of Megaman, Protoman, Bass &amp; Duo. Features cool 2-D graphics and the same tried &amp; true Mega Man controls. Pay attention to Dr. Light's advice and you may reach Dr. Wily's fortress and come out victorious!</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight-Fight /  Co-op</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/megaman2.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="78892" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./megaman.7z</path>
		<name>Rockman: The Power Battle (CPS1, USA 951006)</name>
		<desc>Have you ever pictured a Rockman or Megaman game that allows to skip all the platform elements and just grapple against the bosses? That's pretty much the main idea in this game! Choose from Rockman/Megaman, Protoman or Bass and battle against classic bosses in the series. Features great 2-D graphics, solid control, and a nice use of strategy (since the right order of weapons will rid you of specific enemies in no time!).</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight-Fight /  Co-op</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/megaman.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="43179" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./sonson.7z</path>
		<name>Son Son</name>
		<desc>Son Son is a 2-D sidescrolling platformer. The screen scrolls automatically, only stopping to fight major enemies. The screen features six continuous platforms that occasionally feature small gaps. Sonson and Tonton walk automatically across these platforms. Pressing up or down will cause them to jump up or down to the next platform. Pressing left causes them to move more slowly than the screen scrolls, essentially continuing to move forward but at a reduced pace. Pressing right does the opposite - SonSon and TonTon will move across the platforms faster than the screen scrolls. The duo have only one attack - the ability to fire energy blasts from their staves. Touching an enemy or an unfriendly projectile causes the player to lose a life. If a player has any additional lives, they will return to the screen riding on a cloud that will give them temporary invincibility. If the player presses the control stick in any direction, the cloud will disappear and the character will resume its usual walking mode. The cloud will eventually disappear on its own if the control stick is not used.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform / Shooter Scrolling-Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/sonson.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37377" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./sf2ce.7z</path>
		<name>Street Fighter II' : Champion Edition (World 920513)</name>
		<desc>From the corners of the globe come twelve of the toughest fighters to ever prowl the streets. Choose your champion and step into the arena as one of the eight original challengers or as one of the four Grand Masters! Pound your opponent as Balrog and knock them out for the count. Tower over your prey as Sagat and daze them with your awesome Tiger Shot. Slash your opponent with Vega's claw and send them running for cover. Or strike fear into your enemies as M. Bison, the greatest Grand Master of them all!</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus-Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/sf2ce.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37378" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./sf2hf.7z</path>
		<name>Street Fighter II' : Hyper Fighting (World 921209)</name>
		<desc>Street Fighter II': Hyper Fighting (Street Fighter II' Turbo: Hyper Fighting in Japan) is the second upgrade to the Street Fighter II series after Street Fighter II': Champion Edition. It is a simple modification of the game made by Capcom USA (James Goddard), in an attempt to counter the proliferation of the many unofficial hacks available at the time, and to incorporate into the official game some of the most popular improvements made by them, including attack speed and new paddles on certain hacks.nnThe speed of the game has been greatly increased (hence the Turbo on the console port of the game); and new special moves are available to certain characters, making combat much more strategic.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus-Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/sf2hf.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37425" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./sfiii.7z</path>
		<name>Street Fighter III : New Generation (Euro 970204)</name>
		<desc>Street Fighter III - New Generation é uma Nova Geração de Street Fighters! Apresenta sprites de personagens maiores do que os jogos Street Fighter anteriores com a animação 2D mais detalhada e mais suave já feita até momento de seu lançamento, um nível de qualidade que ainda precisa ser igualado por qualquer outro jogo 2-D fora da série Street Fighter III a partir de 2004; alguns reclamam que muitas coisas são animadas e cada animação contém muitos quadros, diminuindo o ritmo do jogo.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Luta / Versus-Luta</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/sfiii.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37423" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./sfiii2.7z</path>
		<name>Street Fighter III 2nd Impact : Giant Attack (USA 970930)</name>
		<desc>Street Fighter III - 2nd Impact: Giant Attack is the sequel to "Street Fighter III - New Generation". Joining the existing Street Fighter III cast are Hugo, Urien and recurring character Akuma (Gouki in the Japanese version). Other improvements include a speed increase, new moves and several damage-related tweaks.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus-Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/sfiii2.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37424" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./sfiii3.7z</path>
		<name>Street Fighter III 3rd Strike : Fight for the Future (Euro 990608)</name>
		<desc>New characters Remy, Makoto, Q, and Twelve join the returning Street Fighter veteran Chun-Li and the existing "Street Fighter III - 2nd Impact: Giant Attack" cast in this third and final installment of Street Fighter III.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19990512T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus-Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/sfiii3.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="42986" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./sfzj.7z</path>
		<name>Street Fighter Zero (Japan 950727)</name>
		<desc>It's Street Fighter as you always remember it, with some new moves, characters and combo systems, as well as a more polished look and feel.

The new moves available for each fighter, called Super moves, allow them to fire off very powerful moves. A bar at the bottom of the screen represents the power that you have to use for the moves. You start the first round on 0, and each attack that you make adds power to the bar. Once you reach level 3, you can unleash the special attacks, that can sometimes KO the opponant.

The other major change over the Street Fighter 2 series are the Alpha counters. These can be used to counter an on-coming attack after blocking.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight-Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/sfzj.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37408" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./sfz2j.7z</path>
		<name>Street Fighter Zero 2 (Japan 960430)</name>
		<desc>Street Fighter Alpha 2, known as Street Fighter Zero 2 in Japan, Asia and South America, is a 1996 fighting game originally released for the CPS II arcade hardware by Capcom. The game is both a sequel and a remake to the previous year's Street Fighter Alpha: Warriors' Dreams, which is itself a prequel to the Street Fighter II series in terms of plot and setting</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus-Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/sfz2j.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="43009" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./sfz2al.7z</path>
		<name>Street Fighter Zero 2 Alpha (Asia 960826)</name>
		<desc>Street Fighter Zero 2 Alpha is an enhanced version of "Street Fighter Zero 2" released in arcades in Japan, southeast Asia, Brazil, and Hispanic regions. In North America and Europe, where its predecessor is known as "Street Fighter Alpha 2", this enhanced version appears on home consoles only.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus-Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/sfz2al.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37380" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./strider.7z</path>
		<name>Strider (USA, B-Board 89624B-2)</name>
		<desc>Strider is a multi-directional scrolling platform beat-em-up in which the player takes control of 'Strider Hiryu', a ninja-style warrior who must defeat a legendary being known as 'Grandmaster Meio'.  
 
Set in a dystopian future in the year 2048, Meio has been watching Earth from his own distant galaxy and has created a space station (known as 'The Third Moon') between Earth and its moon in order to rule over the Human race. </desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform / Fighter Scrolling-Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/strider.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="42766" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./ringdest.7z</path>
		<name>Super Muscle Bomber: The International Blowout (Euro 940902)</name>
		<desc>Ring of Destruction: Slam Masters II, is the 1994 sequel to Saturday Night Slam Masters and the second game in the series. It was not ported to home consoles. 
 
Unlike the first game, which played like a traditional wrestling game, Ring of Destruction's format was changed to play like a traditional one-on-one 2D fighting game (similar to Super Street Fighter II), with the action restricted to one plane. The game's configuration was changed to a five-button setup (two punch buttons, two kick buttons and a grappling button). The objective of each match is to deplete the opponent's life bar in two out of three rounds. It is no longer necessary for the player to pin their opponent to win a match, although all the other moves have been retained. 
 
</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/ringdest.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37411" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./spf2t.7z</path>
		<name>Super Puzzle Fighter II Turbo (960529 Euro)</name>
		<desc>Burst right into the feverish puzzle action that combines irresistible, addictive fun with famous Capcom characters. Beat your opponent to the punch by stacking block after block in strategic patterns and color combinations. Be the first to fill the opponent's screen with blocks and K.O. you win! But get ready for more, because you can't play just once.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game / Fall-Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/spf2t.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37413" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./ssf2t.7z</path>
		<name>Super Street Fighter II Turbo (World 940223)</name>
		<desc>Super Street Fighter II Turbo, released in Japan as Super Street Fighter II X: Grand Master Challenge, is a competitive fighting game released for the arcades by Capcom in 1994. It is the fifth arcade installment in the Street Fighter II sub-series of Street Fighter games, following Super Street Fighter II. Like its predecessor, it ran on the CP System II hardware. 
 
Super Turbo introduced several new play mechanics to the game system from the previous Street Fighter II installments, including the addition of powered-up Special Moves called Super Combos. It also introduced the hidden character of Akuma, who would go on to become a recurring character in later Street Fighter installments and other Capcom fighting games.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940223T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus-Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/ssf2t.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37413" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./ssf2xj.7z</path>
		<name>Super Street Fighter II X: Grand Master Challenge (Japan 940311)</name>
		<desc>Super Street Fighter II Turbo, released in Japan as Super Street Fighter II X: Grand Master Challenge, is a competitive fighting game released for the arcades by Capcom in 1994. It is the fifth arcade installment in the Street Fighter II sub-series of Street Fighter games, following Super Street Fighter II. Like its predecessor, it ran on the CP System II hardware. 
 
Super Turbo introduced several new play mechanics to the game system from the previous Street Fighter II installments, including the addition of powered-up Special Moves called Super Combos. It also introduced the hidden character of Akuma, who would go on to become a recurring character in later Street Fighter installments and other Capcom fighting games.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940223T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus-Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/ssf2xj.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="43304" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./ssf2.7z</path>
		<name>Super Street Fighter II: The New Challengers (World 931005)</name>
		<desc>Super Street Fighter II: The New Challengers is the fourth game in the Street Fighter II sub-series of Street Fighter games, following Street Fighter II: Hyper Fighting. In addition to refining and balancing the existing character roster from the previous installments, Super Street Fighter II also introduced four new characters. 
 
This game is also known under the name of Super Street Fighter II: The Tournament Battle when 4 Cabinets are connected to play in tournament mode.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus-Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/ssf2.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="43741" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./trojan.7z</path>
		<name>Trojan (US set 1)</name>
		<desc>The game consist of six stages, where the player will face the usual series of small fry enemies, as well as a sub-boss at the middle of each stage and a boss at the end. The player is allowed to start the game at any of the six stages. However, the player must play through the entire game again after defeating the final boss, Achilles, in order to see the true ending (similarly to Ghosts'n Goblins). The player can continue after a game over depending on the dip switch settings.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up-Fight / 2D-Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/trojan.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37366" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./kod.7z</path>
		<name>The King of Dragons (World 910805)</name>
		<desc>The King of Dragons is a 1991 side-scrolling hack and slash video game by Capcom that allows players to choose from five characters (Elf, Wizard, Fighter, Cleric, and Dwarf) in order to travel through the kingdom of Malus and defeat the monsters that have taken over, as well as their leader, the red dragon Gildiss. Like Capcom's Knights of the Round, it features a level advancement system, allowing character attributes to be upgraded as players progress through the game. The setting is very similar to that of Dungeons &amp; Dragons and other medieval fantasy worlds, with familiar monsters such as Orcs, Gnolls, Harpies, Wyverns, Cyclopes, and Minotaurs.

The game was ported to the Super NES and released in 1994. An emulated version of the game was released as part of Capcom Classics Collection Vol. 2 and Capcom Classics Collection: Reloaded.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight-Fight / 2.5D-Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-3</players>
		<image>./media/images/kod.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37375" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./punisher.7z</path>
		<name>The Punisher (World 930422)</name>
		<desc>A Capcom arcade beat-em-up game similar to games like Double Dragon featuring the Marvel character The Punisher. Nick Fury is also a playable character in this game.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/punisher.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="43298" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./srumbler.7z</path>
		<name>The Speed Rumbler (set 1)</name>
		<desc>It's the 21st century in America. Technology has improved by leaps and bounds, and now (most) people live in peace. But in a small town somewhere, a vicious terrorist group known as Zapper is terrorizing small towns and kidnapping innocent people so that they can build a secret weapon. And, as it turns out, the family and friends of someone code-named "Super Joe" just so happened to be one of the innocents caught! Now Super Joe's hungry for revenge. Can Super Joe and his armored car destroy the Zapper organization and save his town from utter destruction in time? The Speed Rumbler is a action game where the player races against the clock in an armored car piloted by Super Joe, destroying other cars and saving captives along the way. Super Joe's car is armed with a gun that he can use to shoot down enemy cars, but the enemy cars have a few tricks up their sleeve, so Super Joe should always be on guard. As the player progresses through the game's six stages, Super Joe can be given a boost by saving captives, who then award him with bonus points, increased fire power, or speed-ups. If Super Joe's car is destroyed, he can continue the fight on foot with his rifle. But unfortunately, Super Joe is not as powerful as his car - one hit and he's history. Super Joe has 24 "hours" to destroy Zapper. The game is over when Super Joe runs out of lives or time - or if he successfully completes his mission.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / Vehicle, Vertical-Shooter</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/srumbler.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37357" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./3wonders.7z</path>
		<name>Three Wonders (World 910520)</name>
		<desc>Three Wonders contains three games from which a player may choose: 
 
Midnight Wanderers: Quest for the Chariot - A platform game that sees the player control a hobbit named Lou and his traveling companion, Siva, to run, climb, and shoot at enemies. 
Chariot: Adventure through the Sky - A shoot 'em up game featuring the characters from Midnight Wanderers, but in a Gradius-esque game. 
Don't Pull - A puzzle game similar to games like the Eggerland series, Pengo and Capcom's own puzzle game Pirate Ship Higemaru. It involves the player controlling either a rabbit named Don (Player 1) or a squirrel called Pull (Player 2), pushing blocks to crush monsters.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Compilation-Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/3wonders.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="43612" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./tigeroad.7z</path>
		<name>Tiger Road (US)</name>
		<desc>Tiger Road is a beat 'em up in which you (as Lee Wong) must rescue the village children from the evil Ryo Ken Oh. Many levels are horizontally scrolling, although with high ledges to jump onto and follow for a slightly different path. Magic urns containing improved weapons appear frequently. Most enemies are easy to attack and only need one hit to kill, although they come at you in large hordes. Once you get to the indoor sections you will find big enemies with the ability to kill you with one hit, in sections set on multiple levels complete with stairways.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform / Fighter Scrolling-Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/tigeroad.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37415" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./vhunt2.7z</path>
		<name>Vampire Hunter 2: Darkstalkers' Revenge (Japan 970929)</name>
		<desc>Fourteen well-animated creatures from Hell rip, tear and otherwise fight for control of the nether-realms.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus-Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/vhunt2.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="44387" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./nwarr.7z</path>
		<name>Night Warriors: Darkstalkers' Revenge (Euro 950316)</name>
		<desc>Night Warriors: Darkstalkers' Revenge is the second game in the Darkstalkers series of gothic horror fighting games. Released in 1995, it is the upgraded version of the original game which introduced several gameplay changes to the game. 
 
The game introduced two new playable characters, Donovan Baine and Hsien-Ko, who were out to hunt the other Darkstalkers (hence the Japanese title, Vampire Hunter). The two bosses from the first game, Huitzil and Pyron, were now playable characters as well. The game was first released for arcades and later ported to the Sega Saturn. Character art was done by Ikeno.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus-Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/nwarr.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37418" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./vsav2.7z</path>
		<name>Vampire Savior 2 : The Lord of Vampire (Japan 970913)</name>
		<desc>Fifteen characters fight to end the reign of Jedah, the Vampire Savior and save their own souls!</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus-Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/vsav2.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37417" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./vsav.7z</path>
		<name>Vampire Savior: The Lord of Vampire (Euro 970519)</name>
		<desc>Jedah, one of the ancient Three Lords of Darkrealm has returned. You play as one of fifteen Darkstalkers. Beat Jedah and take your throne as the Lord of the Darkness.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus-Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/vsav.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="41049" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./vampjr1.7z</path>
		<name>Vampire: The Night Warriors (Japan 940630)</name>
		<desc>People tremble in fear of these monsters. A mysterious force awakens them from their long slumber. 'Arise and show your fangs!' The silence of the night is broken by the growls and roars of these evil spirits which have been summoned from beyond. They are coming... tonight! DarkStalkers - the warriors of the night! 
 
DarkStalkers features spectacular fighting between supernatural monsters with 4 TIMES the graphics of SFII (its 15,000 animation patterns put it way out in front of SSFII Turbo, resulting in realistic movement with smooth animation). With endless playability you'll never tire of, make sport of your opponent with incredible moves like the Special Attack and Death Blow which are humanly impossible. We're talking about unlimited varieties of attack! 
 
The unimaginable secret power of the dark is unleashed!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight-Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/dstlk.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37382" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./varth.7z</path>
		<name>Varth: Operation Thunderstorm (World 920714)</name>
		<desc>Varth: Operation Thunderstorm is an arcade game in the vertical scrolling shooter genre, published in 1992. The game did not see a console port following its initial release, but 14 years later Digital Eclipse Software would port the game onto the PlayStation 2, PSP and Xbox as part of the Capcom Classics Collection Vol. 2.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Shoot'em up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/varth.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="44019" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./vulgus.7z</path>
		<name>Vulgus (set 1)</name>
		<desc>Vulgus is pretty simple. You just pilot a spaceship and blast countless enemies. That is what is fun about this game. There is nothing complicated, just pure blasting. You only have two weapons, your blaster, and a limited supply of bombs. This title uses the time honored top-down vertically scrolling format. The background moves eternally forward, but you can move all around the screen, and can make the screen scroll both left and right. Your enemies consist of an assortment of fairly realistic looking spacecraft, some of which have a distinctive 'insectoid' look to them. This game is endless and it doesn't seem to have a level format. You just move forward and shoot. The backgrounds will change from time to time from planetary surfaces to space scenes and eventually they will start repeating once you blast this particularly large alien formation.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Shoot'em up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/vulgus.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="44111" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./wof.7z</path>
		<name>Warriors of Fate (World 921031)</name>
		<desc>Warriors of Fate is a side-scrolling beat 'em up produced by Capcom, first released as a coin-operated arcade game in 1992 and later ported to the Sega Saturn and Sony PlayStation. It is Capcom's third game based on the Tenchi wo Kurau manga, following Dynasty Wars and Destiny of an Emperor.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-3</players>
		<image>./media/images/wof.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37426" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./redearth.7z</path>
		<name>Red Earth (Euro 961121)</name>
		<desc>Red Earth take place in the year 1999 of an alternate Earth, follow the adventures of four heroes as they take on an army of mythical monsters unleashed by Scion to bring about the destruction of the world. Take your pick from Leo the Lion King, Mai-Ling the Martial artist, Tessa the Witch, or Kenji the Ninja as they fight their way across the globe in order to defeat Scion the iron giant.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19961121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight /  Co-op-Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/warzard.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37426" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./warzard.7z</path>
		<name>Warzard (Japan 961121)</name>
		<desc>Red Earth take place in the year 1999 of an alternate Earth, follow the adventures of four heroes as they take on an army of mythical monsters unleashed by Scion to bring about the destruction of the world. Take your pick from Leo the Lion King, Mai-Ling the Martial artist, Tessa the Witch, or Kenji the Ninja as they fight their way across the globe in order to defeat Scion the iron giant.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19961121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight /  Co-op-Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/warzard.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="37383" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./willow.7z</path>
		<name>Willow (World)</name>
		<desc>Willow is a sideways scrolling platform shoot-em-up game loosely based upon the movie of the same name. Players take on the role of one of two characters: Willow Ufgood or Madmartigan. The hero's mission is to rescue the baby Elora Danan from the evil Queen Bavmorda and bring her back safely. If the quest fails, the Queen will plunge the world into darkness and chaos. 
 
The game consists of 6 levels, each representing a scene from the movie. Defeated enemies drop gold coins that can be collected by the player. In addition, each level is littered with locked treasure chests that can be shot open and the treasure within collected. The gold can be used to purchase a number of weapons and character power-ups from a nearby shop (represented on screen by a wise old man). All power-ups will stay with the player until all lives are lost and the game is over.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Lucasfilm Games</publisher>
		<genre>Platform / Shooter Scrolling-Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/willow.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="39873" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./1941.7z</path>
		<name>1941: Counter Attack (World 900227)</name>
		<desc>The goal is to shoot down enemy airplanes and collect weapon power-ups (POW). One is only able to perform three loops per level and a bonus is awarded at the end of the level for unused loops. Player 1 uses a P-38 Lightning and Player 2 uses a Mosquito Mk IV. The game shifts from the original Pacific Front setting with that of the Western Front.

The game consists of six levels.

It was the first shoot 'em up to add +1 to the score when a continue is used.[1]</desc>
		<image>./media/images/1941.png</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19900201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Shoot'em up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="42955" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./sectionz.7z</path>
		<name>Section Z (set 1)</name>
		<desc>As a sole astronaut, you must penetrate the alien Balangool space craft and destroy the evil 'L-Brain'. Make your way through 27 alphabet-labeled levels to find his lair. 
 
The player maneuvers the space ranger throughout the enemy space station, which consists of 26 alphabetically ordered corridors known as "sections", starting from Section A and ending at the titular Section Z. The game is divided into five stages, each consisting of five sections (with the final stage having six sections to accommodate the spare letter). The player will fight an enemy boss at the end of each stage, concluding with the final battle against the "L Brain" at Section Z. The game's stages alternates between horizontal-scrolling stage (left or right) and upwards vertical-scrolling stages. The player will lose a life every time they get hit by enemy fire. Additional lives can be obtained if the player achieves a high enough score. The game will be over if the player loses all of their lives, although a chance to continue will be provided. 
 
The controls consists of an eight-way joystick and two buttons, one for shooting and the other for changing the character's aim to the left or right. This allows the player to shoot at one direction while moving away towards the opposite. The player will shoot their rifle towards the left or the right with the fire button, while dropping bombs at the same time to the ground. By destroying certain dome-shaped containers, the player can obtain one of three power-up items represented by letters: S, P, and B. S increases the player's mobility speed, while P increases their firing power; each can improved for up to three increments. However, these power-ups will be lost whenever the player loses a life. The B item will simply give the player bonus points</desc>
		<image>./media/images/sectionz.png</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Shoot'em up / Horizontal-Shooter / Plane-Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="42982" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./sf2.7z</path>
		<name>Street Fighter II : The World Warrior (World 910522)</name>
		<desc>GET READY TO RUMBLE!

From across the globe comes eight of the wildest fighters the world has ever known. Choose your champion, gather your courage and prepare to battle your opponents in a bare knuckle brawl. Face Ken and his devastating "Dragon Punch"! Watch the temperature rise as Dhalsim incinerates you with his mystical Yoga Flame! Hear your spine crack as Zangief smashes you to the pavement with his spinning pile driver! Cover your ears as Guile breaks the sound barrier with the awesome power of the Sonic Boom!

Annihilate your competition and claim the right to test your skills against the bone-crushing power of the Grand Masters! Can you survive? Can Anyone?</desc>
		<image>./media/images/sf2.png</image>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight-Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="42986" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./sfa.7z</path>
		<name>Street Fighter Alpha: Warriors' Dreams (Euro 950727)</name>
		<desc>It's Street Fighter as you always remember it, with some new moves, characters and combo systems, as well as a more polished look and feel.

The new moves available for each fighter, called Super moves, allow them to fire off very powerful moves. A bar at the bottom of the screen represents the power that you have to use for the moves. You start the first round on 0, and each attack that you make adds power to the bar. Once you reach level 3, you can unleash the special attacks, that can sometimes KO the opponant.

The other major change over the Street Fighter 2 series are the Alpha counters. These can be used to counter an on-coming attack after blocking.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/sfzj.png</image>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight-Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="37408" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./sfa2.7z</path>
		<name>Street Fighter Alpha 2 (Euro 960229)</name>
		<desc>Street Fighter Alpha 2, known as Street Fighter Zero 2 in Japan, Asia and South America, is a 1996 fighting game originally released for the CPS II arcade hardware by Capcom. The game is both a sequel and a remake to the previous year's Street Fighter Alpha: Warriors' Dreams, which is itself a prequel to the Street Fighter II series in terms of plot and setting</desc>
		<image>./media/images/sfz2j.png</image>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus-Fight</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="37379" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./slammast.7z</path>
		<name>Saturday Night Slam Masters (World 930713)</name>
		<desc>A 1-on-1 fighting game in which players choose from 10 different wrestlers and take to the ring to try and defeat their larger-than-life opponents. Each wrestler has an assortment of moves, including his own special 'super slam'. The object of the game is to win and defend the championship by pinning or putting a submission hold on your opponent.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/slammast.png</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Wrestling-Sports</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="37419" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./xmcota.7z</path>
		<name>X-Men: Children of the Atom (Euro 950331)</name>
		<desc>X-MEN UNLEASHED! It's here! Ultimate combat! Mutant mayhem! X-Power! Special moves! Mid-air action! Big characters! Sizzling graphics! Exactly like you played in the arcade! You will need all your mutant powers, all your speed, all your strength... for this is the ultimate combat! Have you got enough to defeat Magneto, Omega Red and the Sentinel? Are you tough enough for Wolverine, powerful enough for Cyclops, cool enough for Iceman... are you good enough to join the new breed of mutant heroes? X-Men Children of the Atom - the fighting game to end them all!</desc>
		<image>./media/images/xmcota.png</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus-Fight</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="37420" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./xmvsf.7z</path>
		<name>X-Men vs. Street Fighter (Euro 961004)</name>
		<desc>X-Men vs. Street Fighter pits Marvel's mighty mutants against Capcom's legendary fighters in a slugfest of epic proportions. Now you can perform outrageous moves and link together amazing Chain Combos. X-Men vs. Street Fighter... the collision of two explosive universes in the world's most amazing fantasy fighter!</desc>
		<image>./media/images/xmvsf.png</image>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="37409" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./sfz3jr1.7z</path>
		<name>Street Fighter Zero 3 (Japan 980727)</name>
		<desc>Street Fighter Alpha 3, the third game in the Alpha series, has a total of 31 fighters, the most in the series so far. New characters include old favorites E. Honda, Blanka, Vega, Cammy, T. Hawk, Dee Jay, Juni and Juli. Some of the newest fighters on the block include a former Final Fight character (Cody, who has been in jail since the last Final Fight game, or so his clothing suggests), Karin Kanzuki and Rainbow Mika. The major difference between this Alpha and the last two are the new play modes World Tour, Arcade, VS, Training and Entry.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/sfa3.png</image>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19980101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus-Fight</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220325T141250</lastplayed>
		<gametime>107</gametime>
	</game>
	<game id="39874" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./1942.7z</path>
		<name>1942 (Revision B)</name>
		<desc>"1942" is a vertically-scrolling shoot-em-up set in the Pacific theatre during World War II, in which the goal is to reach Tokyo and destroy the entire Japanese air fleet.  
 
The player pilots a plane dubbed the "Super Ace" (its appearance is that of a Lockheed P-38 Lightning) and has to shoot down waves of enemy planes while avoiding incoming enemy fire. The 'Super Ace' can perform a limited number of rolls or 'loop-the-loops' to evade enemy planes and shots.  
 
During the game, waves of red enemy planes periodically appear. If the player manages to destroy a red wave, a power-up, in the form of a 'POW' symbol, will be dropped and can be picked up. The power-up will award either increased fire-power (doubling the player's guns from two to four), a smart bomb that destroys all on-screen enemy planes the instant it's collected, two wingmen planes that flank the Super Ace and increase fire power, or simply extra points. 
 
At the end of each stage the 'Super Ace' lands on an aircraft carrier and bonus points are awarded based on player performance. "1942" differs from other games in that its levels are numbered in reverse order, so the game begins at stage 32 and ends at stage 1.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/1942.png</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Shoot'em up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="37388" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./avsp.7z</path>
		<name>Alien VS Predator (Euro 940520)</name>
		<desc>San Drad, California, has been overrun by the Aliens, and the cybernetically-enhanced Major Dutch Schaefer and Lieutenant Linn Kurosawa have been abandoned by their superiors and are cornered by a swarm of the Alien drones. Before they can be killed, a pair of the Predators appear and destroy the Aliens. The Predators offer an alliance with the two humans in order to stop the Alien infestation.

The players take control of up to three of four characters: Dutch, Linn, a Predator hunter, and a Predator warrior, and battle the Aliens through several environments. In the process, the characters discover that the Alien presence on Earth is the result of an experiment headed by a renegade General Bush of the U.S. Colonial Marines in conjunction with the Weyland-Yutani corporation. They destroy the Alien hive by crashing a military ship into San Drad, causing a huge explosion. The Predator warrior then gives his wrist blades to Dutch and Linn in recognition of their skills as warriors, before the Predators depart back into space.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/avsp.png</image>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>3</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="0" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./sf2mix.7z</path>
		<name>Street Fighter 2 Mix</name>
		<desc>Este Jogo foi feito por fã baseado em Street Fighter 2 CE e Turbo (Arcade CPS1).
Não produzido sobre licença da Capcom.
Distribuído gratuitamente e sem fins comerciais.
Modificações no Sistema:
- Modo Versus (ao ser desafiado os 2 players podem escolher)
- Cenários Randômicos
- Cenários com uma chance de vir com movimentação de falso 3d
- Posição inicial Randômica com diferentes posições
- Os 2 últimos dígitos da pontuação marca vitórias contra outros jogadores (PVP)
- Golpes de carga com tempo menor que metade do tempo original (Honda, Blanka, Guile...)
- Golpes de apertar rápido mais fáceis de sair
- Barra de Vigor (ficar tonto, quebra de defesa, golpes especiais)
- Quebra de Defesa (G.CRUSH!)
- Defesa Perfeita: defender no último momento
- Esquiva -&gt; Start (invencível no rolamento)
- Saida de Agarrões: Cima + qualquer botão ao ser agarrado (usa 1/2 Barra de Vigor)
- Pulo Curto (pular estando totalmente parado)
- Pulo longo (rapidamente baixo -&gt; cima)
- Corrida (Frente + Frente)
- Recuar (Trás + Trás)
- Frases de Vitórias em PT-BR: Habilitar, SW(A8) CPS1 DIP Switch não utilizada

- Modo Completo: Habilitar, SW(B4) (Falso 3d, Carro na Índia, Cenários de bônus randômicos)

- Modo Clássico: Habilitar, SW(B5) (Sem Cenários randômicos contra a CPU)</desc>
		<image>./media/images/sf2mix.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/sf2mix.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./media/marquees/sf2mix.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20221201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Luta / Versus-Luta</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220408T164146</lastplayed>
		<gametime>41</gametime>
	</game>
	<game id="0" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./sfa3ud.7z</path>
		<name>Street Fighter Zero 3 Mix</name>
		<desc>O fangame Street Fighter Zero 3 Mix traz novos golpes, barra de especial, quebra de guarda, just defense, novas cores para os personagens, entre outras novidades. Este CPS2 Hack foi feito por fã baseado em SFZ3 Arcade CPS-2. Não produzido sob licença da Capcom.
		Select Screen:
Default Color	If it is in the default color each button selects a different color
Color Preview	Hold  and move cursor to change char color
Skip Selection	The winner of the previous fight can skip the selection holding the 
_________________________________________________________________________
Before Fight:
Change Order (1-2)	Hold , before the Stage is loaded
Change Order (1-3)	Hold  + , before the Stage is loaded
Invert Air Recovery	Hold , before the Stage is loaded to change Recovery mode selected
_________________________________________________________________________
In the Fight:
Short Jump	Quickly press and release the directional (ver 0.09)
First Attack	Power Level +1 (except in Zero Counter)
Provocation	 Randomly reduces a little of the opponent's Guard (except Dan)
No Air Guard	Only Just Defence can be done on air
Just Defence	 Block at the last moment (Cannot be done if you are already in the defense)
Air Recovery
	Neutral - Press  when knocked into the air
Front - Press  +  when knocked into the air
Back - Press  +  when knocked into the air
Ground Recovery	Press  or   when knocked to the floor
Tech. Hit	Perform a throw to escape as you are thrown (air)
Zero Counter Z	Block,  +  (guard-1 + Lv1)
Zero Counter V	Block,  +  +  (guard-1 + Lv1)
"Custom Combo 1	 +   (Life = 25% + Lv3)
Custom Combo 2	 +   (Life = 25% + Lv3)
Custom Combo 3	 +   (Life = 25% + Lv3)
_________________________________________________________________________
After Fight:
Life Recovery Lv1 (+08)	Hold Down + , before counting the Score
Life Recovery Lv2 (+18)	Hold Down + , before counting the Score
Life Recovery Lv3 (+28)	Hold Down + , before counting the Score</desc>
		<image>./media/images/sfz3mix.png</image>
		<video>./media/videos/sfz3mix.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./media/marquees/sfz3mix.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20221201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Luta / Versus-Luta</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220408T165310</lastplayed>
		<gametime>674</gametime>
	</game>
	<game id="42981" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./sf.7z</path>
		<name>Street Fighter (US, set 1)</name>
		<desc>Martial arts masters Ryu and Ken enter a worldwide martial arts tournament spanning 5 nations as they face 10 of the world's greatest fighters. The game can be played alone or with 2 players competing, with Player 1 taking the role of Ryu and Player 2 as Ken. The predecessor to the ultra-popular "Street Fighter II - The World Warrior".</desc>
		<image>./media/images/sf.png</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus-Fight</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220712T124601</lastplayed>
		<gametime>23</gametime>
	</game>
	<game id="37409" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./sfa3.7z</path>
		<name>Street Fighter Alpha 3 (Euro 980904)</name>
		<desc>Street Fighter Alpha 3, the third game in the Alpha series, has a total of 31 fighters, the most in the series so far. New characters include old favorites E. Honda, Blanka, Vega, Cammy, T. Hawk, Dee Jay, Juni and Juli. Some of the newest fighters on the block include a former Final Fight character (Cody, who has been in jail since the last Final Fight game, or so his clothing suggests), Karin Kanzuki and Rainbow Mika. The major difference between this Alpha and the last two are the new play modes World Tour, Arcade, VS, Training and Entry.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/sfa3.png</image>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19980101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus-Fight</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>17</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20141231T180256</lastplayed>
		<gametime>1972</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="39875" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./1943.7z</path>
		<name>1943: The Battle of Midway (Euro)</name>
		<desc>The game is set in the Pacific theater of World War II, off the coast of the Midway Atoll. The goal is to attack the Japanese Air Fleet that bombed the players' American Aircraft Carrier, pursue all Japanese Air and Sea forces, fly through the 16 levels of play, make their way to the Japanese battleship Yamato and destroy her. 11 Levels consist of an Air-to-Sea battle (with a huge battleship or an aircraft carrier as an End-Level Boss), while 5 levels consist of an all-aerial battle against a squadron of Japanese Bombers and a Mother Bomber that needs to be destroyed.
As in 1942, players pilot a P-38. Two buttons are used: one for regular attacks (with several weapons) and one for special actions that executes either a loop like in 1942 or one of three special attacks that damage the plane. Unlike 1942, the player only has one life, with one refillable energy meter. Destroying a complete formation of red enemy planes will result in a power-up, such as a health boost or a temporary special weapons which replaces the default twin gun.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/1943.png</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Shoot'em up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220810T160406</lastplayed>
		<gametime>20</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="39876" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./1943kai.7z</path>
		<name>1943 Kai: Midway Kaisen (Japan)</name>
		<desc>An update of 1943 with tweaked weapons, fewer levels, and a new soundtrack.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/1943kai.png</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Shoot'em up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220810T160341</lastplayed>
		<gametime>18</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="37386" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./19xx.7z</path>
		<name>19XX : The War Against Destiny (USA 951207)</name>
		<desc>19XX: The War Against Destiny is a vertical scrolling shooter arcade game made by Capcom in 1995 (copyrighted in 1996). The game is the 4th of a series of World War II vertical shooters made by Capcom. The story takes place before a fictional war (Hence, the 19XX) as a lone pilot tries to defeat an entire army/evil organization from starting another World War, which soon escalates to a nuclear apocalypse.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/19xx.png</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Shoot'em up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220810T160255</lastplayed>
		<gametime>3149</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="37385" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./1944.7z</path>
		<name>1944 : The Loop Master (USA 000620)</name>
		<desc>The game takes place in the heated battles of 1944 during the Second World War as a super ace pilot attempts to defeat an entire army. The game operates and plays like most standard shooters. The objective of every level is to shoot enemy planes, tanks, trains, turrets, battleships, and defeat the boss after each level. Unlike its predecessor, 19XX: The War Against Destiny, the game plays more like the early games in the series.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/1944.png</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Shoot'em up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220810T162828</lastplayed>
		<gametime>572</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="37387" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./armwar.7z</path>
		<name>Armored Warriors (Euro 941024)</name>
		<desc>In the year 2281, the war spanning half a century over territory between the United World Forces and the Raian Kingdom had at last come to an end.

But this peace was not to last. A year after a truce was signed between the two forces, former Raian army captain Azrael, who has converted himself into a cyborg in an attempt to become "the perfect warrior", has marshalled several thousand other cyborgs and declared war against the Raian Kingdom. Robbing mobile weapons from the army, this group of rogues has invaded the Raian capital of Merkid and has begun to abduct the civilians.

The United World Government, receiving an emergency message from the planet Raia, has but one choice: to organize and dispatch an army formed around its elite corps, a squadron of warriors called "Bloody Armor", to eradicate the enemy forces and rescue the civilians.

And so, in October 2282, the United World Forces begin to launch its attack upon the planet Raia.

The most intense battle in human history is about to begin...</desc>
		<image>./media/images/armwar.png</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>3</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220810T162912</lastplayed>
		<gametime>32</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="40115" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./avengers.7z</path>
		<name>Avengers (US set 1)</name>
		<desc>Avenger takes place in Paradise City, where the villain, "Geshita", has captured six girls from the city. The player's objective (as Ryu or Ko) is to banish "Geshita" from Paradise City once and for all. During the game, the player can pick up powerups like the "Speed Up", the Super Punch, Grenades, Shurikens, Nunchaku and extra health.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/avengers.png</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Vertical-Fight</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220810T162954</lastplayed>
		<gametime>29</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="37389" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./batcir.7z</path>
		<name>Battle Circuit (Euro 970319)</name>
		<desc>Battle Circuit take place in an alternate future earth, the game revolves around a group of bounty hunters who must capture the mad scientist Doctor Saturn and secure a sophisticated computer disc carrying a program known as the "Shiva System". Battle Circuit, which was Capcom's last beat 'em game for the arcades, contains comic-like characters in a futuristic science fiction setting and is considered by some to be a cult classic.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/batcir.png</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220810T163029</lastplayed>
		<gametime>31</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="150942" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./bionicc.7z</path>
		<name>Bionic Commando (Euro)</name>
		<desc>Bionic Commando is a scrolling platform shoot-em-up set ten years after the end of World War III, with the player taking on the role of 'Super Joe'; an elite Commando tasked with infiltrating the enemy's heavily defended military base to discover their secrets plans and destroy their missile silos.  
 
To aid him in his mission, Joe is equipped with a bionic arm; a telescopic grappling hook that is used to traverse the many platforms and ledges that make up the game's levels. The arm can also be used to temporarily stun enemies or knock them from platforms, as well as to retrieve the bonus items, wooden crates and weapons that are occasionally dropped into the war zone by parachute.  
 
As well as the bionic arm, Joe is armed with a shotgun used to kill enemies and destroy obstructions. The shotgun can only be fired left and right, however, and cannot be used at the same time as the bionic arm. More powerful guns can be picked up throughout the game.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/bionicc.png</image>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform / Shooter Scrolling-Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220810T163413</lastplayed>
		<gametime>20</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="40270" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./blktiger.7z</path>
		<name>Black Tiger</name>
		<desc>Black Dragon/Tiger is a scrolling platform shoot-em-up set in a fantasy world and is the spiritual successor to the Capcom classic, "Makaimura" ("Ghosts'n' Goblins" outside Japan). 
 
The player takes on the role of a barbarian hero who must jump and fight his way through a variety of colourful, enemy-packed levels, collecting treasure and weapon power-ups and rescuing the trapped 'wise old men' that litter the levels.  
 
Rescuing the wise men sees the player awarded 'Zeny coins'; these are the game's currency and allow the player to buy such items as weapon and armour upgrades, keys for treasure chests, anti-poisoning potions and health potions from the shops that appear on each level. Occasionally, a rescued wise man will also offer to sell the player weapon and armour power-ups.  
 
The barbarian hero is armed with a spiked mace on the end of a long chain, as well as unlimited throwing daggers. Both these and the armour worn by the barbarian (which offers limited protection from enemy attacks) can be upgraded by finding or buying the relevant power-ups. 
 
The sprawling, eight-way scrolling levels are packed with hidden bonuses to encourage and reward exploration. These bonuses are in the form of weapon and armour power-ups, as well as valuable treasure items. Many levels also include a hidden dungeon and each dungeon is filled with both bonus items and trapped wise men. 
 
Special items that reveal coins, upgraded armour, or simply bonus points can be found by attacking certain walls.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/blktiger.png</image>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform / Fighter Scrolling-Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220810T163434</lastplayed>
		<gametime>18</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="40273" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./block.7z</path>
		<name>Block Block (World 911219 Joystick)</name>
		<desc>A ball travels across the screen, bouncing off the top and side walls of the screen. When a brick is hit, the ball bounces away and the brick is destroyed. The player loses a turn when the ball touches the bottom of the screen. To prevent this from happening, the player has a movable paddle to bounce the ball upward and back into play.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/block.png</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Breakout games-Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220810T163631</lastplayed>
		<gametime>18</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="37358" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./captcomm.7z</path>
		<name>Captain Commando (World 911202)</name>
		<desc>Captain Commando is set in a crime-ridden future in the year 2026, where a superhero named Captain Commando, assisted by his three faithful Commando Companions rise up to protect the Earth and all the Galaxy from a gang of super-powered criminals.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/captcomm.png</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220810T164058</lastplayed>
		<gametime>207</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="37359" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./cawing.7z</path>
		<name>Carrier Air Wing (World 901012)</name>
		<desc>Carrier Air Wing / U.S. Navy is a horizontally-scrolling shoot-em-up for one or two players set in the 1990s, a decade of great change marked by growing friendships between old enemies and never before seen levels of co-operation between powerful nations of the world. However, in 1997, using new weapons designed in secrecy, the Middle Eastern country of 'Rabu' threatens to destroy this new and fragile peace.  
 
Players chose to pilot any one of three different jet fighters and must battle their way through ten enemy-packed stages. Each fighter has a fuel bar which is full at the start of each stage but gradually decreases, additional fuel is lost each time the fighter takes damage from an enemy.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/cawing.png</image>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Shoot'em up / Horizontal</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220810T164125</lastplayed>
		<gametime>24</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="40660" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./commando.7z</path>
		<name>Commando (World)</name>
		<desc>Commando is a vertically scrolling shoot'em up in which the player takes on the role of a highly trained commando soldier called "Super Joe", who starts the game by being dropped off in a jungle by a helicopter.  
 
Joe's mission is to rescue captives and destroy the enemy bases and strongholds that appear at the end of each level, killing as many enemy soldiers as possible in the process.  
 
The end-of-level strongholds see waves of enemy soldiers ordered to attack by a cowardly officer, who immediately runs away. Shooting the fleeing officer earns the player bonus points. Along the way, players can attempt to free prisoners-of-war by shooting their enemy guard escorts as they are transported across the screen. 
 
Super Joe carries only two weapons: a limited-range machine gun with unlimited shots, and a limited supply of hand grenades. Extra grenades can be picked up as the player progresses through the levels.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/commando.png</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / Run and Gun-Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220810T164237</lastplayed>
		<gametime>54</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="37390" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./csclub.7z</path>
		<name>Capcom Sports Club (Euro 971017)</name>
		<desc>Capcom Sports Club is an arcade game released by Capcom in 1997. It is a multi-sport game that consists of Smash Stars (Tennis), Dunk Stars (Basketball), and Kick Stars (Football/Soccer).</desc>
		<image>./media/images/csclub.png</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Compilation-Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220810T163722</lastplayed>
		<gametime>18</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="37391" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./cybots.7z</path>
		<name>Cyberbots : Fullmetal Madness (Euro 950424)</name>
		<desc>Near the end of the 21st century, Earth begins to become overpopulated, leading to many people living in man-made space colonies. The primary army of Earth called "Earth Corps", has been conducting nefarious experiments and their work, along with the actions of the playable characters, will determine Earth's future.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/cybots.png</image>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus-Fight</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220810T164423</lastplayed>
		<gametime>31</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="37360" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./dino.7z</path>
		<name>Cadillacs and Dinosaurs (World 930201)</name>
		<desc>Cadillacs and Dinosaurs: The Arcade Game, known in Japan as Cadillacs: Dinosaurs of a New Century is a 1993 arcade game released by Capcom. It is a side-scrolling beat 'em up based on the comic book series Xenozoic Tales. The game was produced as a tie-in to the Cadillacs and Dinosaurs animated series which was aired during the same year the game was released.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/dino.png</image>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>3</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220810T163654</lastplayed>
		<gametime>45</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="37392" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./ddsom.7z</path>
		<name>Dungeons &amp; Dragons: Shadow over Mystara (Euro 960619)</name>
		<desc>Dungeons &amp; Dragons: Shadow over Mystara is an arcade game developed and published by Capcom in 1996 as a sequel to Dungeons &amp; Dragons: Tower of Doom. It was also released on the Sega Saturn, packaged with Tower of Doom, under the title Dungeons &amp; Dragons Collection. The game is set in the Dungeons &amp; Dragons campaign setting of Mystara. It was one of the last 2-D arcade side-scrollers created by Capcom; only Battle Circuit (1997) came after Shadow over Mystara.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/ddsom.png</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19960619T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220810T165010</lastplayed>
		<gametime>47</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="37393" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./ddtod.7z</path>
		<name>Dungeons &amp; Dragons: Tower of Doom (Euro 940412)</name>
		<desc>Dungeons &amp; Dragons: Tower of Doom is the first of two video games created by Capcom based on the Dungeons &amp; Dragons tabletop role-playing game. The game was also released on the Sega Saturn, packaged with its sequel, Dungeons &amp; Dragons: Shadow over Mystara, under the title Dungeons &amp; Dragons Collection, although the Saturn version limited the gameplay to only 2 players. The game is set in the Mystara campaign setting.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/ddtod.png</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220810T165100</lastplayed>
		<gametime>47</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="37394" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./dimahoo.7z</path>
		<name>Dimahoo (000121 USA)</name>
		<desc>The game is set in a futuristic environment with dragons, little turtles with lasers on their back, and little green goblins with red eyes. The player picks one of four friends to travel with. The two characters fly through the levels in the game and collect items. Each item has a point value and the points are used to fill up a chart at the end. The items include: food, swords, armors, boots, etc. Towards the end of the game, the bosses become incredibly hard. The fast backgrounds create a confusing state of mind for the player.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/dimahoo.png</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Raizing</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Shoot'em up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220810T164917</lastplayed>
		<gametime>24</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="41078" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./dynwar.7z</path>
		<name>Dynasty Wars (USA, B-Board 89624B-?)</name>
		<desc>This game is a side-scrolling beat-em-up based on Japanese manga books of the same name and is a re-enactment of the historical battles between the Kingdom of Shu and the Yellow Turban rebels. Up to two players assume the roles of one of the four Chinese generals riding on horseback whose goal is to wipe out the 'Huang Ching', the organization responsible for the unrest of the Han Dynasty, and to eventually defeat the tyrant, Dong Zhuo.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/dynwar.png</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220810T165124</lastplayed>
		<gametime>19</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="37395" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./ecofghtr.7z</path>
		<name>Eco Fighters (World 931203)</name>
		<desc>Eco Fighters is a horizontal shooter, where the player controls a ship with a rotating gun. As suggested by both its titles, the game has an "eco-friendly" theme. It was also developed by the same team from two Mega Man arcade titles, The Power Battle and The Power Fighters.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/ecofghtr.png</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Shoot'em up / Horizontal</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220810T165201</lastplayed>
		<gametime>33</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="41136" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./exedexes.7z</path>
		<name>Exed Exes</name>
		<desc>Exed Exes is an arcade vertical shooter developed by Capcom. It was licensed to Memetron and released outside of Japan in the arcades as Savage Bees Memetron (licensor to the game). It uses similar hardware to Capcom's 1942, but it is more of a spiritual successor to Capcom's earlier shooter Vulgus. It takes place in a science fiction alien hive where you must pilot your ship through many stages protected by insects, some as large as your craft, and some even larger. 
 
What made Exed Exes stand apart from other shooters, besides the high resolution graphics for its time, and the detailed use of parallax scrolling to indicate depth, was the fact that it was one of the earliest vertical shooters to allow for two player simultaneous play. Rather than waiting for one player to take his turn, two players could enjoy the game at the same time, and even work cooperatively to get further along in the game.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/exedexes.png</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Shoot'em up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220810T165224</lastplayed>
		<gametime>19</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="41148" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./f1dream.7z</path>
		<name>F-1 Dream</name>
		<desc>You take the role of a newcomer race driver. Beginning in the Formula 3000, you will have to prove yourself worthy of being promoted to Formula 1 and challenge the best drivers of the late eighties. 
 
F-1 Dream is not one of Capcom's best known games. From a top-down perspective and decorated with cute "deformed" graphics, it may offer a serious challenge. There are essentially two race instances: first you have to beat the clock in a single lap to qualify for a good position in the race, and second you have to beat your opponents. You also have to keep an eye on your car's condition, as the tyres and body wear out, so part of your strategy must consider pit stops. 
 
Despite its looks, F-1 Dream is not a parody game. Released in 1988, it's in fact very respectful towards the sport, featuring little details which add realism to it. This includes several real brands advertised in the game, and others which have one or two letters changed in the logo, but are very easy to recognize. So it is with your opponents, featuring the great Ayrton Senna, Alain Prost or Nigel Mansell. The car behavior also features skids when speeding at corners, gears, and damage.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/f1dream.png</image>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving / Race-Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="41441" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./ghouls.7z</path>
		<name>Ghouls'n Ghosts (World)</name>
		<desc>Three years have passed since the events of "Ghosts'n Goblins" and the knight Arthur finds himself once again facing the horrible creatures of Demon World. This time the demons have invaded the kingdom and upon his return, Arthur is the only survivor, his beloved Genever having been killed by Lucifer. Arthur embarks once again on a quest to defeat the demonic invaders and save Genever's soul.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/ghouls.png</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Platform / Fighter Scrolling</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="41446" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./gigawing.7z</path>
		<name>Giga Wing (USA 990222)</name>
		<desc>'Medallions' are mystic stones sent from heaven, brought evolution to human technology and lead tremendous progress to the armories. To gain their powers which the 'Stones' hold for the promised victory, many nations fought over the mystic stones and reheated the world of war. Within all the 'Stones' is the 'Medallion of Wisdom', known as the power source of all mystic stones, it had enough energy to terminate humanity. The whole world was in despair. And now, four brave worriers have risen to fly straight into the combat zone! All four had different reasons, but their ultimate goal was the same: to destroy the Medallion of Wisdom! Fight to save the humanity! 
 
Giga Wing is a shoot-em-up set during a fictional war. The player controls one of four different futuristic aircraft and must destroy enemy aircraft, tanks, ships, and buildings using both guns and missiles mounted on the aircraft and a limited supply of bombs which damage or destroy all enemies on-screen when used.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/gigawing.png</image>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19990101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Takumi</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Shoot'em up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="41596" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./gunsmoke.7z</path>
		<name>Gun.Smoke (World, 851115)</name>
		<desc>Gun.Smoke is a vertically-scrolling shoot-em-up set in the Wild West, in which the player takes the role of a Billy; a young Sheriff charged with hunting down and killing a number of infamous 'Wanted' outlaws. 
 
Each level is packed with gun-toting bandits and the Sheriff must shoot his way through the stage, before finally taking on the wanted outlaw 'boss' character at the end. Each outlaw wields a special weapon unique to them, such as a Winchester rifle, knives, darts or boomerangs. 
 
Shooting the barrels that litter the levels reveals power-ups such as boots (for extra speed), rifles (for increased range) and bullets (for rapid fire). The game's 3 directional fire buttons (for firing left, right or ahead) can be combined (pressed Simultaneously) to create a total of 8 different firing directions.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/gunsmoke.png</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / Run and Gun-Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="149430" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./hsf2.7z</path>
		<name>Hyper Street Fighter II: The Anniversary Edition (USA 040202)</name>
		<desc>Hyper Street Fighter II: The Anniversary Edition is a competitive fighting game by Capcom that was originally released for the PlayStation 2 in 2003 in Japan and in 2004 in North America and Asia. Released to commemorate the 15th anniversary of the Street Fighter series, Hyper Street Fighter II is a modified port of Super Street Fighter II Turbo in which players can control any versions of the main characters from the five Street Fighter II games previously released for the arcades. Although, originally released as a home console game, an arcade port was released shortly afterwards in limited quantities, turning it into the sixth and final arcade iteration.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/hsf2.png</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20031201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight / Versus-Fight</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="37422" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./jojo.7z</path>
		<name>JoJo's Venture (Euro 990128)</name>
		<desc>JoJo's Venture is a 2D fighting game based off of the hit Japanese manga series JoJo's Bizarre Adventure (famous for over-the-top violence, an intricate plot, and numerous Western rock music references).</desc>
		<image>./media/images/jojo.png</image>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19980101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight-Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220810T170602</lastplayed>
		<gametime>34</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="37421" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./jojobaner1.7z</path>
		<name>JoJo's Bizarre Adventure (Euro 990913)</name>
		<desc>Based on the Japanese manga/animé of the same name, JoJo's Bizarre Adventure is a 2D fighting game from Capcom. Take on the role of one of 18 characters and compete with your friends or take on the role of Jotaro "JoJo" Kujo and his friends in the SUper Story Mode as they race to defeat the evil vampire, Dio Brando, and save the world!</desc>
		<image>./media/images/jojobaner1.png</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight-Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220810T170758</lastplayed>
		<gametime>111</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="42020" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./knights.7z</path>
		<name>Knights of the Round (World 911127)</name>
		<desc>Knights of the Round is an arcade game released by Capcom in 1991. A side-scrolling beat 'em up based loosely on the legend of King Arthur and the Knights of the Round Table, the game features an role-playing video game-like level advancement system, with fighters getting new weapons and armour as they advance through the game, however the player can not choose how to upgrade his/her character - the level up system is static.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/knights.png</image>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>3</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220811T062715</lastplayed>
		<gametime>60</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="42109" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./lastduel.7z</path>
		<name>Last Duel (US New Ver.)</name>
		<desc>Last Duel - Inter Planet War 2012 take place in the year 2012 in an alternate galaxy, Last Duel involves the struggle between two planets Mu and Bacula. On planet Bacula, a strong warrior tribe known as the Galden rose to immense military power and conquered all of the societies on the planet. Unsatisfied with conquering just one planet, the Galden decided to conquer a neighboring terrestrial planet, Mu. Using advanced bioships, star fighters, and motor vehicles, the Galden invaded Mu, destroying many of its cities and taking the planet's ruler Queen Sheeta hostage. The remaining royal guards of Mu are deployed in space fighters that can transform into cars to rescue the queen and crush the Galden forces. 
 
The player alternates each level between using car and space ship. The vehicle has two main attacks one of which varies depending on the form the vehicle took. In car mode, the vehicle can jump over pot holes and enemies. While in ship mode, the vehicle can perform a barrel roll, making it temporarily invincible. 
 
The player can select Power-Ups that including a large, slow firing laser, a twin-shot, a wide shot and options that provided side attacks. Speed-Ups were only available in ship mode. Every driving section is timed and if the player is unable to reach the boss on time, they will lose a life. However, the moment the player encounters the boss, the timer will be removed.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/lastduel.png</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / Vehicle, Vertical-Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220811T062749</lastplayed>
		<gametime>24</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="42360" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./ledstorm.7z</path>
		<name>Led Storm (US)</name>
		<desc>By 2011, the only way to travel at top speed is on skyways build high above the ground. These become popular with boy-racers and general speed freaks pretty soon, and that's why you're aiming to hurtle across them in this arcade conversion. 
 
The road scrolls vertically, with some moderately sharp bends in a manner similar to Spy Hunter You have a jump device to clear the many jumps, or to land onto and flatten the other maniacs who line the road. You must choose which path to follow at OutRun-style forks in the road.  
 
The roads contain bonus tags including bonus points, a battering ram to make contact with other cars more effective, and energy boosts to replenish damage. If you leave the road you must replace your car onto it using a directable winch which appears at the appropriate point.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/ledstorm.png</image>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving / Race-Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="42360" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./madgear.7z</path>
		<name>Mad Gear (US)</name>
		<desc>By 2011, the only way to travel at top speed is on skyways build high above the ground. These become popular with boy-racers and general speed freaks pretty soon, and that's why you're aiming to hurtle across them in this arcade conversion. 
 
The road scrolls vertically, with some moderately sharp bends in a manner similar to Spy Hunter You have a jump device to clear the many jumps, or to land onto and flatten the other maniacs who line the road. You must choose which path to follow at OutRun-style forks in the road.  
 
The roads contain bonus tags including bonus points, a battering ram to make contact with other cars more effective, and energy boosts to replenish damage. If you leave the road you must replace your car onto it using a directable winch which appears at the appropriate point.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/ledstorm.png</image>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving / Race-Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="43837" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./area88.7z</path>
		<name>Area 88 (Japan)</name>
		<desc>U.N. Squadron / Area 88 is a horizontally-scrolling shoot-em-up and is based on the Manga series of the same name. The game features characters from the original Manga and their mission is to battle their way through enemy-packed levels to stop a terrorist group known as 'Project 4'.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/area88.png</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Shoot'em up / Horizontal</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="41049" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./dstlk.7z</path>
		<name>Darkstalkers: The Night Warriors (Euro 940705)</name>
		<desc>People tremble in fear of these monsters. A mysterious force awakens them from their long slumber. 'Arise and show your fangs!' The silence of the night is broken by the growls and roars of these evil spirits which have been summoned from beyond. They are coming... tonight! DarkStalkers - the warriors of the night! 
 
DarkStalkers features spectacular fighting between supernatural monsters with 4 TIMES the graphics of SFII (its 15,000 animation patterns put it way out in front of SSFII Turbo, resulting in realistic movement with smooth animation). With endless playability you'll never tire of, make sport of your opponent with incredible moves like the Special Attack and Death Blow which are humanly impossible. We're talking about unlimited varieties of attack! 
 
The unimaginable secret power of the dark is unleashed!</desc>
		<image>./media/images/dstlk.png</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight-Fight / Versus</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="37362" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./ffight.7z</path>
		<name>Final Fight (World, set 1)</name>
		<desc>Final Fight can be played by up to two players simultaneously, with each player controlling a different character. Before the game begins, the player chooses between the three main characters, Guy, Cody, and Haggar, each with his own fighting style and attributes. Guy is the weakest but has faster attacks, Haggar is the strongest but also the slowest, and Cody has all-round attributes.

Final Fight consists of six stages or "rounds", as well as two bonus rounds. Each round takes place in a different section of Metro City such as the Slums and the Subway, with most rounds featuring more than one level. At the end of each round the player will face a boss character unique to that round.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/ffight.png</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
	<game id="0" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./ffightae.7z</path>
		<name>Final Fight 30th Anniversary Edition</name>
		<desc>Final Fight can be played by up to two players simultaneously, with each player controlling a different character. Before the game begins, the player chooses between the three main characters, Guy, Cody, and Haggar, each with his own fighting style and attributes. Guy is the weakest but has faster attacks, Haggar is the strongest but also the slowest, and Cody has all-round attributes.

Final Fight consists of six stages or "rounds", as well as two bonus rounds. Each round takes place in a different section of Metro City such as the Slums and the Subway, with most rounds featuring more than one level. At the end of each round the player will face a boss character unique to that round.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/ffightae.png</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
		<region>us</region>
	</game>
</gameList>
