<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game id="3869" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./007 - NightFire (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De).7z</path>
		<name>007 : Nightfire</name>
		<desc>The ultimate secret agent is back in his most dangerous adventure yet in James Bond 007: NightFire. Explore new heights and depths like never before -- infiltrate towering skyscrapers, take on treacherous underwater missions, and tackle original missions including assignments in outer space. All this plus glamorous (and sometimes deadly) Bond women, new state-of-the-art gadgets and weapons, and an advanced in-game camera system will leave you shaken and stirred.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20030402T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>JV Games</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter-Shooter / 1st person-Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/007 - NightFire (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4595" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./All-Star Baseball 2004 (USA).7z</path>
		<name>All-Star Baseball 2004 Featuring Derek Jeter</name>
		<desc>Like Derek Jeter, All-Star Baseball 2004 is the game "with all the tools." With the most realistic simulation ever, easier to play functionality, and the same all around skill set that makes Derek the leader and winner he is, ASB 2004 truly is the game with all the tools.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20030226T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Acclaim</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Baseball-Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/All-Star Baseball 2004 (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4139" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Altered Beast - Guardian of the Realms (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Altered Beast : Guardian of the Realms</name>
		<desc>Zeus, creator and ruler of the Guardians of the Gates, raises you from your grave! You must go fourth and defeat a new, unknown evil that has destroyed the Guardians and ravaged the universe. To do so, you must collect the keys and Essence of each land, transforming you into beasts with unnatural powers and special abilities. Conquer this evil and you will become the sole Guardian, the protector of the universe.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20021125T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>THQ</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up-Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/Altered Beast - Guardian of the Realms (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="97398" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Anguna (Nathan Tolbert and Chris Hildenbrand).7z</path>
		<name>Anguna - Warriors Of Virtue</name>
		<desc>It is a short but exciting action-adventure game, reminiscent of the original Legend of Zelda. 
Anguna includes: 5 dungeons and a large overworld to explore, Multiple weapons and items including: a sword, bow &amp; arrows, bear traps, dynamite, lantern, magic boots, and more, Many hidden rooms, secrets, and powerups, Lots of interesting enemies and boss monsters 
</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20080101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nathan Tolbert and Chris Hildenbrand</developer>
		<publisher>Nathan Tolbert</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Anguna (Nathan Tolbert and Chris Hildenbrand).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="83155" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Army Men - Turf Wars (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Army Men : Turf Wars</name>
		<desc>Colonel Grimm has ordered the defeat of the Tan Army and chosen a two-man Special Forces team for the mission. This Special Forces team will consist of the Blue Spy and you, Sgt. Hawk. Battle through several different backyard environments with the ultimate goal of destroying the Tan Army. Good luck, soldier!</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20020929T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mobius Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>3DO</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Shoot'em up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Army Men - Turf Wars (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4303" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Army Men Advance (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).7z</path>
		<name>Army Men Advance</name>
		<desc>Plastro, the infamous leader of the Tan Army, has recruited alien forces from another world to aid in his ongoing war against the Green Nation. It's up to Sarge and Vikki G. to jump into action to save their troops from a variety of unknown enemies, and then track down Plastro himself for a final confrontation!</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20010610T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Panasonic</developer>
		<publisher>DC Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Shoot'em up / Vertical-Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Army Men Advance (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3906" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Avatar - The Last Airbender - The Burning Earth (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Avatar : The Last Airbender - The Burning Earth</name>
		<desc>Avatar: The Burning Earth continues the epic adventure of Aang and his courageous fight against the evil Fire Nation in order to restore balance in his war-torn world. Based on the second season of the Avatar animated series, players will join Aang and his friends as they master their skills and fight their way to defend the greatest Earth Kingdom city against a deadly Fire Nation invasion.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20071016T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>THQ</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Action / Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Avatar - The Last Airbender - The Burning Earth (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3914" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Banjo-Kazooie - Grunty's Revenge (USA, Europe).7z</path>
		<name>Banjo-Kazooie: Grunty's Revenge</name>
		<desc>Gruntilda is back, and it's up to Banjo and Kazooie to stop her master plan. In Banjo-Kazooie: Grunty's Revenge, you'll play as Banjo and follow him through six worlds rife with trials and contests. Some of the challenges you must overcome include solving puzzles, avoiding obstacles, and battling different enemies. Defeat your foes by using Banjo's array of combat moves. You can also seek help from witch doctors, who can transform Banjo into a mouse, a tank, and other creatures.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20031107T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Banjo-Kazooie - Grunty's Revenge (USA, Europe).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4209" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Batman - Rise of Sin Tzu (USA) (En,Fr,Es).7z</path>
		<name>Batman : Rise of Sin Tzu</name>
		<desc>In Batman: Rise of Sin Tzu, Batman faces a new enemy unlike any he has ever faced before. The faceless foe plunges Gotham City into chaos on the night of the anniversary of Bruce Wayne's parents' murder. Who is responsible for unleashing havoc on Gotham City? The truth will be revealed after you battle evil forces and super-villains, including Bane, Clayface, Scarecrow, and the new formidable foe--Sin Tzu. In addition to Batman's martial arts attacks, Batman has an arsenal including the Batarang, Grappling Hook, and Smoke Bomb.</desc>
		<rating>0.3</rating>
		<releasedate>20031014T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Platform / Fighter Scrolling-Action-Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Batman - Rise of Sin Tzu (USA) (En,Fr,Es).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3999" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Batman - Vengeance (USA) (En,Fr,Es).7z</path>
		<name>Batman : Vengeance</name>
		<desc>The gritty underworld of Gotham City ignites as Batman becomes the target of a nerve-rattling conspiracy. After the Joker plummets to his death in an attempt to kill Batman, Gotham's criminals quickly escalate their schemes to gain power. Batman discovers subtle links in these seemingly unrelated crimes, but is forced undercover after being framed for an attack on Commissioner Gordon. Hunted by the police, the Dark Knight must pinpoint the unseen enemy weaving this sinister web - before Gotham City falls to a fiery demise.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20011030T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action-Action / Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Batman - Vengeance (USA) (En,Fr,Es).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4327" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Blackthorne (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Blackthorne</name>
		<desc>Blackthorne is an action-adventure game that takes place on the planet Tuul. Tuul was a peaceful place, until the evil warrior Sarlac used the power of the Darkstone to take control.  Blackthorne's father, the good King Vlaros, sent him to Earth just as his kingdom crumbled around him.  Now, 20 years later, Blackthorne is grown and must return to Tuul to free it from the clutches of Sarlac.

This game is played from a side-view with non-scrolling backgrounds. It has strong similarities to Prince of Persia, except you battle your foes using guns and bombs instead of a sword.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20030919T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mass Media</developer>
		<publisher>Blizzard Classic Arcade</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action-Various</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Blackthorne (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4150" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Bomberman Max 2 - Blue Advance (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Bomberman Max 2 : Blue Advance</name>
		<desc>Bomberman and Max have been shrunk to the size of an ant by the evil Mujie's secret weapon. Work together with max to find and destroy the device before Mujoe can take control of the universe. And so the newest adventures of Bomberman begins!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20020530T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Vivendi Universal Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Action / Labyrinth-Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Bomberman Max 2 - Blue Advance (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4293" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Bomberman Max 2 - Red Advance (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Bomberman Max 2 : Red Advance</name>
		<desc>Bomberman again teams up with Max to take on the evil Mujoe. But before they get the chance, Mujoe turns the tables, shrinking the heroes into tiny critters. Now the two must use their bombing powers and traverse the levels, blowing up obstacles and enemies to get to the exit, to eventually destroy the device and return themselves to normal size.

As with all previous Bomberman title, the aim of the game is to plant bombs, destroying anything that come within the boundaries of the blast. Charabomb characters can be collected during play to increase your powers, or you battle and trade them with a friend in link mode.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20020530T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Vivendi Universal Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Action / Labyrinth-Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Bomberman Max 2 - Red Advance (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3912" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Bomberman Tournament (USA, Europe).7z</path>
		<name>Bomberman Tournament</name>
		<desc>An S.O.S. from the cosmos signals that planet Phantarion is in trouble! Grab your arsenal and get ready for non-stop action as you blast your way through interactive battlefields and take on up to 4 real-time players. Battle opponents through 8 interactive battlefield mazes! Take on up to 4 players in multi-player blastfests! Fast, furious, explosive bombing adventure!</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20010626T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Bomberman Tournament (USA, Europe).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4370" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Capcom Classics Mini Mix (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Capcom Classics Mini Mix</name>
		<desc>An action-packed compilation of three of Capcom's most popular titles, originally released for the Nintendo Entertainment System. The trio of old school action titles includes "Bionic Commando," "Strider" and "Mighty Final Fight," all faithfully recreated and available to play in either the original aspect ratio or stretched to fill the handheld's widescreen display.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20060919T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sensory Sweep Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Compilation-Fight</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Capcom Classics Mini Mix (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4196" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Casper (USA) (En,Fr,Es).7z</path>
		<name>Casper</name>
		<desc>Game Boy Advance adaption of the kid-friendly cartoon series. Players slip into the role of Casper as he goes toe-to-toe with the mean ghosts Stretch, Stinkie, and Fatso. The evil trio is attempting to transform all the towns people into zombies -- a fate that the friendly ghost cannot and will not tolerate. Players explore six different levels of spooky fun in this adventure-filled quest for young players.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20020302T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Planet Interactive Development</developer>
		<publisher>Microïds</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Puzzle-Game-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Casper (USA) (En,Fr,Es).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3776" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Castlevania - Aria of Sorrow (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Castlevania : Aria of Sorrow</name>
		<desc>The year is 2035 and Soma Cruz is about to witness the first solar eclipse of the 21st century when he suddenly blacks out -- only to awaken inside a mysterious castle. As Soma, you must navigate the castle's labyrinths while confronting perilous monsters at every turn. But beware, you must escape before the evil consumes you!</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20030506T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Action / Adventure-Fight</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Castlevania - Aria of Sorrow (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3780" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Castlevania - Circle of the Moon (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Castlevania : Circle of the Moon</name>
		<desc>The year is 1830. At an old Austrian castle, the worshipers of Chaos attempted to revive the Lord of Darkness, Count Dracula. Vampire Hunter Morris Baldwin and his apprentices, Nathan Graves and Hugh Baldwin, heard of this and headed to Castlevania to stop Count Dracula's resurrection and restoration of power. However, they arrived a few seconds too late and Camilla, a minion of Count Dracula, started the rite to revive her master. 
Now it is up to you to fight your way through various monsters, and Dracula's minions, in order to defeat the Lord of Darkness!</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20010611T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Adventure-Action-Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Castlevania - Circle of the Moon (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3798" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Castlevania - Harmony of Dissonance (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Castlevania : Harmony of Dissonance</name>
		<desc>Nearly fifty years has past since Simon Belmont rescued the land from the curse of Dracula. Now, Simon's descendant Juste Belmont, must acquire the relics of Dracula to unravel the disappearance of his childhood friend Lydie. The castle's enchanting mysteries and danger await all those who dare enter.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20020920T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Action / Adventure-Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Castlevania - Harmony of Dissonance (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4243" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Comix Zone (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).7z</path>
		<name>Comix Zone</name>
		<desc>Sketch Turner was a starving comic book artist, living with his pet rat Roadkill... that is until a lightning storm mysteriously brought his cartoon villain, Mortus, to life and imprisoned Sketch within the pages of his own comic book. Now trapped in the world that he himself created, but someone else is now drawing, Sketch must battle through the pages of his own comic book, and past his own creations, to a final battle with Mortus. Perhaps one of his own creations, General Alissa Cyan might be able to help...

Comix Zone is a side-scrolling fighting game with a difference, you're inside of a comic book and you yourself know it. Smash enemies into the sides of frames, rip through the paper to unleash a super move and otherwise wreck havoc throughout the limitations of the graphic novel. Sketch himself can jump, attack and use various items that he finds along the comic book, including his rat friend, Roadkill. Button combinations can be used to unleash powerful techniques.

The game progresses linear through each page of the comic book, however secret paths and alternate routes through the story can be discovered. At the end of each level, Sketch receives a super hero rating for how well he's progressing.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20020911T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Virtucraft</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Comix Zone (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4087" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Contra Advance - The Alien Wars EX (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Contra Advance : The Alien Wars EX</name>
		<desc>In Contra Advance The Alien Wars EX, take down massive hordes of aliens, robots, and monsters to stop the evil Red Falcon from taking over the world! Featuring all new levels and graphics from the original Super Nintendo® hit, Contra's fast paced shooting action will keep you on the edge of your seat!</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20021103T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter-Shooter / Run and Gun-Shoot'em Up-Shoot'em up / Horizontal-Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/Contra Advance - The Alien Wars EX (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3882" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Crash Bandicoot - The Huge Adventure (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Crash Bandicoot : The Huge Adventure</name>
		<desc>Tired of endlessly doing battle with meddling bandicoots, the nefarious Dr. Neo Cortex shrinks the entire Earth, and Crash and Coco along with it, to the size of a wumpa fruit. Luckily, Coco invents a machine to reverse the effects, but she needs crystals from around the world to power it. Crash must retrieve the crystals to help return the entire planet to its natural state. Experience Crash's biggest adventure yet, with gameplay modes ranging from side-scrolling to 3D chase levels to aerial dogfight combat sequences. Battle your way through over 20 huge levels and six unique locations to defeat Cortex and save the world.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20020225T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vicarious Visions</developer>
		<publisher>Universal Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Crash Bandicoot - The Huge Adventure (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3947" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Crash Bandicoot 2 - N-Tranced (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Crash Bandicoot 2 : N-Tranced</name>
		<desc>Crash is back and ready to take on an all-new nefarious villain. After the events of Crash Bandicoot: The Huge Adventure, Tropy, with the help of N. Trance, kidnaps Coco and Crunch, planning to brainwash them to the evil side. Now, Crash must travel to N. Trance's twisted realm, battle and rescue Coco and Crunch, and ultimately defeat N. Trance and N. Tropy. To achieve these goals, you must use all of Crash's spin, slide, and jumping abilities across 24 different levels. As you progress through the game, you'll find yourself flying a helicopter, water-skiing, and piloting a spaceship--all for the sake of saving your friends.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20031204T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vicarious Visions</developer>
		<publisher>Universal Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/Crash Bandicoot 2 - N-Tranced (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3946" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Crash Bandicoot Purple - Ripto's Rampage (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Crash Bandicoot Purple : Ripto's Rampage</name>
		<desc>In Crash Bandicoot Purple: Ripto's Rampage and Spyro Orange: The Cortex Conspiracy, Dr. Neo Cortex--Crash's nemesis--and Ripto--Spyro's nemesis--have accidentally met up through underground portals and are set on taking over the entire universe. Crash and Spyro must team up with each other to discover the identity of the new menace and save the universe from this evil plot. In these side-scrolling adventures, you can link up with three friends for a variety of multiplayer modes, including Party Games, Wager Games, and Card Trading. Connecting both Crash Bandicoot Purple and Spyro Orange gives you the option of unlocking special content and allows you to trade and wager the cards with friends.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20040601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vicarious Visions</developer>
		<publisher>Vivendi Universal Games</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Crash Bandicoot Purple - Ripto's Rampage (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3951" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Crash Nitro Kart (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Crash Nitro Kart</name>
		<desc>Crash Bandicoot returns to the karting scene with a host of other characters from the adventure series, and this time they have both Neo Cortex and Emperor Velo to worry about. Velo has taken the crew to a remote planet, forced to race for their lives against Neo Cortex and his many evil doers.

Choose from various game modes, from the straight into the action Arcade mode to Adventure mode, following Crash and the gang in the story to save Earth. Race against four friends in multiplayer battle modes, plus connect to the Gamecube for extra options and upload your high scores to the internet ranking system.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20031111T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vicarious Visions</developer>
		<publisher>Universal Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Crash Nitro Kart (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3901" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Crash of the Titans (USA) (En,Fr).7z</path>
		<name>Crash of the Titans</name>
		<desc>Neo Cortex is back and has corrupted the Tiki powers of Wumpa Island to create hundreds of strange, titanic monsters! Fortunately, Crash is ready for him and has learned new combat and acrobatic abilities to hijack these large outrageous mutants and use their powers against each other and eventually defeat Neo Cortex's new Doominator Robot.

Crash of the Titans for GBA is an action-sidescroller game. Crash jumps, punches, and smashes his way through six island locations in search of Wumpa Fruit, Tiki Masks, and other collectibles. Along the way, he'll encounter Cortex's titular henchmen, which he'll have to climb on top and hijack to take their combat powers. By jacking the right combination of foes, he'll eventually gain the powers he needs to take on Neo Cortex himself and save Wumpa Island yet again.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20071002T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Amaze Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Crash of the Titans (USA) (En,Fr).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4280" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Crazy Taxi - Catch a Ride (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Crazy Taxi : Catch a Ride</name>
		<desc>Race against the clock as you pick up passengers and white-knuckle it through busy streets and back alleys. And time is money! So get a grip on the wheel and put the pedal to the metal.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20030408T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Graphic State Games</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Crazy Taxi - Catch a Ride (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4560" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Cruis'n Velocity (USA, Europe).7z</path>
		<name>Cruis'n Velocity</name>
		<desc>Take control of one of ten high powered vehicles and race through 14 tracks based on different places in the world including Las Vegas, Paris and even Mars! Race to win the Cruis'n Cup or a range of different championships, or race against 3 friends in 4 player mode.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20011130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Graphic State Limited</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving-Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Cruis'n Velocity (USA, Europe).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4156" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Donald Duck Advance (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Donald Duck Advance</name>
		<desc>Search the ends of the world to find and defeat Merlock, rescue Daisy and harness the energy spheres needed to activate Gyro's time machine. 
 
*Prevent the quackiest of all heroes from losing his cool and exploding into a laughable frenzy 
*Master action-packed gameplay through 18 pluse-pounding levels 
*Play a game that minics a cartoon with vivid graphics wacky characters and zany sound effects</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20011119T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Donald Duck Advance (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3898" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Donkey Kong Country 2 (USA, Australia).7z</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Country 2</name>
		<desc>The Donkey Kong Country series returns to the Game Boy Advance in a sequel that features Dixie Kong. She and Diddy Kong must team up to rescue Donkey Kong from the evil Kaptain K. Rool. You'll play as both Diddy and Dixie, and master their different attacks. Test your skills and beat the clock in Diddy's Dash, or race against your friends to see who's the fastest. You can play the game solo or challenge your friends in new bonus games such as Funky's Flights and Bag a Bug.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20041115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Donkey Kong Country 2 (USA, Australia).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3857" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Donkey Kong Country 3 (USA, Australia).7z</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Country 3</name>
		<desc>Revisit Donkey Kong Island and join the Kong family for their latest adventure. The Kremlings have a mysterious new leader named KAOS and are up to their usual mischief, even capturing Donkey Kong and Diddy Kong. Now it's up to Dixie Kong and the newest Kong, a giant infant named Kiddy, to rescue the two missing apes.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20051107T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/Donkey Kong Country 3 (USA, Australia).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3831" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Donkey Kong Country (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Country</name>
		<desc>In Donkey Kong Country for Gameboy Advance, you play as Nintendo's famous gorilla. King K. Rool has stolen Donkey's bananas and he decides to go looking for them. Two characters are playable, Donkey is bigger and stronger, while Diddy is faster. It is possible to play in pairs, either in turns or in teams. Animals will help you get through certain levels and defeat the Kremlings.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20030609T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/Donkey Kong Country (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3905" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Doom II (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Doom II</name>
		<desc>In this sequel to the original Doom, you play the same hero - the last remaining space marine. After having single-handedly saved Mars from demonic threat, you return to Earth, only to find out that the demons have already invaded it, killed all its inhabitants or turned them into demons. It's your task to kill all the demons and to save the Earth.

Doom II looks and plays very similarly to its predecessor, utilizing the same 3D graphical engine with 2D sprites for enemies. The gameplay once again consists entirely of navigating the hero from first-person view through 3D environments and shooting at the demons while attempting to find your way out by flipping switches and looking for keys. Unlike in Doom, which is divided into three episodes, the 30 levels of Doom II (plus the 2 secret levels) form one long episode. 

You have the same weapons as in the first Doom, plus a new one: a super shotgun. There are also some new demons in this sequel, such as the chaingun-toting Heavy Weapon Dudes, the skeletal Revenants who launch homing missiles and the Arch-Viles who have a highly damaging fire attack. There is also one new power-up, a Megasphere which boosts your health and armor to the max.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20021023T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Torus Games</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person-Action-Shooter</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Doom II (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3816" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Doom (USA, Europe).7z</path>
		<name>Doom</name>
		<desc>From the legendary game developers at id Software, comes an explosive journey into the nightmare world of DOOM. Embark on a harrowing mission to rid of Martian Moon Base of hordes of demonic creatures. Navigate through DOOM's 24 maze like levels, scouring the corridors for secret areas and combat aids as you take on hell spawned demons with an explosive arsenal of chainguns, plasma rifles and rocket launchers. Use the Game Boy Advance Game Link® Cable to team up with a friend and blast the levels together or link up to 4 players for the ultimate deathmatch.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20011116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>id Software</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person-Action-Shooter</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Doom (USA, Europe).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3784" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dragon Ball - Advanced Adventure (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Dragon Ball : Advanced Adventure</name>
		<desc>Join Goku in his very first epic adventure as he defends the earth from the relentless Red Ribbon Army. Start down his path to power, and help turn an ordinary boy into the ultimate champion.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050617T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dimps Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action-Action / Adventure-Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/Dragon Ball - Advanced Adventure (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3785" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dragonball Z - Buu's Fury .7z</path>
		<name>Dragon Ball Z : Buu's Fury</name>
		<desc>Dragon Ball Z: Buu's Fury begins with the Other World Tournament Saga and continues through the Kid Buu Saga, the final chapter in the Dragon Ball Z story. In a game that combines action and role-playing game elements with exploration, enemies, boss enemies, puzzles, and quests, your ultimate goal is to defeat Buu. Choose the best character Goku, Vegeta, Gohan, Goten, or Trunks for each mission, create fusion characters whenever necessary, and unleash powerful attack combos and super moves.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20040914T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Webfoot</developer>
		<publisher>Atari SA</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games-Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/Dragonball Z - Buu's Fury .png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3791" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dragonball Z - Supersonic Warriors.7z</path>
		<name>Dragon Ball Z : Supersonic Warriors</name>
		<desc>The Aerial Assault Begins! 
 
Pick your DBZ Dream Team and shake the Dragon Ball Z universe with free-flight combat! Bombard opponents with punishing attacks on the ground and in the air. It's thunderous DBZ fighting unlike anything you've ever seen before!</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20040622T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cavia</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/Dragonball Z - Supersonic Warriors.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3991" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Duke Nukem Advance (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Duke Nukem Advance</name>
		<desc>Alien scientists are working at taking over earth, and have already occupied the secret military base, Area 51. But little do they know that Duke Nukem is back and on their case, and he'll be travelling around the world, from Egypt to Australia, to make sure he's shot, frozen and/or stamped on every one of these creeps; and pick up a few girls while he's at it.

There are 19 stages to be completed, each hosting their own secrets and colored keycards, not to be mention the alien nasties themselves. Some of the classic weaponry is in, the shrink ray and freezer for instance. And in, also, are some old villains too, like the all time fav Pig Cop.

Upto 4 GBA's can be linked together for the multiplayer deathmatch mode, but each player has to have his own gamepak.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20020830T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Torus Games</developer>
		<publisher>Take 2 Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter-Shooter / 1st person-Action-Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Duke Nukem Advance (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3807" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Eragon (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Eragon</name>
		<desc>Eragon for the Game Boy Advance is a traditional turn based RPG with a combat system that emphasizes motion and action.  Players use combinations of spells, melee attacks, and ranged attacks to battle Urgals, thieves, soldiers, and other various enemies.  This is an RPG where combat strategy plays a key role in success.

Players can make use of the RPG mechanics to create offensive and defensive potions, craft better armor and weapons, learn offensive and defensive spells, or become trackers who are able to find hidden encounters.  This design encourages experimentation, opens up a lot of strategic possibilities, and allows a lot of replayability.

The player assumes the role of Eragon, a young boy with a mysterious origin and an important future, on his perilous journey to avenge his father, rescue the woman of his dreams and join forces with the Varden in their war against King Galbatorix. On this adventure Eragon encounters many allies; Brom the old wizened story teller, Ayra the elf guard of the dragon egg, Murtagh the orphan with a troubled past, Angela an herbalist witch, and a powerful dragon that will help unveil Eragon's true destiny.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20061124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Amaze Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Eragon (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3787" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Final Fantasy I &amp; II - Dawn of Souls (USA, Australia).7z</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy I &amp; II : Dawn of Souls</name>
		<desc>Final Fantasy I: Experience Final Fantasy in a way you've never imagined, with improved graphics and the all-new Soul of Chaos dungeon. Take on the role of the four Warriors of Light, and restore order to their chaotic world! 
Final Fantasy II: Final Fantasy II gave players deeper characters and a more compelling storyline. In this enhanced edition, experience the addition of the Soul of Rebirth, the never-before-told saga of the heroes who gave their lives to save their world!</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20041129T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Final Fantasy I &amp; II - Dawn of Souls (USA, Australia).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3763" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Final Fantasy IV Advance (USA, Australia).7z</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy IV Advance</name>
		<desc>This classic adventure includes 18 towns and castles, dozens of magical spells, and hundreds of monsters, weapons, and items to help players on their quests. The game features the astounding music, challenging adventures, and interesting storyline that are the hallmarks of the Final Fantasy franchise. Additional game elements also have been added to enhance the Game Boy Advance version.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20051212T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Final Fantasy IV Advance (USA, Australia).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3760" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Final Fantasy Tactics Advance (USA, Australia).7z</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy Tactics Advance</name>
		<desc>Marche and a few friends are out on a usual venture through their local town, St. Ivalice, only to discover a book filled with fantasy and magic. Setting their mind to the thoughts of a magical land, they get transported to the world of Ivalice, which happens to be based on one of the friends' favourite games, Final Fantasy.

Finding himself alone, Marche must join a clan of warriors and travel through this new land of mystery to find his lost friends, and return to the real world, while learning all about this new place and the magic it holds.

Not a direct sequel to Final Fantasy Tactics, FFTA combines the many elements of the tactical original with a slightly modern feel, and an original storyline for the GBA. As a clan leader, you must manage your team (from their combat skills and inventory to each and every battle you face).

Both your basic handheld weapons and magic are available to you, with the ability to summon monsters for support. Two players can link GBA's for battles, trading items and clan members as well.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20030908T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/Final Fantasy Tactics Advance (USA, Australia).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3778" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Final Fantasy V Advance (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy V Advance</name>
		<desc>The winds fail. Ships stand still, unable to fill their sails. The world races to its end. Unless a handful of heroes can protect the remaining crystals, the world will fall into ruin. Set off on a grand adventure in the finest version of FINAL FANTASY V ever released!</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20061106T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Final Fantasy V Advance (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3765" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Final Fantasy VI Advance (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy VI Advance</name>
		<desc>An Ancient War Rekindled 
 
A thousand years after the War of the Magi, the Gestahlian Empire has succeeded in reviving the lost power of magic through its clandestine Magitek research program. Now, as the Empire threatens to enslave the world with its newfound might, it is up to a band of rebels known as the Returners to find a way to strike back before the flames of war consume the world once more.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20070205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games-Fight</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Final Fantasy VI Advance (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4024" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Final Fight One (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Final Fight One</name>
		<desc>Classic arcade action is unleased on the Game Boy Advance system in Final Fight One. There's trouble in Metro City. The members of the Mad Gear Gang have kidnapped the mayor's daughter Jessica and the clock is ticking. The mayor, an ex-street fighter himself, calls in the big guns to help, enlisting the iron fist team of Cody and Guy. Now, it's a race against time to scour the city, defeat an army of the Mad Gear Gang's minions, and rescue Jessica before it's too late!</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20010927T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Fight-Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/Final Fight One (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3879" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./F-Zero - GP Legend (USA).7z</path>
		<name>F-Zero : GP Legend</name>
		<desc>The year is A.D. 2201, and you are about to enter the world of ultra-high-speed F-ZERO Grand Prix races, which take place on specially-constructed circuit tracks located all over the universe. Take control of eight different characters - including the mysterious Captain Falcon, new racing star Rick Wheeler, and the evil lord Black Shadow - as you race through an action-packed story that spans multiple planets!</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20040902T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/F-Zero - GP Legend (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3889" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./F-Zero - Maximum Velocity (USA, Europe).7z</path>
		<name>F-Zero : Maximum Velocity</name>
		<desc>All galactic speed limits are about to be broken! F-Zero Maximum Velocity has arrived, and the future of racing has never looked so sweet. Brand-new vehicles and Game Boy Advance original tracks await, so whether you're a Super NES® veteran or a race rookies, you'll need some practice laps. And even if you do master the Grand Prix circuit, you'll still have to beat your friends to the finish line. That's right, race fans--with the Game Boy Advance Game Link® cable you can take on up to three rival racers, so put the pedal to the metal and get busy boosting, bumping and jumping your way to intergalactic glory!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20010612T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/F-Zero - Maximum Velocity (USA, Europe).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="97399" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./GEMini (Mr Smayds).7z</path>
		<name>Gemini</name>
		<desc>Bejeweled style match-3 for the GameBoy Advance.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Mr Smayds</developer>
		<publisher>Mr Smayds</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/GEMini (Mr Smayds).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3838" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Grand Theft Auto Advance (U).7z</path>
		<name>Grand Theft Auto Advance</name>
		<desc>The Grand Theft Auto series finally makes its way to the Game Boy Advance. You play as a member of the Mob looking for a way out of your vicious lifestyle. The murder of your mentor, however, sets you off on a search for those responsible. To track down the killers, you must complete all-new missions while avoiding every cop in the city. As in previous installments in the Grand Theft Auto series, you can jack cars, explore the city, and wield a variety of weapons.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20041026T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Eclipse</developer>
		<publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Grand Theft Auto Advance (U).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3941" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Gunstar Super Heroes (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Gunstar Super Heroes</name>
		<desc>Your enemies intend to use a powerful crystal to resurrect the devastating God of Ruin and it's up to the Gunstar Heroes, Blue and Red to stop them! Developed by critically acclaimed developer, Treasure, this fast-paced action game will push your Game Boy Advance to the limits! 
 
-Blast your way through six intense levels and defeat an evil empire 
-Choose your hero: play as Red or Blue to combat powerful enemies and gigantic bosses 
-Amazing visuals create an unforgettable gaming experience</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20051118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Treasure</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Gunstar Super Heroes (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3921" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Jackie Chan Adventures - Legend of the Darkhand (USA, Europe).7z</path>
		<name>Jackie Chan Adventures : Legend of the Dark Hand</name>
		<desc>Are you Chan enough? 
As Jackie Chan, martial arts master and expert archeologist, you have | to take a quest around the world to defeat the evil Dark Hand organization. Their sinister demons seek to enter the earthly realm and it's up to you and your cunning wit, martial arts skill and magical scrolls to stop them in their tracks.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20011130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Torus Games</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Jackie Chan Adventures - Legend of the Darkhand (USA, Europe).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3961" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./James Pond - Codename Robocod (USA) (En,Fr,Es,Pt).7z</path>
		<name>James Pond : Codename RoboCod</name>
		<desc>In his second adventure James Pond must retrieve the toys Dr Maybe has stolen. Pond has been armed with an Inspector Gadget-style stretch device, which he can use to view higher areas or claw onto ceilings so as to slide across them. The gameplay takes place across worlds themed around particular types of toys, such as sporting goods, candy and aircraft. The levels scroll sideways, although a small amount of vertical movement is included. On each level Pond must collect 2 penguins and reach the exit, although there are usually multiple exits and lots of secret areas to explore. After completing each pair of two worlds (each of which has three sub levels), a boss must be faced.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>20050101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Creature Labs</developer>
		<publisher>Play It!</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/James Pond - Codename Robocod (USA) (En,Fr,Es,Pt).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4003" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Jurassic Park III - Island Attack (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Jurassic Park III : Island Attack</name>
		<desc>Won't these dinosaurs ever die? Refusing to succumb to extinction, the big, bad monsters of Jurassic Park return for another dino-sized adventure. Make your way through 12 levels of action, using high-tech weaponry to stalk to the prehistoric beasts before they can stalk you. Ten different species will terrorize you throughout the JURASSIC PARK locales. With graphics and play that rival coin-operated games, JURASSIC PARK III: Island Attack might just be the biggest thing to ever happen to handheld gaming.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20011126T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Adventure-Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Jurassic Park III - Island Attack (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3880" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Jurassic Park III - Park Builder (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Jurassic Park III : Park Builder</name>
		<desc>Clearly, the folks who built the original park were guilty of a few oversights. Think you can do any better? Try your hand at plotting out all of the details of the creation and management of a dinosaur park in JURASSIC PARK III: Park Builder. A strategy-simulation title of the highest caliber, the game leaves you in charge of 100 dinosaur species you have the task of placing them and maintaining their health. Of course, there's also the matter of the restaurants, shops, rides, and other attractions. If the park you create is too boring, poorly maintained, or excessively expensive, no one will show up, so you'd better use some seriously discerning judgment. In addition to managing the park, you'll have to pick up DNA strands from throughout the park to create new dinosaurs to keep the people coming back. Does it sound like too much to handle? Just wait until one of your prehistoric pals escapes on opening day.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20011012T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/Jurassic Park III - Park Builder (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4058" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Jurassic Park III - The DNA Factor (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Jurassic Park III : The DNA Factor</name>
		<desc>Jurassic Park III: The DNA Factor recreates the Jurassic Park world and takes players into an interactive pre-historic adventure. The game is a fun and unique mix of side-scrolling adventure stages and intense puzzle action. Jurassic Park III: The DNA Factor includes more than 10 species of dinosaurs and 12 huge levels to explore.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20010716T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Jurassic Park III - The DNA Factor (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3758" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Kingdom Hearts - Chain of Memories (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Kingdom Hearts : Chain of Memories</name>
		<desc>Adventure is in the cards ! 
 
Kingdom Hearts: Chain of Memories delivers an entirely new adventure and set the stage for Kingdom Hearts II. 
Sora, Donald, and Goofy travel through many vast and colourful worlds in search of their missing companions. 
Encounter over 100 of your favourite Disney and Final Fantasy friends and foes. 
 
Collect mysterious cards that open doors to new adventures, unlock powerful abilities, and call familiar friends 
to your side. 
 
Experience big, bold graphics and high-quality animation.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20041207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jupiter Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games-Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/Kingdom Hearts - Chain of Memories (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3822" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Kirby &amp; the Amazing Mirror (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Kirby &amp; the Amazing Mirror</name>
		<desc>The Mirror World has been invaded by an evil shadow, and Kirby's got to save the day! Fortunately, he won't have to go it alone! He's been split into four Kirbys of different colors, and with his trusty cell phone, he can call up his colorful clones to lend a hand!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20041018T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Flagship Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action-Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Kirby &amp; the Amazing Mirror (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3860" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Kirby - Nightmare in Dream Land (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Kirby : Nightmare in Dream Land</name>
		<desc>Everyone in Dream Land has lost the ability to dream! It seems that King Dedede has stolen the Star Rod, the source of power for the Fountain of Dreams, and given its fragmented pieces to his goons for safekeeping. The world needs a hero... a round pink one. As Kirby embarks on an adventure to recover the Star Rod, he'll have to copy every trick in the book to bring good dreams back to Dream Land.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20021202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Kirby - Nightmare in Dream Land (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3860" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Kirby - Nightmare in Dreamland (U) [!].7z</path>
		<name>Kirby : Nightmare in Dream Land</name>
		<desc>Everyone in Dream Land has lost the ability to dream! It seems that King Dedede has stolen the Star Rod, the source of power for the Fountain of Dreams, and given its fragmented pieces to his goons for safekeeping. The world needs a hero... a round pink one. As Kirby embarks on an adventure to recover the Star Rod, he'll have to copy every trick in the book to bring good dreams back to Dream Land.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20021202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Kirby - Nightmare in Dream Land (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4000" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Klonoa - Empire of Dreams (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Klonoa : Empire of Dreams</name>
		<desc>A grumpy Emperor suffering from insomnia has banned dreaming and imprisoned Klonoa for breaking the law. To prove his courage and win his freedom, Klonoa must defeat the monsters that are creating havoc throughout the empire. Help our hero in his most perilous journey yet and experience the all-new thrills!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20010911T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Now Production</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Klonoa - Empire of Dreams (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="84032" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Tomb Raider - The Prophecy (U) (M5).7z</path>
		<name>Lara Croft Tomb Raider : The Prophecy</name>
		<desc>Lara Croft discovers a manuscript which speaks of a mysterious occult magic which will bring desolation on earth in the near future. This prophecy also talks of three legendary stones which are linked with the mentioned devastation. Fascinated, Lara travels around the globe in search of these fabled stones. Along the way she'll meet enemies both human and otherwise and will also have to deal with dark magic of sorts. 
 
Lara is now in a "quasi-3D" overhead environment, as opposed to the 2D-platformer view of the previous handheld (GBC) versions. This view proves helpful while Lara runs, jumps, shimmys, and shoots around. Although there is lack of a save feature, there is a password system which lets you restore back to 'almost' where you left.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20021112T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Action / Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Tomb Raider - The Prophecy (U) (M5).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3762" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mario &amp; Luigi - Superstar Saga (U).7z</path>
		<name>Mario &amp; Luigi : Superstar Saga</name>
		<desc>An evil witch has replaced Princess Peach's fair speech with explosives! Mario and Luigi must once again come to her rescue, but this time they employ the help of Bowser, their sworn enemy. Mario and Luigi must learn new moves and combine powers to fight off enemies and move closer to the witch's castle. Guide this unlikely bunch through an abundance of minigames such as Border Jump and Mystery Carts. Combine the powers of Mario and Luigi to pull off special tag-team moves. Immerse yourself in this bright, cartoonish, and humorous world, complete with hit music featured in previous Mario games.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20031117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Alpha Dream</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games-Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Mario &amp; Luigi - Superstar Saga (U).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4027" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mario Golf - Advance Tour (U).7z</path>
		<name>Mario Golf : Advance Tour</name>
		<desc>Grab your clubs and start down the road to golfing perfection in this role-playing golf adventure! Chat up the locals at golf clinics, hone your skills in challenges like Club Slots and Go-Go Gates, and try to become the champ of all the country clubs! The Mushroom Kingdom residents take on only the very best.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20040622T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Camelot Software</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports-Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Mario Golf - Advance Tour (U).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3790" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mario Kart - Super Circuit (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Mario Kart : Super Circuit</name>
		<desc>All your favourite kart-racing characters are back and ready to kick it into high gear! 20 brand-new tracks await on Game Boy Advance, loaded with classic power-ups and primed for the type of frenzied racing that only Mario Kart: Super Circuit can deliver. It's time to burn rubber in the Grand Prix, challenge your pals, race your own ghost, clash in battle mode and feel the power in the palm of your hand!</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20010827T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Mario Kart Super Circuit (U) [!].png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3790" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mario Kart Super Circuit (U) [!].7z</path>
		<name>Mario Kart : Super Circuit</name>
		<desc>All your favourite kart-racing characters are back and ready to kick it into high gear! 20 brand-new tracks await on Game Boy Advance, loaded with classic power-ups and primed for the type of frenzied racing that only Mario Kart: Super Circuit can deliver. It's time to burn rubber in the Grand Prix, challenge your pals, race your own ghost, clash in battle mode and feel the power in the palm of your hand!</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20010827T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Mario Kart Super Circuit (U) [!].png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3883" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mario Party Advance (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Mario Party Advance</name>
		<desc>The first portable incarnation of the Mario Party series, Mario Party Advance shakes things up quite a bit on the GBA.  With the focus on the single-player, there are all kinds of single-player mini-games, one giant single-player board to traverse instead of multiple ones (Shroom City), and all kinds of different Gaddgets and gameplay modes to indulge in.

The main single-player experience involves traveling across "Shroom City," which is a major departure from the standard set-up in past Mario Party titles.  You have the choice to be Mario, Luigi, Peach, or Yoshi, and depending on who you choose, you'll start at a different spot on the board, which is quite large.

You're given die rolls to navigate the board and, when you reach special sections of the map, complete special quests, which often involve helping residents of Shroom City and/or participating in special challenges.  Most quests involve collecting some sort of object elsewhere or a mini-game.  By completing these quests, you'll collect stars, which eventually allow for special boss bouts with Bowser, and you'll unlock mini-games and Gaddgets, which are simple, toy-like contraptions that you can play with.

The game ends when you complete your allotted number of turns, although additional turns and die rolls can be earned during the game by completing the "Mushroom Challenges" that occur rather often.  After completing your session, your rewards are saved, and you can play with your mini-games and Gaddgets in Play Mode.

There are also two additional modes available, "Party Land," where you can play special duel mini-games with a friend, and "Challenge Land," where you play through special modes that test your mini-game skills to earn coins, which can be used to purchase additional unlockables in a shop.

Finally, there is also a feature called the "Bonus Board."  You can play with a board that is included with the game using the GBA.  The GBA takes care of die rolls, mini-games, and end-of-the-game events.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20050328T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>A.I</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Board game-Various</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/Mario Party Advance (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="84123" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mario Pinball Land (USA, Australia).7z</path>
		<name>Mario Pinball Land</name>
		<desc>This is the standard "Bowser has kidnapped the Princess, and Mario must rescue her" story. In this case, the Princess is transformed into a ball and launched from a Super Mario 64-style cannon, which a pair of goombas aim directly at Bowser's Castle. Mario is also transformed into a ball and chases after her.

There are 5 levels, each consisting of a set of pinball tables. Each table has some exits (including the one below the flippers) that Mario can use to move to other tables. Also, each one holds a star, normally obtained by defeating all enemies on the table. Some exits require that Mario has a certain number of stars. To gain access to Bowser's castle, Mario must defeat the bosses of the first 4 levels, which gives him star keys. The game also features a "Time Attack" mode, which allows players to fight already defeated bosses again.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20041004T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Fuse Games Limited</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Pinball-Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Mario Pinball Land (USA, Australia).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3819" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mario Tennis - Power Tour (USA, Australia) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).7z</path>
		<name>Mario Tennis: Power Tour</name>
		<desc>Players can test their backhand in this unique role-playing tennis adventure. Train hard at the Royal Tennis Academy to be a champion. Gain experience and improve your skills through lessons and tournaments, and rise to the top of the ranks. Play as Mario, Peach, Waluigi, or Donkey Kong in a slew of wild modes. Advance through the story and unlock even more characters, all with their own power moves. Beat Mario at his own game, then link up with a friend or three for even more frantic fun.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20051205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Camelot Software</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Tennis-Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Mario Tennis Advance - Power Tour (U).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3819" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mario Tennis Advance - Power Tour (U).7z</path>
		<name>Mario Tennis: Power Tour</name>
		<desc>Players can test their backhand in this unique role-playing tennis adventure. Train hard at the Royal Tennis Academy to be a champion. Gain experience and improve your skills through lessons and tournaments, and rise to the top of the ranks. Play as Mario, Peach, Waluigi, or Donkey Kong in a slew of wild modes. Advance through the story and unlock even more characters, all with their own power moves. Beat Mario at his own game, then link up with a friend or three for even more frantic fun.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20051205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Camelot Software</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Tennis-Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Mario Tennis Advance - Power Tour (U).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3871" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mario vs. Donkey Kong (USA, Australia).7z</path>
		<name>Mario vs. Donkey Kong</name>
		<desc>After years of apparent goodwill, Mario and Donkey Kong are at it again--this time, on Game Boy Advance. Donkey Kong has stolen all the Mini-Mario toys from the Mario Toy Co., and now it's up to Mario to hunt down his longtime nemesis and retrieve the pilfered goods. As Mario, you must race through challenging levels while finding keys and releasing Mini Marios before time runs out. Along the way, you'll master new moves that can help you overcome new puzzles.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20040524T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game-Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Mario vs. Donkey Kong (USA, Australia).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3855" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Marvel - Ultimate Alliance (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Marvel : Ultimate Alliance</name>
		<desc>The handheld version of Marvel Ultimate Alliance, like its console counterparts, has the player taking control over one of a selection of Marvel super-heroes and battling through locations and enemies from the Marvel universe. Selectable playable characters are: Spider-Man, Blade, Elektra, Thor, Wolverine, Captain America, Deadpool and Iceman. Ms. Marvel and Thing as also available as unlockable characters.

The game plays out something like Final Fight, where the player walks from left to right with the ability to move on the z-axis and punch and kick wave after wave of enemies including the occasional boss.

It has some unique elements added to the genre basics, however.  A meter controls the use of super powers, which can be upgraded as experience is gained. Players also have the ability to summon various Marvel heroes for quick support roles.  There are many items to find, both quest items, such as keys to unlock doors and weapons and equipment, like weapons and armor, to buff up the characters' abilties.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>20061027T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Raven Software</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games-Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Marvel - Ultimate Alliance (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4064" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mega Man Zero 2 (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Mega Man Zero 2</name>
		<desc>A year after the events in Mega Man Zero, the hero finds himself in another battle to save the world. Caught in-between the reploids and humans, Neo Arcadia's new commander has tricked Zero into helping her, although her reasons are uncertain.

To fix the problem, Zero must battle through level after level, using the new Chain Rod weapon to grapple onto ledges to gain an advantage in collecting out of reach items or attacking enemies from above. Cyber Elfs can again be collected to gain some helpful powerups.

New to the series is a two player challenge mode, where the first to complete the level wins.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20031014T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Inti Creates</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/Mega Man Zero 2 (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3987" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mega Man Zero 3 (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Mega Man Zero 3</name>
		<desc>In the third installment of Capcom's Mega Man Zero series, you, unsurprisingly, play as Zero. Continuing where the Mega Man Zero 2 left off, you have to find and neutralize the recently escaped "Dark Elf," before it's able to brainwash the Resistance for the purpose of conquering Neo Arcadia. 

In addition to the old Cyber Elf system, this game also contains a new "chip" system, where Zero can gain new abilities by finding chips and installing chip in himself. But they didn't decide to abandon the Cyber Elves in this game by giving them nothing new. No, in order to extend the life of the Cyber Elves, they added the new concept of "Cyber Space" to levels, where you enter a door to Cyber Space and are allowed to use each Cyber Elf as much as you please without them dying. However, there aren't too many "Secret Disks" (items that can contain anything from profiles of characters to Cyber Elves to new chips) in Cyber Space, so it's better to spend more time in the normal level.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20041005T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Inti Creates</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Mega Man Zero 3 (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3886" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mega Man Zero 4 (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Mega Man Zero 4</name>
		<desc>The Zero Knuckle... the baddest new tool in Zero's arsenal lets you steal enemies' weapons and use them in battle. Employ this along with countless other cool moves to fight the Neo Arcadian army, defeat the evil Dr. Weil and help the caravan of humans reach the peace and security of Area Zero.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20051004T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Inti Creates</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action-Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Mega Man Zero 4 (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3856" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mega Man Zero (USA, Europe).7z</path>
		<name>Mega Man Zero</name>
		<desc>It is the year 22XX...

The legendary heroes of the Reploids, X and Zero, defeated the evil Sigma long ago, and a new army was created to prevent outbreaks of the Maverick Virus. But as time went on, the army became oppressive, and began to deal out a paranoid brand of justice. It is said that their leader, once a great warrior, has become cold and calculating, eliminating any Reploid that dares oppose him.

A hero is needed in these dark times, and that is exactly what Ciel and her rebel group have found in an old ruin...a hero from the past, reborn in the future.

Zero has come into a time he does not know, to save it from a figure of the past...the fate of freedom rests on his shoulders.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20021102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Inti Creates</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Mega Man Zero (USA, Europe).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3937" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Metal Slug Advance (U).7z</path>
		<name>Metal Slug Advance</name>
		<desc>You're a warrior of the war, but now you are alone. Enemies have captured your allied troops, and it's up to you to get them back. Armed to the teeth with firearms, grenades and specially made "Slug" vehicles, you must travel across the levels and blast anything in sight that isn't a friendly.

Two characters are offered to play as, and along with the usual Metal Slug flair visually, and epic battle sequences against strange and startling foes, you can now collect special E-cards during the game. Saved allies will hand you these cards that, when brought back to camp, can increase ammo, power and many more improvements to alter the gameplay experience.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20041116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Noise Factory</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / Run and Gun-Action-Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Metal Slug Advance (U).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3769" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Metroid - Zero Mission (U) [!].7z</path>
		<name>Metroid : Zero Mission</name>
		<desc>She's battled baddies on nearly every Nintendo system, and now, Samus Aran returns to her roots. Metroid: Zero Mission relives the story that started it all--revealing for the first time full details of her meeting with the Metroids. The plotline will be familiar to longtime fans of the Metroid series, but the challenges are new, the power-ups are plentiful, and the graphics and sound are supercharged. Plus, if you thought that the original Metroid had a surprise ending, wait until you get past the Mother Brain in Metroid: Zero Mission. A new twist provides a deeper adventure than ever before.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20040209T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action-Action / Adventure-Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Metroid - Zero Mission (U) [!].png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3767" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Metroid Fusion (U) [!].7z</path>
		<name>Metroid Fusion</name>
		<desc>While lending mission support on planet SR388, interstellar bounty hunter Samus Aran is attacked by an X parasite, an organism with the ability to mimic the abilities of any creature it infects. Near death, Samus is saved by a vaccine made from the DNA of the last Metroid -- the X parasite's only natural predator. When the X spread to a research station in orbit around SR388, a weakened Samus is forced to exterminate them all ... or die trying.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20021117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Metroid Fusion (U) [!].png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4469" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Ms. Pac-Man - Maze Madness (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Ms. Pac-Man : Maze Madness</name>
		<desc>Ms. Pac-Man is back in an all-new "a-MAZE-ing" 3-D adventure. Chomp your way through mystical worlds to rescue Professor Pac. Free the lost worlds of Pac-Land from the horrid witch Mesmeralda. Videogame's most famous and favorite heroine is back to save the day!</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20041103T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Zoo Digital Publishing</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Action / Labyrinth-Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Ms. Pac-Man - Maze Madness (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4020" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Naruto - Ninja Council 2 (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Naruto : Ninja Council 2</name>
		<desc>Action game, based on the Shonen Jump manga. This sequel to the very first Naruto game on the GBA (the second game was a much different simulation/adventure) has three-times the amount of stages and characters twice the size. The action is streamlined and more dynamic. Players can transform into Naruto, Sasuke and Sakura and use their abilities to defeat the scrolling stages. The game also utilizes the link cable for a two-player co-op mode and for a four-player battle mode.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20040429T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tomy</developer>
		<publisher>Tomy</publisher>
		<genre>Fight-Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Naruto - Ninja Council 2 (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4032" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Naruto - Ninja Council (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Naruto : Ninja Council</name>
		<desc>Action game, based on the Shonen Jump manga. Slip into the role of series hero Uzumaki Naruto and make your way through side-scrolling levels with the help of Sasuke and Kakashi.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20060307T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Aspect</developer>
		<publisher>D3 Publisher</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Naruto - Ninja Council (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3764" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Need for Speed - Underground 2 (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,It).7z</path>
		<name>Need for Speed : Underground 2</name>
		<desc>The popular Need For Speed Underground franchise was adapted for systems with different capabilities. You drive around a city split into 5 distinct areas. As with the other versions, the aim is to drive well enough to boost your reputation. In this version the route is prescribed, without the exploration of the other systems. Available cars include machines from Volkswagen, Mitsubishi and Toyota. There are less upgrades in this version, although the appearance and handling of your car can still be varied. The story in this version follows a predefined path.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>20041115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/Need for Speed - Underground 2 (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,It).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3870" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Need for Speed - Underground (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,It).7z</path>
		<name>Need for Speed : Underground</name>
		<desc>Need For Speed: Underground is the seventh game in the long running Need For Speed racing series. Underground revolves around illegal nighttime streetracing with heavily modified import cars and has been greatly influenced by the movie "The Fast And The Furious" and its sequel.. Players get the chance to build their own racing machine almost from ground up, with hundreds or real licensed parts and lots of licensed cars, including the Mazda RX-7 and the Nissan Skyline GT-R. The game also features over 100 single player races and a hiphop/hardrock soundtrack including artists such as Mystikal, Rob Zombie and The Crystal Method.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20031218T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Need for Speed - Underground (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,It).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4224" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Pac-Man Collection (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Pac-Man Collection</name>
		<desc>Four classic Pac-Man games are included in this collection from Namco:

1. Pac-Man: The original arcade classic, complete and un-cut. 
2. Pac-Mania: A conversion of the 1987 update to Pac-Man, which takes the elements of the original arcade game and puts it into an isometric view, as well as adding the ability to jump.
3. Pac-Man Arrangement: Never re-produced outside of the arcade, Arrangement again uses the elements of the original Pac-Man and adds a fifth ghost, who can change shape and size when combined with the other 4 ghosts, and make life harder for Pac-Man. New power-ups are also included, like the ability to dash quickly around the screen, warp points to get from one place to the other and new ways of catching ghosts.
Pac-Attack: Like Tetris before it, you must fit falling blocks together to complete a line to clear the screen. In this case, the falling tiles also have ghosts in them, and once the Pac-Man tile appears (a tile with the Pac-Man symbol), Pac-Man will eat all of the ghosts that are in his path until he gets to a dead end.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20011207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Labyrinth-Action-Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Pac-Man Collection (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="84409" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Pokemon - LeafGreen Version (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Pokémon LeafGreen Version</name>
		<desc>Pokémon FireRed Version and LeafGreen Version are enhanced remakes of the original Pokémon Red and Blue video games, which were released in 1996. They were first released in Japan in January 2004 and released in North America and Europe in September and October respectively. Nearly two years after their original release, Nintendo re-marketed them as Player's Choice titles. The two games hold the distinction of being the first enhanced remakes of previous games within the franchise.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20040907T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>The Pokémon Company</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1-5</players>
		<image>./media/images/Pokemon - LeafGreen Version (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="84394" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Pokemon Mystery Dungeon - Red Rescue Team (USA, Australia).7z</path>
		<name>Pokémon Mystery Dungeon: Red Rescue Team</name>
		<desc>Introducing the newest Pokemon, YOU! 
 
What if you woke up one day, and you were a Pokemon? What if all of the sudden you find yourself in a NEW world, where you can speak and interact with other Pokemon? The adventure begins when you and your partner Pokemon set out on rescue missions in a world ravaged by natural disasters. But what is your true purpose and destiny in this Pokemon world? That's the real mystery....</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20060918T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Chunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Pokemon Mystery Dungeon - Red Rescue Team (USA, Australia).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="84396" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Pokemon Pinball - Ruby &amp; Sapphire (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Pokémon Pinball: Ruby &amp; Sapphire</name>
		<desc>Pokémon Pinball: Ruby &amp; Sapphire has all the features you'd demand of a pinball game, including bonus tables, lots of bumpers and ways to score massive points. As with your standard pinball video game, the left button on the D-pad and the A-button control the flippers with the R/L triggers used to shake the table. The catch here is that everything is themed in Pokémon. Instead of a ball, you make use of a Pokéball. Instead of standard bumpers, you're hitting the Pokéball against other Pokémon, and the ultimate goal is of course to "catch 'em all". The game features 200 Pokémon, two main tables, and link cable support.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20030826T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jupiter Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Pinball</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/Pokemon Pinball - Ruby &amp; Sapphire (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="0" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Pokemon Rosso Fuoco (I)(Independent).7z</path>
		<name>Pokemon Rosso Fuoco (I)(Independent)</name>
		<desc />
		<releasedate />
		<developer />
		<publisher />
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game id="84406" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Pokemon - Emerald Version (USA, Europe).7z</path>
		<name>Pokémon: Emerald Version</name>
		<desc>The Hoenn region is unstable ? Rayquaza has awakened! Your skills as a Trainer will be challenged like they've never been challenged before as you try to maintain balance between Kyogre &amp; Groudon. Prove your skill by earning Badges &amp; gaining access to Battle Frontier ? the front line of Pokémon battling that offers a whole new level of competition. Never-before-experienced battles await you!</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20050501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1-5</players>
		<image>./media/images/Pokemon - Emerald Version (USA, Europe).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="84408" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Pokemon - FireRed Version (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Pokémon: FireRed Version</name>
		<desc>Set off on a grand adventure to fulfil your dreams of becoming a Pokémon Master! Explore the Kanto region and discover wild Pokémon around every corner. Build your Pokémon collection and train and battle your way to success?earn your badges as you develop winning strategies to use against experienced Gym Leaders in every town. Explore every inch to uncover amazing secrets that will help you in your quest to be the very best trainer ever!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20040907T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1-5</players>
		<image>./media/images/Pokemon Fire Red (U)(Independent).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="84408" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Pokemon Fire Red (U)(Independent).7z</path>
		<name>Pokémon: FireRed Version</name>
		<desc>Set off on a grand adventure to fulfil your dreams of becoming a Pokémon Master! Explore the Kanto region and discover wild Pokémon around every corner. Build your Pokémon collection and train and battle your way to success?earn your badges as you develop winning strategies to use against experienced Gym Leaders in every town. Explore every inch to uncover amazing secrets that will help you in your quest to be the very best trainer ever!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20040907T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1-5</players>
		<image>./media/images/Pokemon Fire Red (U)(Independent).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="84409" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Pokemon Leaf Green (U)(Independent).7z</path>
		<name>Pokémon: LeafGreen Version</name>
		<desc>Pokémon FireRed Version and LeafGreen Version are enhanced remakes of the original Pokémon Red and Blue video games, which were released in 1996. They were first released in Japan in January 2004 and released in North America and Europe in September and October respectively. Nearly two years after their original release, Nintendo re-marketed them as Player's Choice titles. The two games hold the distinction of being the first enhanced remakes of previous games within the franchise.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20040907T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>The Pokémon Company</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1-5</players>
		<image>./media/images/Pokemon - LeafGreen Version (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="84411" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Pokemon - Ruby Version (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Pokémon: Ruby Version</name>
		<desc>The race to catch 'em all is on again in Pokémon Ruby. This entry in the Pokémon series features an all-new storyline, awesome new Pokémon, and addictive RPG gameplay. One of the biggest additions to Pokémon Ruby is the two-on-two battle system, which allows you to link up with three friends to battle competitively or cooperatively. You can also showcase your Pokémon's coolness, beauty, cuteness, smartness, and toughness in Pokémon contests. With new Pokémon, two-on-two battles, and an all-new region of Hoenn to explore, Pokémon Ruby takes the Pokémon experience to the next level.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20030318T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Pokemon - Ruby Version (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="84413" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Pokemon - Sapphire Version (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Pokémon: Sapphire Version</name>
		<desc>The race to catch 'em all is on again in Pokémon Sapphire. This entry in the Pokémon series features an all-new storyline, awesome new Pokémon, and addictive RPG gameplay. One of the biggest additions to Pokémon Sapphire is the two-on-two battle system, which allows you to link up with three friends to battle competitively or cooperatively. You can also showcase your Pokémon's coolness, beauty, cuteness, smartness, and toughness in Pokémon contests. With new Pokémon, two-on-two battles, and an all-new region of Hoenn to explore, Pokémon Sapphire takes the Pokémon experience to the next level.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20030319T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Pokemon - Sapphire Version (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="84439" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Prince of Persia - The Sands of Time (USA) (En,Fr,Es).7z</path>
		<name>Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time</name>
		<desc>Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time is a 3D platformer which focuses on acrobatics and agility. Throughout much of the game, the player must attempt to traverse the palace by running across walls, ascending or descending chasms by jumping back and forth between walls, avoiding traps, climbing structures and jumping from platform to platform, making other types of well-timed leaps, solving puzzles, and using discovered objects to progress.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20031030T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Prince of Persia - The Sands of Time (USA) (En,Fr,Es).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4641" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Rampage - Puzzle Attack (USA, Europe).7z</path>
		<name>Rampage : Puzzle Attack</name>
		<desc>Using a similar game style to the Game Boy classic, Tetris Attack, a line of blocks sits above the play field which you can change the order of and drop two at a time onto the blocks below. Once a Detoblock (a block that is different in appearance to the usual blocks) appears, drop it onto the corresponding colour to clear those blocks from the field. 
 
Play modes include Clear (clean the playfield of all blocks), Puzzle (try and clear all blocks within a set number of drops), Marathon (the usual play as far as you can mode) and Rescue Mode, where you must clear the blocks from the top of a cage, in which the many monsters from the arcade hit, Rampage World Tour, are trapped in.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20011229T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ninai Games</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/Rampage - Puzzle Attack (USA, Europe).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="84467" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Rayman - Hoodlum's Revenge (USA) (En,Fr,Es).7z</path>
		<name>Rayman : Hoodlum's Revenge</name>
		<desc>Rayman 3 Hoodlum Havoc will feature many brand new game elements. Its action adventure format will be familiar to many fans but advanced combat will form the heart of this latest installment. Rayman will have new movements and powers including, The Power Fist, Grapple and Super Helicopter, and he will certainly need them as he comes up against over 20 powerful enemies, including the savage Hoodlum tribe. The new Tactical Arcade Combat System will ensure players use their brains, as each enemy has specific strengths and combat strategies, and will only be defeated by the correct fighting techniques.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20030304T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Platform / Fighter Scrolling</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/Rayman - Hoodlum's Revenge (USA) (En,Fr,Es).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="84469" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Rayman - Raving Rabbids (USA) (En,Fr,Es).7z</path>
		<name>Rayman : Raving Rabbids</name>
		<desc>Rayman Raving Rabbids marks the return of the iconic video-game hero, Rayman, in his funniest and zaniest adventure ever. When the world of Rayman is threatened by a devastating invasion of crazed, out-of-control bunnies Rayman must rise up against his furry foes to foil their wicked plans. Utilizing an array of amazing new abilities, and with the help of magical creatures, Rayman must break out all the moves to save his world from these delirious bunnies and their hare-raising antics.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20061207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Rayman - Raving Rabbids (USA) (En,Fr,Es).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3850" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Rayman 3 (USA) (En,Fr,Es).7z</path>
		<name>Rayman 3</name>
		<desc>Rayman returns in an all new adventure with all new abilities, but the same humor that has pervaded the series.

Globox, a friend of Rayman, has placed the world in peril. By eating the Lord of the Dark Lums, Globox has enraged the Hoodlums, who plan to take back their master no matter what the cost to the world around them. It's up to Rayman to save the day and find a cure to rid the Dark Lord from Globox.

New abilities, thanks to power ups littered around the levels, allow Rayman to use the likes of Heavy Metal Fist and the Shock Rocket to take down enemies around him, while the lock jaw allows Rayman to get to hard to reach places.

Rayman 3 can link to a Gamecube via the link port, allowing players to play exclusive mini-games on both systems and download new levels to the GBA.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20030302T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Platform</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Rayman 3 (USA) (En,Fr,Es).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3823" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Rayman Advance (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).7z</path>
		<name>Rayman Advance</name>
		<desc>Rayman Advance is a GBA game. It is basically a port of Rayman 1, however bears some minor changes. The evil Mr. Dark has stolen the Great Protoon, kidnapped all of the Electoons and defeated Betilla the Fairy. Rayman has to travel through 5 worlds before finally meeting up with Mr Dark and defeating him.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20010610T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Digital Eclipse</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Rayman Advance (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4323" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Road Rash - Jailbreak (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Road Rash : Jailbreak</name>
		<desc>This is the Game Boy Advance installment in the long-running motorcycle action series. Players fight for the trophy at the Great Bikers Convention, and burn rubber on the track to win the Wild Race, where driving style and weapons are part of the show. The objective is to defeat the winner of last year's contest and kick the hell out of his gang buddies while doing so. But watch your back: the County Police won't let you slow down for a sec. The Game Boy Advance version was developed by Magic Pockets for Destination Software.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Road Rash - Jailbreak (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4300" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Rock n' Roll Racing (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Rock n' Roll Racing</name>
		<desc>Featuring multiple racetracks and a classic soundtrack, Rock N' Roll Racing puts players behind the wheel for an over-the-top demolition-racing experience. In the game, drivers take their pick from a variety of cars, each equipped with a selection of weaponry designed to help them outmaneuver the competition. Taking advantage of the Game Boy Advance Game Link cable, players can also go head-to-head against each other for fast-paced multiplayer action.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>20030623T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Interplay</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<image>./media/images/Rock n' Roll Racing (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4219" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Samurai Jack - The Amulet of Time (USA, Europe).7z</path>
		<name>Samurai Jack : The Amulet of Time</name>
		<desc>Samurai Jack is a warrior who is banished by the shape-shifting wizard Aku into the bizarre and twisted future. Bearing his new futuristic name, Jack wanders the land searching for a portal back in time to right the wrongs of the past. He has learned of a mysterious Amulet that, when all its pieces are found, will enable him to return to the past.. Join Samurai Jack on a journey of honor and revenge through a futuristic world filled with wonders and help him rid the world of evil once and for all.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20050902T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Zoo Digital Publishing</developer>
		<publisher>Virtucraft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Samurai Jack - The Amulet of Time (USA, Europe).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3852" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Sonic Advance 2 (E).7z</path>
		<name>Sonic Advance 2</name>
		<desc>Sonic returns for a second outing on the Game Boy Advance.

Once again, Sonic is called upon to save the world from the evil Dr. Eggman. On this occasion, Sonic is joined by friends Tails, Knuckles and Cream and rabbit, the latest addition to the Sonic team. Each comes with a set of unique moves, allowing you to reach certain areas through-out the levels. However, unlike Sonic Advance, you must compelte the game as Sonic to unlock the other characters.

Chaos Emeralds and Special Rings litter the stages. To collect the emeralds (transforming Sonic into Super Sonic for the final battle with Dr. Eggman), you must find the special rings hidden in each stage to unlock the bonus stage. Complete the bonus stage and the emerald is yours.

You'll also get the chance to collect and raise chaos, and trade them over to Sonic Adventure 2: Battle on Gamecube, through the use of the GBA/GC link cable.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20030309T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Sonic Advance 2 (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3852" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Sonic Advance 2 (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).7z</path>
		<name>Sonic Advance 2</name>
		<desc>Sonic returns for a second outing on the Game Boy Advance.

Once again, Sonic is called upon to save the world from the evil Dr. Eggman. On this occasion, Sonic is joined by friends Tails, Knuckles and Cream and rabbit, the latest addition to the Sonic team. Each comes with a set of unique moves, allowing you to reach certain areas through-out the levels. However, unlike Sonic Advance, you must compelte the game as Sonic to unlock the other characters.

Chaos Emeralds and Special Rings litter the stages. To collect the emeralds (transforming Sonic into Super Sonic for the final battle with Dr. Eggman), you must find the special rings hidden in each stage to unlock the bonus stage. Complete the bonus stage and the emerald is yours.

You'll also get the chance to collect and raise chaos, and trade them over to Sonic Adventure 2: Battle on Gamecube, through the use of the GBA/GC link cable.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20030309T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Sonic Advance 2 (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3843" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Sonic Advance 3 (U) (M6).7z</path>
		<name>Sonic Advance 3</name>
		<desc>Eggman has broken the world into seven parts, now the player must find the seven Chaos Emeralds to restore the world. 

Sonic Advance 3 is a Sonic game with a twist: the player can play with a friend in co-op mode or one of many multi-player modes like ring race. The game contains features from Sonic Advance and Sonic Advance 2, but with more options like choosing from 2 characters in story mode (a leading and a following character).</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20040607T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Sonic Advance 3 (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3843" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Sonic Advance 3 (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).7z</path>
		<name>Sonic Advance 3</name>
		<desc>Eggman has broken the world into seven parts, now the player must find the seven Chaos Emeralds to restore the world. 

Sonic Advance 3 is a Sonic game with a twist: the player can play with a friend in co-op mode or one of many multi-player modes like ring race. The game contains features from Sonic Advance and Sonic Advance 2, but with more options like choosing from 2 characters in story mode (a leading and a following character).</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20040607T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Sonic Advance 3 (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3845" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Sonic Advance (E).7z</path>
		<name>Sonic Advance</name>
		<desc>Sonic the Hedgehog has arrived for his first ever adventure on a Nintendo console. Sonic Advance combines elements from the original Sonic series on Sega's Genesis, as well as from the Dreamcast Sonic Adventure series.

Choose from Sonic, Knuckles, Tails, or Amy and take them through level after level of blindingly fast gameplay and ring collecting, dodging enemies in your path towards the final showdown with Dr Robotnik (aka Dr Eggman). 

Collect Chaos Emeralds along the way to transform into Super Sonic for added speed, and train your Chao to exchange them into Sonic Adventure 2 Battle on the Nintendo Gamecube.

And if that wasn't enough, you can also play 4 player battle modes with your mates, using one game cart between 4 GBA's.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20020203T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action-Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Sonic Advance (USA) (En,Ja).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3845" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Sonic Advance (USA) (En,Ja).7z</path>
		<name>Sonic Advance</name>
		<desc>Sonic the Hedgehog has arrived for his first ever adventure on a Nintendo console. Sonic Advance combines elements from the original Sonic series on Sega's Genesis, as well as from the Dreamcast Sonic Adventure series.

Choose from Sonic, Knuckles, Tails, or Amy and take them through level after level of blindingly fast gameplay and ring collecting, dodging enemies in your path towards the final showdown with Dr Robotnik (aka Dr Eggman). 

Collect Chaos Emeralds along the way to transform into Super Sonic for added speed, and train your Chao to exchange them into Sonic Adventure 2 Battle on the Nintendo Gamecube.

And if that wasn't enough, you can also play 4 player battle modes with your mates, using one game cart between 4 GBA's.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20020203T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action-Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Sonic Advance (USA) (En,Ja).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3876" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Sonic Battle (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).7z</path>
		<name>Sonic Battle</name>
		<desc>Sonic Battle is a fast paced pseudo-fighting game akin to Super Smash Bros. Rather than being 3D side-scrolling, the game employs a 3D isometric view that is comprised of actual texture-mapped polygons. The character sprites are 2D.

There are 9 characters to choose from and 5 modes of play: Story, Battle, Challenge, Training, and Mini Games. You can link up 4 GBA's to fight your friends, and each character has several different attacks. It has a system of selecting Aerial, Ground, and Guard based attacks. Depending on what type of attack you set for which area (aerial/ground/guard) you have a possibility of 9 total different special attacks to choose from (only 3 at a time in a match though) which you can change each time you lose 1 stock point.

The game includes a trainable character whose abilities and techniques you can raise and add to. You get to pick and choose every aspect of the robot's style (running, attacking, jumping, dashing, etc.).

The game takes a moderate amount of time to play through as all the characters, and adds a longer lifespan to itself if you wish to play through and beat it completely (all characters, get all moves for the trainable robot, etc).</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20040105T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Fight</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Sonic Battle (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4218" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Sonic Pinball Party (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).7z</path>
		<name>Sonic Pinball Party</name>
		<desc>Sonic Pinball Party is the second Sonic Pinball game since Sonic Spinball in the early 90's. The game has an arcade mode, a tutorial mode, and a vs mode (party mode). In the game the game has pinball tables of famous Sonic Team characters such as Nights, Samba de Amigo, and of course SONIC! 

The story mode of the game is the usual type of story, Robotnik steals animals visiting Casinopolis, and is going turn into his Robotic slaves. Of course, Sonic is going to try and stop him. Before he does, he has to win a pinball competition and during the game you unlock prizes. The competition is set out as a knockout format. The game also has a Casinopolis mode, which has Casino games like Roulette. There is also a chao garden, just like in the Sonic Advance games.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20030601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Pinball-Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Sonic Pinball Party (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="97400" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./SpaceTwins.7z</path>
		<name>Space Twins</name>
		<desc>Very professional and solid platform/puzzle game for Gameboy Advance.</desc>
		<releasedate>20090427T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>9wires</developer>
		<publisher>9wires</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/SpaceTwins.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="84639" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Spider-Man - Battle for New York (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Spider-Man : Battle for New York</name>
		<desc>Spider-Man: Battle for New York allows players to take on the role of Spider-Man, and one of his famed nemeses, Green Goblin. For the first time in a handheld Spider-Man game players can personalize their experiences by choosing what abilities and powers to upgrade and when, such as Spider-Manâ€™s web maneuvers or Green Goblinâ€™s fire attacks.</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20061124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Torus Games</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Spider-Man - Battle for New York (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4026" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Spider-Man - Mysterio's Menace (USA, Europe).7z</path>
		<name>Spider-Man : Mysterio's Menace</name>
		<desc>Set in New York, Spider-Man: Mysterio's Menace enables players to assume the role of Spider-Man as they take on super-villain Mysterio and his illusory tricks for control of Manhattan. Spider-Man must fight a slew of Mysterio's sinister conspirators and gadgetry to get to the bottom of their plot and free New York from Mysterio's mind-warping grip.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20010928T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Vicarious Visions</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Spider-Man - Mysterio's Menace (USA, Europe).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3885" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Spider-Man 2 (USA, Europe).7z</path>
		<name>Spider-Man 2</name>
		<desc>Orphaned at a young age, Peter Parker, a good-hearted teenager, lives in Queens, New York with his aunt and uncle. On a school trip to a research institute, Peter Parker is bitten by a genetically engineered spider and soon discovers that suddenly his vision is perfect and his previously scrawny body has become muscular-he now has incredible strength, and his hands mysteriously adhere like glue to everything. Assume the role of Peter Parker and his alter-ego Spider-man to defend the city from the clutches of evil. Master all-new combat moves and dizzying airborne acrobatics. Move through stunning scenes from the movie as you explore enormous city environments with newfound maneuverability. Battle the world's toughest villains, including Shocker, Vulture, and the Green Goblin.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20040709T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Digital Eclipse</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Spider-Man 2 (USA, Europe).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3859" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Spider-Man 3 (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Spider-Man 3</name>
		<desc>The game's plot expands on the film by including additional characters and elements from the Spider-Man comics and the Marvel Universe. Depending on the platform, different villains from the comics are featured, but all versions of the game feature the film's main villains: Venom, New Goblin, and Sandman.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20070504T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Vicarious Visions</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Spider-Man 3 (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3964" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Spider-Man (USA, Europe).7z</path>
		<name>Spider-Man</name>
		<desc>Spider-Man, the classic comic book co-created by Stan Lee, is now a major motion picture. This conversion of the movie to the video game world takes the major storyline, characters and artwork of the Spider-Man movie and adds a lengthy backstory and new characters. 
 
The Green Goblin is the main villian here, and as Peter Parker you must defy gravity using your spider crawl, web-slinging and spider-sense abilities to track down Spidey's nemesis through the skyscapers of New York City. 
 
The major inclusion for this title over the previous Spider-Man series (on Playstation also by Activision) is aerial combat. Attack the enemy mid-air while web-slinging, rise and decend while swinging and banking around buildings create a greater emphasis on Spidey's greatest asset, the spider web.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20020531T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Treyarch</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Spider-Man (USA, Europe).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3834" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Street Fighter Alpha 3 (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Street Fighter Alpha 3</name>
		<desc>Street Fighter Alpha 3, the third game in the Alpha series, has a total of 31 fighters, the most in the series so far. New characters include old favorites E. Honda, Blanka, Vega, Cammy, T. Hawk, Dee Jay, Juni and Juli. Some of the newest fighters on the block include a former Final Fight character (Cody, who has been in jail since the last Final Fight game, or so his clothing suggests), Karin Kanzuki and Rainbow Mika.

The major difference between this Alpha and the last two are the new play modes World Tour, Arcade, VS, Training and Entry. 

World Tour - Simply choose your fighter and travel around the world, fighting the home town heroes that you run into. The more fights you win, the stronger you fighter becomes. You can also learn new moves, and there are three levels of Super moves to choose from before you start each round (called Isms).

Arcade - A simple conversion of the arcade version. Beat each fighter with your chosen warrior, in three rounds per match (much the same as past versions of Street Fighter)

Versus - Two human players battle it out. 

Training - A good way to learn all the super moves that are available, against a dummy.

Entry - If you save your character during the World Tour mode, you can upload him here to use in the other modes in the game (especially handy for Training).

Finally, if you complete certain areas of the game three new fighters become available, including another old favourite in Guile, Evil Ryu and Shin Akuma.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20021201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crawfish Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/Street Fighter Alpha 3 (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3944" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Super Ghouls'n Ghosts (USA, Europe).7z</path>
		<name>Super Ghouls'n Ghosts</name>
		<desc>As dauntless knight Arthur you are caught up in the most dangerous of quests! A spell has been cast upon the kingdom. Your fair maiden, Princess Prin Prin has been snatched up by the evil emperor. Only as Arthur can you get her back from the creatures of the undead that haunt the land. Test your courage and skill to the limit. You must keep up the quest. On your journey, your mightiest weapon of all awaits you... MAGIC!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20020926T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Super Ghouls'n Ghosts (USA, Europe).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="84712" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Super Mario Advance 2 - Super Mario World (U) [!].7z</path>
		<name>Super Mario Advance 2 - Super Mario World</name>
		<desc>One of Mario's greatest adventures is in your hands! 
 
Bowser and his crew of cruel Koopalings have taken over Dinosaur Island, but luckily, Mario and Luigi are up for some Koopa-kicking. As they ride Yoshi, search for P-Switches, find secret paths, blast fireballs, and soar skyward with the Cape, they'll need to use every trick in the plumber handbook. Dino Rhinos, Chargin' Chucks, and a host of unforgettable enemies await in one of the Mario Bros. biggest and most challenging adventures ever! 
 
-All 96 levels in the palm of your hand! Ride Yoshi from the spooky Forest of Illusion to the super-tough Star Road - everything from the Super NES classic is here, powered up with all-new features for the Game Boy Advance. 
-Luigi's ready, so pick a Bro and go! Now you can play as Mario or his brother, Luigi, who can jump and fly higher than his famous sibling. Which Bro is the best for each stage? 
-Get linked! Using a single Game Pak, link up four players and play the timeless Mario Bros. arcade game. You can even connect with Super Mario Advance Game Paks for Multi-Pak madness!</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20020211T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/Super Mario Advance 2 - Super Mario World (U) [!].png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="84714" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Super Mario Advance 3 - Yoshi's Island (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Super Mario Advance 3 - Yoshi's Island</name>
		<desc>Go for a spin around Yoshi's island. 
 
Baby-sitting a whiny newborn is about as fun as a head cold on the first day of summer vacation. But when Baby Mario falls from the sky, the Yoshis seize the opportunity to do a lot more than change diapers. 
 
The big-hearted Yoshis vow to reunite Baby Mario with his twin brother on the far side of the island. It won't be easy, but the Yoshis are determined to take on a meddling Magikoopa and his entire cast of underhanded underlings. 
 
Brilliant game-designer Shigeru Miyamoto has crammed the island's jungles, caves and snowcapped peaks with one brain-bending surprise after another. Hidden rooms, secret passages, charming minigames, demented bosses and all-new pals await your discovery. 
 
Sure, Yoshi looks cute, but he packs some pretty amazing firepower. He can jump, hover, stomp, pound the ground and slurp up enemies. Best of all, he can throw eggs. Heck, Mario even gets to presto-chango into superfast Superstar Mario, while Yoshi morphs into a toy submarine that shoots itty-bitty torpedoes. 
 
As an added bonus, Yoshi's Island includes six super-challenging levels developed just for the GBA. You can also take a break from baby-sitting duties to indulge in multiplayer Mario Bros. action. 
 
In Super Yoshi's Island: Super Mario Advance 3, the unlikely duo of Yoshi and Baby Mario must together brave a world of infinite surprise and challenge. Richly varied gameplay, brilliant graphics and precision control perfectly meld in an adventure you won't be able to put down!</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20020924T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Super Mario Advance 3 - Yoshi's Island (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3813" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Super Mario Advance 4 - Super Mario Bros. 3 (USA, Australia) (Rev 1).7z</path>
		<name>Super Mario Advance 4 : Super Mario Bros. 3</name>
		<desc>A combination of exciting platforming action, wild power-ups, and charming Mario style has made Super Mario Bros. 3 a classic. With Super Mario Advance 4: Super Mario Bros. 3, you have your chance to partake in the special adventure anywhere you go on your Game Boy Advance. Your mission is to rescue the Mushroom Kingdom monarchs who have been transformed into animals by Bowser and his mischievous offspring, and in the process save the princess kidnapped by Bowser. Traverse eight huge worlds and encounter fun minigames and frantic boss battles as you explore the first Mario game to use an overworld map.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20031021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Super Mario Advance 4 - Super Mario Bros. 3 (USA, Australia) (Rev 1).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3820" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Super Mario Advance (E).7z</path>
		<name>Super Mario Advance</name>
		<desc>Super Mario Advance is the adaptation on GBA of Super Mario Bros 2 released on NES. This episode marks a turning point in the series as it introduces the possibility of choosing his character. Embody the famous tandem of mustachio plumbers, Princess Peach or her companion Toad in a magical adventure. You must save the inhabitants of the dream world from the clutches of the ignoble Wart, the batrachian tyrant. This version offers as a bonus a revamped version of the game Mario Bros.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20010610T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Super Mario Advance (E).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3820" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Super Mario Advance (USA, Europe).7z</path>
		<name>Super Mario Advance</name>
		<desc>Super Mario Advance is the adaptation on GBA of Super Mario Bros 2 released on NES. This episode marks a turning point in the series as it introduces the possibility of choosing his character. Embody the famous tandem of mustachio plumbers, Princess Peach or her companion Toad in a magical adventure. You must save the inhabitants of the dream world from the clutches of the ignoble Wart, the batrachian tyrant. This version offers as a bonus a revamped version of the game Mario Bros.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20010610T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Super Mario Advance (E).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3963" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles 2 - Battle Nexus (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles 2 : Battle Nexus</name>
		<desc>Play with 
Up To 4 Players! 
Venture with the Turtles to shell and back in TMNT 2: BattleNexus . Pick up the action on a strange new planet with mysterious new technology. Two tail-kickin' modes deliver green-knuckled action including Story and Battle Nexus Mode! 
 
-Specialized moves for each Turtle! 
-4-player shell-action! 
-Cooperative play &amp; head-to-head four player competition</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20041119T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles 2 - Battle Nexus (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3873" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles</name>
		<desc>The heroes in a half shell are back in an all new adventure. The four turtles have been split up in order to combat the many bad guys that surround the city.

Each turtle (Leonardo, Michelangelo, Raphael &amp; Donatello) has their own set of levels to complete, with their own distinct moves and combat options to use during battle. Along with a set of side-scrolling levels, complete with end of level boss battles, the four turtles will also get the chance to race through the sewers in the unique 3rd person race modes, shooting down the enemy or collecting items, while Donatello takes to the sky in the Shell Glider and Raphael challenges Casey Jones to a one-on-one cycle race.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20031024T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up-Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3930" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Tekken Advance (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Tekken Advance</name>
		<desc>With nine playable characters, multiple gameplay modes and link cable support for two players, Tekken Advance is port of the original arcade fighter. You'll find all your favorite fighters including Jin Kazama, Paul Phoenix, Forest Law and Gun Jack, as well as Hwoarang, King, Ling Xiaoyu, Nina Williams, and Yoshimitsu. This version of Tekken is only available on the Game Boy Advance.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>20020128T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/Tekken Advance (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4148" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Top Gear Rally (USA).7z</path>
		<name>TG Rally</name>
		<desc>Race through 10 circuits, each one tougher then the last and featuring different terrain, in an attempt to beat the other 7 rally racers on the track.
Choose your rally car and make any changes required in order to compete with the other drivers. You can save copy of your ghost to race against, or compete against a friend using the link cable.

You can also upload your best times for each track on the internet, using the Worldwide Ranking system. By entering the password given to you after each race, you can enter it on the site and compare with other drivers around the globe.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20030921T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kemco</developer>
		<publisher>Kemco</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving-Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/Top Gear Rally (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="84787" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Incredible Hulk, The (USA).7z</path>
		<name>The Incredible Hulk</name>
		<desc>Prepare for the most furious game ever to hit the Game BoyÂ® Advance. You are Dr. Bruce Banner, a government scientist transformed into The Hulk after a nuclear test gone wrong. Rage through more than 30 levels of intense action, crushing everythign and everyone in your way, and when you are done destroying your enemies, link up with your friends and battle it out in a multiplayer Hulk-Match!</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20030611T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pocket Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Universal Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Incredible Hulk, The (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4072" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./King of Fighters EX, The - NeoBlood (USA) (Rev 1).7z</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters EX : Neo Blood</name>
		<desc>Invitations to the King of Fighters Tournament have been sent to the best fighters in the world by an unknown host. Despite suspicions of an evil scheme, the fighters are ready to enter the arena to determine who the true King of Fighters will be.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20021105T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Artoon</developer>
		<publisher>Sammy Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Fight-Fight / 2D-Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/King of Fighters EX, The - NeoBlood (USA) (Rev 1).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3948" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./King of Fighters EX2, The - Howling Blood (USA).7z</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters EX 2 : Howling Blood</name>
		<desc>The latest portable fighting masterpiece in one of the greatest series of all time!</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20031210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Marvelous Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/King of Fighters EX2, The - Howling Blood (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="84036" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - A Link To The Past Four Swords (U) [!].7z</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda : A Link to the Past &amp; Four Swords</name>
		<desc>The Legend of Zelda: A Link to the Past &amp; Four Swords for Game Boy Advance is a remake of A Link to the Past coupled with an entirely new game, Four Swords. This two-in-one game was released shortly before The Wind Waker. 
 
While A Link to the Past is largely a faithful port of the original, it does include an entirely new dungeon and a new quest as rewards for the player playing through the multiplayer-only Four Swords. Aside from these additions, it includes a number of smaller gameplay and dialogue changes, the latter of which are designed to correct a number of minor translation mistakes and inconsistencies with the original Japanese release and to unify the common terms used with the later games.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20021202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Legend of Zelda, The - A Link To The Past Four Swords (U) [!].png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3751" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - The Minish Cap (U).7z</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda: The Minish Cap</name>
		<desc>Link returns in an all-new Game Boy Advance adventure. When the sorcerer Vaati turns Princess Zelda to stone, the king of Hyrule sends Link on a quest that takes him to all-new locations. Using the power of a mystical hat called the Minish Cap, Link must travel through a fantastic world rife with new items, puzzles, and bosses. As Link, you can shrink down to either battle large enemies from within or find secret items. You can also unlock items and solve puzzles by fusing together magic relics.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20050110T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games-Adventure-Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Legend of Zelda, The - The Minish Cap (U).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="84820" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Sims 2, The (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl).7z</path>
		<name>The Sims 2</name>
		<desc>Sims become stars in this platform-specific port of the popular PC sequel. From an isometric perspective similar to that of the original home computer version of The Sims, Game Boy Advance players guide their custom Sims 2 characters to tend to basic needs, interact with in-game objects, and make friends (or enemies) with other characters. Set in the extraterrestrial-friendly Strangetown, the game casts the player's character as the star of a hit "reality" television series, and the game's storyline progresses from one episode to the next, according to how well the character can stick to the script.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20051024T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Amaze Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<image>./media/images/Sims 2, The (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="84615" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Sims 2, The - Pets (USA, Europe).7z</path>
		<name>The Sims 2: Pets</name>
		<desc>Create Your Sim choose your Sims' gender, skin tone, hairstyle, hair colour and aspirations. 
Adopt a Pet pick out the perfect pet at The Pet Shop, each day six new pets are available for adoption. 
Make some Simoleans! choose from a variety of careers including Pet Sitting, Animal Education, Veterinary Medicine and Animal Para-Psychology. 
Pets with personality like their Sim friends, pets have personalities that determine their behaviour including neatness, friendliness, playfulness and activeness. But remember, you can't always teach old dogs new tricks! 
Teaching and Training have your Sim train their pet to compete in pet shows.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20061109T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Artificial Mind &amp; Movement</developer>
		<publisher>EA Games</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Sims 2, The - Pets (USA, Europe).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="84616" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Sims, The - Bustin' Out (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl).7z</path>
		<name>The Sims: Bustin' Out</name>
		<desc>The Sims Bustin' Out is the second title in The Sims console series and the first The Sims title to not be released on PC. It featured the same 3D environment and engine the past game did, however adds several features from The Sims expansion packs: The Sims: Hot Date, The Sims: Superstar, and The Sims: Livin' Large. Bustin' Out was released for the Game Boy Advance, GameCube, PlayStation 2, Xbox and N-Gage in the fourth quarter of 2003. As the title suggests, the Sims can get out of the house to visit other locations such as Shiny Things Lab or Casa Caliente. There are two modes. Bust Out Mode which has mission based gameplay and Freeplay Mode which is open-ended gameplay very much like the original The Sims PC game.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20031202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Griptonite Games</developer>
		<publisher>EA Games</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Sims, The - Bustin' Out (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4202" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Tony Hawk's Downhill Jam (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Downhill Jam</name>
		<desc>Tony Hawk's Downhill Jam delivers a totally unique skateboard experience focused on head-to-head racing. The game allows players to feel the breakneck speed of downhill competition as they tear up the world's steepest terrains while performing tricks and outmanoeuvring opponents in such locations as San Francisco, Machu Picchu and Hong Kong. Taking on the role of Tony Hawk or one of nine characters, players compete in time-based challenges in one of three gameplay modes, including race, trick and slalom.</desc>
		<rating>0.1</rating>
		<releasedate>20061110T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<image>./media/images/Tony Hawk's Downhill Jam (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3865" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2 (USA, Europe).7z</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2</name>
		<desc>The Tony Hawk skateboarding series makes its debut on the Game Boy Advance with this adaptation of the second Pro Skater game.

Gameplay is similar to the original console game. The levels have been adapted from the console version for the two dimensional isometric perspective; one is even taken from the original Tony Hawk's Pro Skater.

In Career Mode, choose from one of 13 professional skaters and, in each level, complete various goals like collecting items, performing special tricks and of course breaking high scores by performing tricks and combos. Completing the goals earns money which unlocks new levels and can be spent on new boards, tricks and upgrading your skater's stats. In competition levels, you don't skate for money but compete for a medal.

In the Free Skate and Single Session modes, unlocked levels can be practiced and new high scores be established.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20010622T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Neversoft</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2 (USA, Europe).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3940" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 3 (USA, Europe).7z</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 3</name>
		<desc>Tony Hawk returns with an all new line-up of skaters, an all new line-up of parks to crash through, and a whole new level of graphics.

The line-up of street and vert riders include Elissa Steamer, Jamie Thomas, Steve Caballero, Rune Glifberg, Geoff Rowley, Andrew Reynolds, Rodney Mullen, Eric Koston, Chad Muska, Bucky Lasek and Bam Margera from MTV's Jackass (and Tony Hawk, of course).

The create a skater mode returns, allowing for even further levels of options for your character, like adding glasses and tatoos to changing the colour of the knee and elbow pads or even the hair.

And the levels themselves that you must skate through are now more interactive, with cars and humans blocking paths and making noise as you race around to make as many points as possible. Use items around the streets or the park to jump from or over to increase your score, and pull of as many wild and wacky tricks as you can.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>20020322T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vicarious Visions</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 3 (USA, Europe).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3968" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 4 (USA, Europe).7z</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 4</name>
		<desc>THPS4 is the fourth game in Activision's ever popular franchise.

The main feature of this game is it's redesigned career mode.  When beginning a level, you have all the time in the world to skate around, perform tricks, get a feel for the level, without the hassel of any goals or time limits.  When you're ready to attempt a goal, simply find a pro skater, talk to him, then receive the goal, similar to Dave Mirra Freestyle BMX.  Goals are similar to the previous games, such as collect SKATE, get a certain amount of points, transfer over this and grind that.  There are new goals, however, such as collecting the word COMBO while doing one big combo.  Miss a trick, and goal fails.  Once all regular goals are accomplished, you can attempt the Pro Goal, which is specific to each skater, and is extremely hard.

All the major skaters are here, including Tony Hawk, Bob Burnquist, Steve Caballero, Kareem Campbell, Rune Gilfberg, Eric Koston, Bucky Lasek, Bam Margera, Rodney Mullen, Chad Muska, Andrew Reynolds, Geoff Rowley, Elissa Steamer and Jamie Thomas.

The levels are been expanded and are huge.  Some of the levels include a college campus, a shipyard, and the infamous prison complex Alcatraz.

For multiplayer, all the favorite modes are back, from Graffiti and Trick Attack to Horse and King Of The Hill.  New modes include Capture The Flag and Combo Mambo.  THPS4 also supports System Link play, but not XBox Live.

The PlayStation 2 version offers everything from the XBox version, but also has online play, utilizing either your own network adaptor or the official one.  The PS2 version also features a one level demo of Shaun Murray's Pro Wakeboarder, which is not featured on any other version of the game.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20021122T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vicarious Visions</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 4 (USA, Europe).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3891" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Tony Hawk's Underground 2 (USA, Europe).7z</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Underground 2</name>
		<desc>Tony Hawk's Underground 2 is based on the console games of the same name.  Like the previous GBA releases of the series, it's an isometric representation of the console levels combined with polygonal characters.  It contains both a story mode, in which you create a rookie skater and take him or her on a world tour with pros to improve their skills and win prizes; and a classic mode, in which you must accomplish various goals such as tricking off objects or getting a high score within two minutes.  Changes in this iteration include removing the timer from most goals in story mode, allowing you to have several active at once and new moves like the nata spin, tantrum, which allows you to recover from a bail without losing everything, focus, where you can slow time in order to land the best trick and sticker-slapping.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20041022T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vicarious Visions</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/Tony Hawk's Underground 2 (USA, Europe).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4177" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Tony Hawk's Underground (USA, Europe).7z</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Underground</name>
		<desc>Like earlier entries in the Tony Hawk skateboarding series on the Game Boy Advance, Tony Hawk's Underground adapts the console title to the handheld platform using isometric graphics and polygonal characters.The main game mode is story mode. Players creat</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20031027T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<image>./media/images/Tony Hawk's Underground (USA, Europe).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4505" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Top Gear GT Championship (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Top Gear GT Championship</name>
		<desc>Top Gear GT Championship carries the official Japanese GT title and lets players race fast cars on different GT tracks. The game features two main game modes: quick race and championship. In quick race, players can alone, against another human player or create custom courses for the game. This is further divided into versus games against the computer and time attack. The game can also connect through mobile phones to check global rankings, enter local ranking entries, and download ghosts and new courses.

In the championship mode, players need to complete the courses in a fixed order while a ranking is kept. The cars are shown from a third-person perspective and there are different AI-controlled racers to beat. Prior to the races, players can do free runs, qualify and eventually start the race or tune the car further. There are two weather types, sunny and rainy, which affects the handling of the cars.

There are different cars and courses to choose from, with extensive tuning options based on the gear ratio, steering, brakes, tires, aerodynamic settings and the height handicap. There are also three difficulty levels.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20010628T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vision Works</developer>
		<publisher>Kemco</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/Top Gear GT Championship (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4015" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Turok Evolution (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Turok Evolution</name>
		<desc>The game begins with the seer, Tarkeen, explaining the history of the Lost Lands which had, for years, been fought over by tyrannic warlords. 
 
On earth during the old west, Tal'Set faces off his enemy, Captain Bruckner and succeeds in cutting off his arm, but both of them are sucked into a wormhole. Tal'Set is nearly killed and the people of the River Village, who found him, call upon Tarkeen to heal him. Tarkeen then commands them to bring Tal'Set to him. He is sent into the jungle and kills enemy factions, lizard-like enemies known as the Sleg, that are close to the Village. Tal'Set hooks up with Genn, a pilot from the Village, who will be guiding him to the seer. Along the way, he uses the Pterosaur to evict the Sleg from the jungle and destroy their air ship.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20020901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>RFX Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/Turok Evolution (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="97401" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Uranus Zero EV.7z</path>
		<name>Uranus Zero Ev</name>
		<desc>Third game of "Uranus" serie from ZoneGN, in his "easy version".
This is a vertical scrolling space shooter. Very good from what I've played (using VisualBoyAdvance), with good graphics, music, and the action was pretty fierce as well.</desc>
		<releasedate>20030101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ZoneGN</developer>
		<publisher>ZoneGN</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Vertical-Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Uranus Zero EV.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="97402" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Uranus Zero.7z</path>
		<name>Uranus Zero</name>
		<desc>Third game of "Uranus" serie from ZoneGN.
This is a vertical scrolling space shooter. Very good from what I've played (using VisualBoyAdvance), with good graphics, music, and the action was pretty fierce as well.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>ZoneGN</developer>
		<publisher>ZoneGN</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Shoot'em up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Uranus Zero.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="97403" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Uranus.7z</path>
		<name>Uranus</name>
		<desc>First game of "Uranus" serie from ZoneGN. 
 
This is a vertical scrolling space shooter. Very good from what I've played (using VisualBoyAdvance), with good graphics, music, and the action was pretty fierce as well.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>ZoneGN</developer>
		<publisher>ZoneGN</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Shoot'em up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Uranus.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="97404" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Uranus2.7z</path>
		<name>Uranus2</name>
		<desc>Second game of "Uranus" serie from ZoneGN. 
 
This is a vertical scrolling space shooter. Very good from what I've played (using VisualBoyAdvance), with good graphics, music, and the action was pretty fierce as well.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>ZoneGN</developer>
		<publisher>ZoneGN</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Shoot'em up / Vertical</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Uranus2.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4086" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Virtua Tennis (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Virtua Tennis</name>
		<desc>Virtua Tennis arrives on the GBA, without the 'Virtual' 3D element, but with the same gameplay you expect from a tennis game.

Choose from a male or female player (or create your own) and take to the world tour, competing in various tournaments on clay, hardcourt, grass or indoors. Play against some of the best players in the world, both in singles and doubles, or compete against your friends in 4 player doubles.

Mini-games test your skills and improves the timing of your shots. Games range from Burger Chef (aim at the grid to decide what comes next on the burger), Disc Shooter (similar to Othello) and Bull's Eye, where you aim for the center of the target. Your created character will also improve depending on your success in each mini-game, with his or her stats increasing over time.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20020925T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>THQ</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Tennis-Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./media/images/Virtua Tennis (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3950" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./V-Rally 3 (USA) (En,Fr,Es).7z</path>
		<name>V-Rally 3</name>
		<desc>The rally racing series comes to the GBA with texture mapped 3d graphics that take the GBA in a direction never thought possible.
Players can choose from a variety of game modes including rally racing, circuit racing and time trials or link up and go head to head with another player. The better and further you get the more cars and tracks are unlocked.
View the race from inside the car or behind it as you scream through snow, rain, fog, dirt, gravel and over jumps at different times of day and night as you try to become the best rally racer on the planet.
Features battery backup.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20020621T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infogrames</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/V-Rally 3 (USA) (En,Fr,Es).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="97408" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Waimanu (disjointedstudio).7z</path>
		<name>Waimanu - Grinding Blocks Adventure</name>
		<desc>Waimanu for Gameboy Advance - Planet Earth is threatened by Wekas, evil alien Jellies who invaded the planet with the intent of colonizing it. Daring Waimanu will face them to defend the fate of our planet! 
 
Waimanu can push blocks and make them slide, and sliding blocks can squash Wekas between them. He can also destroy blocks that can't be moved because they're against a wall or if there's another block behind them. Also Wekas can destroy blocks whenever they want to try to reach our hero.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20130709T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Disjointed Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Disjointed Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Waimanu (disjointedstudio).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="3952" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Yoshi - Topsy-Turvy (USA).7z</path>
		<name>Yoshi : Topsy-Turvy</name>
		<desc>In his attempt to stop Bowser's mischief, Hongo the Great Book Spirit sealed him in a pop-up book, along with Yoshi's Island which is where Bowser was located at the time. The Spirit who loves Surprises showed up and told Yoshi the dinosaur there is a way to bring Yoshi's Island back. 
 
It's up to Yoshi to save the day in Yoshi Topsy-Turvy. The game is divided into six chapters, each containing numerous stages. The player will have to tilt the world (using the tilt sensor) to help Yoshi climb walls, open new paths, and send enemies rolling away. Happiness Medals should be earned, allowing the player to move on to the next chapter if Yoshi successfully clears certain objectives that the Spirits ask of him. Along the way, Yoshi will be transformed into a ship, a ball, and a balloon.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050422T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Artoon</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Yoshi - Topsy-Turvy (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="4479" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Zooo (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).7z</path>
		<name>Zooo</name>
		<desc>The zoo animals have revolted against the zoo keeper. It is your job to restore order and "capture" all of the animals.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20050804T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Robot</developer>
		<publisher>Success</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Zooo (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="84030" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Lara Croft Tomb Raider - Legend (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).7z</path>
		<name>Lara Croft Tomb Raider : Legend</name>
		<desc>The most famous explorer of all time arrives in a new adventure illustrated by Tomb Raider Legend on GBA. Lara Croft sets out in search of one of the world's most precious treasures, a weapon capable of bringing peace to the world but also of precipitating its fall. So avoid the traps in your path, fight your enemies who are fighting for the same loot and use the beauty's acrobatic skills to get out of it.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Lara Croft Tomb Raider - Legend (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20061110T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Human Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Action / Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220304T073228</lastplayed>
		<gametime>22</gametime>
	</game>
	<game id="3933" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Aladdin (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es).7z</path>
		<name>Aladdin</name>
		<desc>Based on the classic game for the SNES and Disney's animated film, Disney's Aladdin joins the Game Boy Advance library with all-new features. In this side-scrolling platform game, you'll take the role of Aladdin and his mischievous monkey, Abu, as they throw apples, climb ropes, and ride magic carpets to find out their destinies. Disney's Aladdin features a bonus stage for each level and a variety of environments to explore, including Jafar's castle, the Genie's lamp, and an ancient pyramid.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Aladdin (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es).png</image>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20040928T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Disney Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20141231T200141</lastplayed>
		<gametime>180</gametime>
	</game>
	<game id="3949" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./007 - Everything or Nothing (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De).7z</path>
		<name>007 : Everything or Nothing</name>
		<desc>Think like Bond, act like Bond, and experience an entirely new Bond adventure. James Bond, the world's greatest secret agent, returns in Everything or Nothing with new guns and gadgets, combat skills, and clever tricks--and it's up to you to put them to good use. Travel through four exciting continents including the Valley of the Kings in Egypt and the French Quarter in New Orleans. The game also features two-player co-op missions and four-player multiplayer arena modes.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/007 - Everything or Nothing (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De).png</image>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20040411T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Griptonite Games</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter-Shooter / 3rd person</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>de,en,fr</lang>
		<region>eu</region>
	</game>
</gameList>
