<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game id="107041" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Himitsu no Hanazono (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Himitsu No Hanazono</name>
		<desc>A high-school student named K?suke had a dream, in which he saw a beautiful woman talking to him. The next morning he found out that the new teacher looked very similar to the woman he saw. After overhearing a conversation, K?suke realizes that the new teacher is in fact a detective sent to investigate the murder of a female student that occurred in the gym. The young man has to play his cards right in order to become part of the investigation, solve the mystery, and perhaps impress the attractive teacher in other ways. 
 
Himitsu no Hanazono is essentially a visual novel. There are no verb commands and no real interaction with the environment. The choices are rather frequent and fairly numerous (usually four or five choices at most screens). Most of these choices, however, do not affect the plot, though they may alter subsequent dialogue. The player is also able to navigate the protagonist on school grounds and inside the main building in a top-down fashion, visiting locations in any order.</desc>
		<releasedate>19931210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tokuma Shoten</developer>
		<publisher>Tokuma Shoten</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Himitsu no Hanazono (Japan).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="106884" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Jantei Monogatari (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Jantei Monogatari</name>
		<desc>A daughter of the chair of a local high school, Y? Honj?, has been kidnapped by someone unknown. Unable to go to the police, the girl's sister, Mai, hires a private investigator to find out what happened to her. The only piece of evidence is a photograph from the night of Y?'s disappearance, where the missing girl and three other students from the same school are playing a game of mahjong.

Jantei Monogatari is a hybrid of a traditional-style Japanese adventure game and a regular mahjong game. The player takes the role of the unnamed private investigator, and moves from place to place via menus, talking to different characters. The investigation happens through playing mahjong with each suspect: win and they'll tell you a bit more of what they know. At first, the investigator can only speak with the three girls in the photo, but as he wins games of mahjong against them, he gains information and experience that allow him to find new clues and talk to more suspects. The investigator will need to play against a dozen different opponents in his attempt to find out what happened to the kidnapped girl.</desc>
		<releasedate>19901009T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>A.I</developer>
		<publisher>Renovation Products</publisher>
		<genre>Asiatic board game-Mahjong</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Jantei Monogatari (Japan).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="106882" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Juuouki (Japan) (Rev 5).chd</path>
		<name>Juu Ou Ki - Beast King's Chronicle</name>
		<desc>Zeus has called upon you! Only a brave and fearless warrior can save his beloved daughter, Athena, from the cunning clutches of Nelf, evil Lord of the Underworld. Risen from the grave, you are presented with supernatural powers beyond this world. Collect the mystical spirit balls and transform into an awesome array of creatures - as Strongman, punch and kick harder than ever before, as WereWolf and WereTiger, rip the flesh of the demons of hell, and as Bear, knock out your enemies with one bad breath! You hear the distant cries of the beautiful Athena and as the terrors of the Underworld tighten their grasp, the beast within you rises to face the final battle! 
This game was released only for the japanese NEC PC Engine.</desc>
		<releasedate>19890922T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Juuouki.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="106882" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Juuouki.chd</path>
		<name>Juu Ou Ki - Beast King's Chronicle</name>
		<desc>Zeus has called upon you! Only a brave and fearless warrior can save his beloved daughter, Athena, from the cunning clutches of Nelf, evil Lord of the Underworld. Risen from the grave, you are presented with supernatural powers beyond this world. Collect the mystical spirit balls and transform into an awesome array of creatures - as Strongman, punch and kick harder than ever before, as WereWolf and WereTiger, rip the flesh of the demons of hell, and as Bear, knock out your enemies with one bad breath! You hear the distant cries of the beautiful Athena and as the terrors of the Underworld tighten their grasp, the beast within you rises to face the final battle! 
This game was released only for the japanese NEC PC Engine.</desc>
		<releasedate>19890922T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Juuouki.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="141176" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Tengai Makyou - Deden no Den.chd</path>
		<name>Tengai Makyou - Deden No Den</name>
		<desc>Deden no Den is a promotional version of Bomberman '94 with limited distribution. The game was only available through Hudson's newsletter at their Caravan Tournament. It contains only one level of the full game (2 to 5-player modes only), but replaces the titular character with Kabuki Danj?r?, a popular character from Tengai Maky? games. Players control up to five Kabukis in differently-colored outfits.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930710T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./media/images/Tengai Makyou - Deden no Den.png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="106996" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Kick Boxing, The (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>The Kick Boxing</name>
		<desc>Endorsed by André Panza, this video game adaptation of Thai kick boxing features over 35 moves. Use the training gym to build up your character's abilities until you feel ready to take on an opponent. You also have the ability to customize your attacks. When you are ready, go to the ring to take on various opponents as you try to become the best kick boxer in the game. </desc>
		<releasedate>19921213T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Futura</developer>
		<publisher>Micro World</publisher>
		<genre>Sports-Sports / Boxing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./media/images/Kick Boxing, The (Japan).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="141122" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Duo Comic - Bakuretsu Hunter (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>ZZZ(notgame):Duo Comic - Bakuretsu Hunter</name>
		<desc>Duo Comic: Bakuretsu Hunter is a digital comic episode based on the manga and anime series Sorcerer Hunters by Satoru Akahori. The plot focuses on a group of heroes who protect humans from the tyranny of the powerful Sorcerers. The group is led by the young Carrot Glace, who is able to transform into a powerful beast when he is not trying to get dates with beautiful women. 
 
The digital comic is accompanied by voice acting, music and sound effects. It is possible to change the color tint of the comic pages. Pages can be flipped automatically (with various speeds), or by pressing a button. There is no actual interaction, and no possibility to affect the story.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Media Works Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Media Works Inc.</publisher>
		<image>./media/images/Duo Comic - Bakuretsu Hunter (Japan).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="14466" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Akumajou Dracula X - Chi no Rinne (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Akumajou Dracula X - Chi no Rondo</name>
		<desc>In the days of old, the people thrived on peace and prosperity. Indeed, fears of unrest were not among their thoughts... 
 
But, ever-present, beneath the veneer of tranquility, evil lurks. Evil, which spurns prosperity and disdains peace. 
 
Gather they did, those who wished to summon the powers of darkness and cleanse the decadence of the world. And, with smiling countenance, they anxiously awaited the coming of their era. 
 
A hundred years had past, and he was resurrected. Able to become bat, wolf, or mist at will, he lived in the night. He drank the blood of young maidens and lived an eternal life. The lord of Castlevania, the god of evil, Count Dracula was reborn.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Akumajou Dracula X - Chi no Rinne (Japan).png</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19931029T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220322T150055</lastplayed>
		<gametime>202</gametime>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game id="103566" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Bomberman 94 Taikenban (JP).chd</path>
		<name>Bomberman '94 Taikenban</name>
		<desc>Bomberman '94 (??????'94 Bonb?man Nint? F??) is a video game from the Bomberman series which was developed and published by Hudson Soft for the PC Engine and released on December 10, 1993 in Japan. It was later re-developed by Westone and re-published by Sega as Mega Bomberman on the Sega Mega Drive/Genesis in 1994 in other areas. The PC Engine Bomberman '94 was later released outside Japan through the Wii's Virtual Console and the PlayStation 3's PlayStation Network.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/Bomberman 94 Taikenban (JP).png</image>
		<releasedate></releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>5</players>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
	<game id="106873" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./CD Battle - Hikari no Yuusha-tachi (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Cd Battle - Hikari No Yuusha-tachi</name>
		<desc>CD Battle is a game for two players that prompts each of them to insert an audio CD into the console in order to generate a party of three characters for each player, which then engage in a turn-based battle. The characters belong to different classes (warrior, mage, ninja, etc.) and have different parameters and special attacks. Despite the game's visual similarity to contemporary Final Fantasy games, it has no true role-playing elements and consists entirely of battles.</desc>
		<image>./media/images/CD Battle - Hikari no Yuusha-tachi (Japan).png</image>
		<releasedate>19930319T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>King Record Co. Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>King Record Co. Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>jp</lang>
		<region>jp</region>
	</game>
</gameList>
